Chapter 1852 – The Concept of Death

At the Fallen God Mountain Range, there were a considerable number of young elites that could light up the fifth soul sea mark after spending five or six years here. But, the light of their soul sea marks would be dim, like a candle fading in the wind.

In this sort of situation it would be impossible for them to light the sixth soul sea mark.

Thus, within the history of the spiritas, it was extremely rare for anyone to manage to light the sixth soul sea mark. If one did, they would inevitably become some great figure in the future.

Of these people there were peak Empyreans and True Divinities. Even the worst amongst them were ordinary Empyreans and these ordinary Empyreans had bumpy roads growing up or had exhausted their potential midway.

The sixth soul sea was incredibly difficult to reach. It was a miracle to light it up.

And now, whether it was Lin Ming or Sheng Mei, both were rushing to the sixth soul sea, challenging this enormously difficult checkpoint.

As it stood, no one believed that Lin Ming or Sheng Mei would fail the sixth soul sea checkpoint. This was because those that failed all shared a common factor, and that was that they barely managed to open the fifth soul sea mark. However, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s fifth soul sea marks shined like stars and moons, shocking anyone who saw them.

In the opinion of those watching, it was only a matter of time until Sheng Mei and Lin Ming lit up the sixth soul seas.

Grasping the principles atop the shrine platforms wasn’t something accomplished quickly. When ancient True Divinities were in their youth and came here to attempt grasping the principles, they would often spend ten years or longer here.

And these young True Divinities would come here on several occasions, grasping different principles and experiencing different things each time.

As Lin Ming thought, the shrine platforms of the Fallen God Mountain Range were more than just vehicles for one to obtain the golden page. Rather, they were a profound inheritance left behind by the creator of the Holy Scripture. How much one could comprehend all depended on one’s ability.

Ancient True Divinities even regarded this as a cultivation land.

“It is said that the Great Brahmic God King spent five years here to light the sixth soul sea, and then tried grasping further principles for another six years but failed to accomplish anything. A thousand years after that when the Great Brahmic God King was almost 3000 years old, he returned to the Fallen God Mountain Range once more. At that time, he was a peak Great World King and nearly a half-step Empyrean, but his attempt at enlightenment remained unchanged from the past and he wasn’t able to light up the final soul sea mark.”

In the crowd, someone recounted the history of the peerless characters that came from the Soul World.

“I don’t know how long Empress Sheng Mei will take, but her results will definitely be better than those of the Great Brahmic God King!”

“There’s also that Lin Muk. Although I don’t want to admit it… he is really too fierce. Perhaps… he really might be able to create a miracle.”

The Great Brahmic God King had spent five years. If Sheng Mei or Lin Ming were able to accomplish the same in four years, that would already be a world-shocking event.

This was equivalent to surpassing a True Divinity when at the same boundary!

In particular, the Great Brahmic God King was someone who had shocked the world with a single feat during his youth, a peerless character who grew up overwhelming everyone around him. He wasn’t like some True Divinities who slowly matured and only displayed their incredible potential during the World King or Empyrean realm.

At this time, within the world of his mind, Lin Ming had used a full month but still wasn’t able to see the black shadow that Ruby spoke of.

All he saw was black fog filled with death energy all around him. This black fog seemed to possess the power to destroy all, making it so that no one could see through it.

Moreover, the continuous consumption of soul force left Lin Ming a bit impatient. After Lin Ming comprehended a part of the Life Laws, he originally was able to absorb soul force from the world to restore himself, thus he didn’t need to rest. Even sitting in meditation for 10 years at a single time shouldn’t be a problem.

But in this world of death, the Concept of Life was suppressed and Lin Ming could feel the life force within him constantly leaking out. Once he exhausted the entirety of his strength, he would have no choice but to awake from his meditation and leave the shrine platform to rest.

Lin Ming didn’t want to give up halfway during his attempt at enlightenment. Trying to grasp the principles like this meant that he would have to comprehend from the start again and would waste a massive amount of time. Moreover, his comprehensions wouldn’t form a whole, making it so that there would be certain areas lacking in his enlightenment.

“Ruby, is that person’s shadow there?”

Lin Ming asked. Ruby pointed towards a direction and said, “Over there, just 30 feet away, he’s killing a vicious beast!”

After Lin Ming heard this a severe light flashed in his eyes. He shot forwards like an arrow, firing straight towards the direction that Ruby pointed in. And the distance he went was exactly 30 feet!

“Ahh!”

Ruby was frightened to see Lin Ming’s sudden movement. This was because the place where Lin Ming stopped was right in front of that black shadow’s scythe!

“Brother Lin!”

Ruby paled. At this time, the scythe was already slashing Lin Ming!

Shua!

The scythe cut across Lin Ming’s body. As the blade bit into his body, he could feel the sharp black edge and the aura of death within it. In that moment, he felt as if his own soul would be severed.

An incomparably rich death energy poured out from the scythe blade and poured itself into Lin Ming’s body, making his heart nearly stop. In that moment, Lin Ming thought he had really been killed! Even his fires of life began to rapidly fade away because of this strike!

However, this was only a fleeting moment. The shadow left and the vicious beast lay dead. As for Lin Ming, he had only been casually cut through.

Lin Ming fell to his knees, his entire body streaming with a cold sweat. That strike had consumed a massive amount of his soul force, and he even thought that his spiritual sea would be sliced in half!

As the scythe cut across his head, Lin Ming felt the world around him disappear. All that was left over was the scythe formed from death itself, swallowing everything!

“How terrifying! A mere phantom left behind from 10 billion years ago actually possesses such power!”

Lin Ming understood what happened. It was impossible for the scythe phantom from 10 billion years ago to possess any material striking power. But the moment it cut across his soul force, he felt as if he had thoroughly died. This was because the blade contained the Concept of Death!

This Concept of Death had stayed here for 10 billion years without vanishing. When the Concept of Death entered his body just now, Lin Ming felt as if he had experienced a period of death.

If one’s soul wasn’t powerful enough and attempted what Lin Ming just tried, their soul would have been cut in half by that scythe. With the destruction of the soul, the body would also die!

In other words, the master of the Holy Scripture’s scythe phantom from 10 billion years ago was still able to pass through the endlessly glorious river of time and kill people!

Just what sort of terrifying might was that?

Lin Ming took a deep breath and stood up. He looked towards Ruby. Ruby’s small face was still ashen and she covered her wide mouth with her hands.

“I’m fine.” Lin Ming said. He couldn’t understand her. There were far too many secrets on this little girl’s body. She could easily see through everything but she also seemed to know nothing about the mysteries of the Laws.

“That person’s shadow, where is he again?”

Lin Ming asked. Ruby hesitated and pointed in another direction. Lin Ming rushed there once more.

Lin Ming experienced another moment of death. But, what was different was that this time, the mysterious black book formed an endless vortex that sank into Lin Ming’s heart.

In that instant, Lin Ming felt his heart decay and the flow of blood in his body come to a complete stop. His entire body froze, eventually become bones.

This feeling was like witnessing his death with his own eyes. Witnessing his corpse slowly rot over countless thousands of years until only a skeleton was left remaining.

These two experiences were both moments of death, but the feeling they gave Lin Ming were completely different.

“Now… where is that person’s shadow?”

Lin Ming asked Ruby to point out the direction once more.

Like this, Lin Ming determined the position of the shadow and ran over again and again. Every time he would experience a moment of death, but what he comprehended was different each time.

Slowly, the black energy between Lin Ming’s eyebrows became increasingly thick. He also consumed his soul force at an increasingly rapid rate.

At this time, changes began to manifest on Lin Ming’s body in the outside world. Dark clouds seemed to cover his face and a faint death energy exuded from his body. His strength rapidly passed away and he seemed on the verge of death. Eventually, even black blood began flowing out from the corners of Lin Ming’s lips.

Seeing this, the spiritas martial artists gathered around the shrine platforms were left speechless.

Last time when Lin Ming was lighting the fifth soul sea, he appeared to have overdrawn his soul force and had startled bleeding from his head, almost completely exhausted. But before long, he was bursting with energy once more. Moreover, after Sheng Mei lit the fifth soul sea, Lin Ming had lit his fifth soul sea right after and the phenomenon that followed his was far superior to Sheng Mei’s. Those people that were mocking Lin Ming all had their faces slapped and their reputations torn down.

And before that when Lin Ming first came to the Fallen God Mountain Range to attempt enlightenment, the result was that he had been locked down by the divine sense of a True Divinity and teams of martial artists took transmission arrays to catch up to this place and kill Lin Ming. Those people had been elites from Great Brahmic God Mountain, characters who had managed to become World Kings when they were a thousand years old and had high chances of becoming Empyreans in the future. These many proud children of heaven led an assault on Lin Ming, even posting a sky-high bounty reward so that the other young elites at the Fallen God Mountain Range would help strike down Lin Ming.

These young elites at the Fallen God Mountain Range had watched as Lin Ming fought until his entire body was bloodied and the situation had reached incredibly tragic levels. When Lin Ming seemed on the verge of defeat, these people had stepped into the fray, hoping to pick up some small advantages, but finally, they met horrible ends.

As the young elites present thought back to the scene of a year ago when swathes of people were being slaughtered, they felt a cold chill creep down their back!

Now, these young elites at the Fallen God Mountain Range watched on as Lin Ming’s complexion darkened, seeming as if he had been poisoned and would die soon. They glanced at each other, not sure what feeling was in their heart.

They felt that a freakish person like Lin Ming should really be punished by the heavens and struck down by a bolt of lightning. Every time when he seemed almost exhausted and his situation was dire, he would suddenly erupt with some ridiculous strength, frightening everyone that was watching him.

But, even as some people were left speechless, some still hadn’t given up. They said in a low voice, “This time, he really must be in trouble.”

There were too many martial artists surrounding the shrine platforms and there would always be those who didn’t believe in superstitious nonsense.

There were also some people that looked at Sheng Mei. They felt that her current situation was also poor. After all, when comprehending the Concept of Death it wasn’t easy for one to restore their soul force. Even someone like Sheng Mei had to suffer layers of problems as she tried to grasp the principles.

Sheng Mei’s enlightenment was vastly different from Lin Ming’s. But, she also faced endless death energy all around her. Even if Sheng Mei’s understandings of the Concept of Death had reached a nearly unimaginable level, she still found it hard to find a way out from this endless death energy in a short period of time.

In this environment where there was only death and no life, Sheng Mei’s soul force was similarly being slowly used up.

Chapter 1853 – Overtake

Time passed, day by day.

No matter how deep Lin Ming’s background was or how solid his foundation, his strength wasn’t endless. It was impossible for him to be cut down an infinite number of times by the shadow.

He didn’t just sit there and wait for moments of death and these scythes weren’t needlessly suffered. Every time Lin Ming experienced a moment of death, his understanding into the Concept of Death became increasingly profound. Slowly, Lin Ming could already absorb the spiritual energy in this land of death to slowly restore himself.

Although his rate of regeneration couldn’t catch up to his rate of consumption, the situation was much better than before.

A month passed. On this day, as the black book emitted black energy light that broke into Lin Ming’s body, the golden pages within Lin Ming’s body began to be drawn towards this black energy, quietly humming.

In that moment, the scene in front of Lin Ming flickered and he could see a dim shadow!

Lin Ming found himself short of breath. His heart was caught in that black light and started rapidly and tenaciously beating.

He saw it!

He had finally seen the shadow that grasped the Concept of Death!

Although it was only the briefest of glances, this still left a profoundly indelible mark on Lin Ming’s innermost feelings!

This person was the creator of the Holy Scripture that he had seen in the ancient battlefield ruins!

And the feeling this person gave off was one of infinite killing intent. Compared to the mysterious woman from before, they represented two polar extremes!

That mysterious woman seemed to be the mother of all existence, filled with an incomparably boundless vitality. But for this shadow in front of him, it was like there was a fathomless blood pond from hell within his body.

One represented life, one represented death, they were two extremes of existence!

As for the golden pages that trembled within Lin Ming’s body, they faintly resonated with the mysterious black book. The Concepts of Life and Death flowed within them.

Lin Ming had a faint understanding of what happened. Perhaps the legendary Spiritas Holy Scripture was in truth only this black book!

As he recalled the contents of the golden pages, he vaguely felt that the golden pages and black book were both true parts of the Holy Scripture. But, the golden pages were of life, and the black book was of death.

What the Soul Emperor controlled should be the complete and original book of death.

As for the pages of life, the Soul Emperor had copies.

In addition, he also had several of the golden pages.

In other words, the Soul Emperor nearly possessed the entire Holy Scripture!

Thinking of this, Lin Ming realized just how terrifying the Soul Emperor was. Many times, whether a race could be called the strongest race or a sect could be called the number one sect looked not at the population or number of masters, but the most powerful existence amongst them.

The greatest powerhouse often determined the level of an influence.

The reason the spiritas dared to call themselves a peak race of the universe was likely because of the Soul Emperor and the Holy Scripture.

Of course, the saints’ Good Fortune Saint Sovereign wasn’t weak either. This was because the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign possessed the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

Between the original copy of the Holy Scripture and the Grandmist Spirit Bead, Lin Ming found it hard to decide which divine object was a greater influence on a martial artist’s growth.

However, now was not the time to think of such things.

Lin Ming took advantage of his rapid progress in comprehending the Concept of Death and began to absorb the soul force in this land of death. At the same time, he continuously looked for the phantom of the Holy Scripture’s creator, withstanding his attacks and comprehending the mysteries of the Concept of Death in that brief moment.

Time and time again, Lin Ming experience moments of death.

Slowly, the restoration of his soul force had caught up to the rate at which he was consuming it.

Several more months passed. Lin Ming’s restorative rate began to grow larger than his rate of consumption. His physical strength, vitality, and energy started to quickly recover.

Between Lin Ming’s eyebrows, the daevic eye shined bright. Every movement of the shadow seemed to slow to a crawl, allowing Lin Ming to gain a better understanding of them.

He withstood the attacks of the shadow without end. Later, he even began to imitate the shadow, copying his movements and the changes in his aura.

The more Lin Ming tried to copy this shadow, the more he could feel just how terrifying this other person’s boundary was. Even though the actions seemed simple and plain, they actually contained endless mysteries.

Month after month, Lin Ming was lost in a drunken trance.

And in the outside world, the martial artists around the shrine platforms watched helplessly on. Indeed, this cockroach-like Lin Ming couldn’t be underestimated.

If anyone thought Lin Ming was good to bully just because he showed some signs of weakening, they would absolutely suffer a miserable fate.

But at the same time, Sheng Mei also restored herself.

Her talent was amazing. She didn’t have the red-dressed little girl following beside her and giving her pointers, but instead relied completely on her own intuition to find a path to the Concept of Death in the thick black fog. Her road in grasping the principles had been far more difficult than Lin Ming’s.

Like this, Sheng Mei and Lin Ming spent over two years on the shrine platforms.

News of Sheng Mei and Lin Ming’s competition and the fact that they had opened the fifth soul sea and were rushing towards the sixth had long since spread throughout the Akashic Dream Universe.

For these last two years, more and more martial artists rushed towards the Fallen God Mountain Range. Many of these people were outstanding elites of various great influences.

However, they only watched from a distance. In fact, the shrine platforms nearest to Sheng Mei and Lin Ming were empty.

An invisible soul force domain shrouded the two people, making it difficult for others to approach.

Time quietly passed.

Another year passed. Now, it had been three years!

When a martial artist reached the Holy Lord realm their cultivation speed would drastically slow down. To these long-lived martial artists, three years of life could be called a single round of meditation.

By now, whether it was Sheng Mei or Lin Ming, they had already completely adapted to using their soul force in this land of death. Now they could expend all their efforts on comprehending the Death Laws.

Seeing Lin Ming and Sheng Mei competing on par with each other, many people didn’t know what to feel.

Was this human really that heaven-defying?

Disregarding the essence gathering system, Lin Ming was able to roll over all other spiritas martial artists in comprehending the inheritance left behind by the ancient ancestor of the spiritas, even competing evenly with Sheng Mei!

“I believe that the Soul Empress will win.”

Jade Lifestone said with certainty. As Sheng Mei’s die-hard supporter, he secretly cheered her on.

By now, three years and six months had passed.

On this day, a shocking scene occurred.

On the shrine platform that Lin Ming was sitting on, a massive amount of world soul force gathered around him. Endless brilliance began to radiate outwards, shooting into the highest heavens, surging through the void and covering all space for a hundred miles. A glorious halo appeared with rosy clouds, followed by melodies of the Great Dao.

“What?”

“It… it has only been three and a half years… could it be…”

No one dared to believe what they saw, nor were they willing to. But reality was cruel and merciless. On the shrine platform that Lin Ming sat upon, situated within a sheer cliff, strange runes began to light up. Like burning flames, a shimmering divine light shined out, emanating true meanings of the Great Dao and causing the world around the Fallen God Mountain Range to resonate!

The sixth soul sea mark had been lit!

This scene was witnessed by the countless elites of the Soul World. At this moment, they felt as if something shattered in their hearts, making them feel nauseous.

The entire soul race… was compared to a single human.

This human came alone and only had a middle Holy Lord cultivation with a less than 200 year skeletal age. However, there was not a single spiritas able to compare with him!

Their pride as the number one race of the 33 Heavens had been crushed by a mere human!

Even Sheng Mei hadn’t been able to overtake him!

This was just the greatest joke of all!

Many people clenched their fists. Jade Lifestone bit his lips so hard that they turned deep purple.

“Soul Empress Sheng Mei will surely light the sixth soul sea mark soon. Soon…”

He prayed in his heart. This prayer was also the fervent hope of the countless spiritas martial artists present.

However, reality was indifferent to their pleas. Another two months passed and there was no stir from Sheng Mei’s side.

At this time, Sheng Mei pressed her eyebrows together, as if she had met some bottleneck in her enlightenment.

To grasp the principles atop the shrine platform was far too difficult. These were the Law inheritances left behind by the master of the Holy Scripture!

Lin Ming had the mysterious red-dressed little girl to point out the way. Whether it was the Concept of Life or the Concept of Death, she was able to immediately see through them. Although she didn’t understand the Laws, her words gave tremendous inspirations to Lin Ming.

But as for Sheng Mei, she suffered far more by relying on herself.

It was only when four months passed, making it a total of three years and 10 months, that Sheng Mei’s shrine platform lit up with a divine light.

For a time, innumerable bright clouds gushed into the skies, shooting into the heavens and catching the attention of all!

Chapter 1854 – Enlightenment For 10 Years

“The Soul Empress has finally lit up the sixth soul sea.”

Many people looked towards Sheng Mei. To light up the sixth soul sea in less than four years was already a heaven-defying achievement. Compared to the Great Brahmic God King in the past, she was faster by over a year.

But compared to Lin Ming, she was late by several months.

As everyone watched more carefully, they could faintly feel that although the glow of Sheng Mei’s divine light was similarly dazzling, it seemed to hold a faintly inferior momentum compared to Lin Ming’s.

In terms of comprehending the Concept of Death, Sheng Mei had been forced to take many detours. She also consumed far more soul force than Lin Ming did.

And what followed was the most critical moment.

Many people didn’t know what to feel. Once one lit up the seventh soul sea mark, that was considered as having obtained complete enlightenment and one could obtain the golden page buried within the Fallen God Mountain Range.

In truth, when one reached enlightenment of this level, obtaining the golden page became secondary. As long as one could completely grasp the principles they would be able to obtain a massive advantage and their understanding into the Life Laws would reach staggering heights. It would play a tremendous role in a martial artist’s future cultivation.

This sort of lucky chance left others seething with envy.

At this time, within the world of his mind, Lin Ming had already touched upon the threshold of the final soul sea mark.

This final space had no mysterious woman nor was there the peerless death god with his scythe and black book.

Rather, what lay here was a simple stone platform.

Lin Ming sat atop this stone platform, calmly lost in his arduous enlightenment.

The auras of life and death brimmed around the stone platform. Countless Law runes circled about.

Between Lin Ming’s eyebrows, the daevic eye emitted a dazzling sun-bright light. All the Law runes were caught in his divine sense, without a single one escaping his notice.

The final enlightenment was to fuse together the two great Laws of Life and Death.

The difficulty of this level would depend on a martial artist’s perception and whether or not their previous enlightenments were thorough.

If a martial artist just barely managed to grasp the Concept of Death before reaching this point and attempted the final fusion like this, it would be like drawing water without a source; it was naturally impossible to succeed.

For the last 10 billion years, all the young True Divinities had failed in attempting to reach the seventh soul sea mark. This wasn’t because their perception was lacking but because the sixth soul sea mark, the Concept of Death, had been far, far too difficult to understand. Even those young True Divinities had barely managed to comprehend it and had consumed far too much energy in the process.

But to Lin Ming this wasn’t a problem at all, because his comprehensions of the Concepts of Life and Death were extremely solid.

All he needed to do was fuse the two together.

This was an extremely long process. With Lin Ming’s comprehensive capabilities after opening the daevic eye, he gradually fused them together without resorting to any shortcuts.

Time slowly passed. Whether it was Sheng Mei or Lin Ming, both were lost in a trance.

And at this time, many young elites had journeyed to the Fallen God Mountain Range to witness these two peerless geniuses with their own eyes. They wanted to be present when this legendary historical miracle occurred.

Because the timespan was far too long, many young elites came and left, left and then returned. They watched Lin Ming and Sheng Mei try to reach enlightenment. Some people even came into contact with the soul force domain that Lin Ming and Sheng Mei emitted and were able to gain some minor benefits in understanding the Concepts of Life and Death.

Of course, the young spiritas elites that could accomplish this were all extremely talented individuals, people with astonishing perceptions.

“I wonder whether Lin Muk or Empress Sheng Mei will be able to thoroughly comprehend the mysteries of the Phantom God Spirit Cliff. For so many years, young True Divinities have meditated on these shrine platforms and eventually failed, and it’s always felt a bit too fantastical to me…”

Two peerless characters had appeared together, and what was most ridiculous was that one of them was a human. This left everyone scratching their heads in confusion.

“And these two people are both younger than the Great Brahmic God King was and their talent is far more terrifying. In the future they will definitely become True Divinities. For them to create a miracle here isn’t an impossibility. Perhaps the two of them might even surpass the ancient elites of 10 billion years ago.”

10 billion years in the past. That was the peak of the martial arts civilization. The kings and elites of that era were on average far more powerful than those of today.

As for the current martial arts civilization, the truth was that they had undergone a tremendous decline before slowly redeveloping. If an elite of the current era could surpass those of the ancient past, that was an amazing achievement.

“History cannot be changed so easily. There are many people who believed that the rules of the Fallen God Mountain Range’s Phantom God Spirit Cliff have slowly changed over time. That after 10 billion years, this place is no longer suitable for enlightenment. Moreover, the ones who said these things were supreme spiritas elders. I believe there should be some truth to their words.”

Every person had a different opinion.

Many people waited here. Some tried to attempt enlightenment, some tried to cultivate, and like this three years passed…

Many elites from Empyrean influences came to the Fallen God Mountain Range and even elites from True Divinity level influences. They all used recording crystals or photographic array discs to record the scene of Lin Ming and Sheng Mei attempting enlightenment, and then hurried back to report their information.

From all over, hundreds and thousands of large influences had gathered.

For a human with heaven-defying talent to suddenly appear in the Soul World, this naturally caught the attention of all these influences.

In addition, they were also concerned with Sheng Mei’s current condition now that she had completed her seventh revolution.

Another three years passed.

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei were like statues, completely motionless.

Up to this point, nearly 10 years had passed since they started grasping the principles atop the shrine platforms.

In the considerably long history of the spiritas, no one had ever managed to thoroughly comprehend the inheritances of the Fallen God Mountain Range. Because of this, no one knew how long Lin Ming and Sheng Mei would continue in this state.

Time passed. Spring and fall came and left, and the tenth year soon finished. Suddenly, a vast divine light fell from the void, scattering all the fog from the Fallen God Mountain Range. This divine light was like a holy blade that thrust into the skies above the Fallen God Mountain Range before eventually falling down onto the shrine platform where Lin Ming was.

Lin Ming, together with the shrine platform that was several thousands of feet high, was completely shrouded by that pure divine light.

For a time, crazy winds rose throughout the entire Fallen God Mountain Range. Soul force crazily converged, gathering into a massive vortex that swirled around Lin Ming.

Endless soul force revolved, forming a massive spiral-shaped arm that sucked up all the Law fragments around the Fallen God Mountain Range. The center of the vortex slowly fell down, forming a titanic funnel that dropped onto Lin Ming.

As everyone saw this they were incomparably shocked. They could faintly realize that Lin Ming’s enlightenment was reaching its final crescendo. In other words, he would really light the seventh soul sea mark soon.

Everyone stared blankly on as the runes on Lin Ming’s shrine platform shined. Light spread all over, lighting up the entire shrine platform like a rising sun.

The seventh soul mark had lit up.

Seeing this scene, even though the spiritas elites had steeled their minds for it, they were still left dumbfounded. They found it hard to come up with any words.

This was because they knew this was a moment where history was being rewritten. Lin Ming had created a history of his own.

And what they found the hardest to accept was that the one who created this history was actually a human. He had taken away the inheritance that no spiritas elite had managed to take through all these years.

This result left all the spiritas elites feeling frustrated.

As for supporters of Sheng Mei like Jade Lifestone and the others, they felt sick to their stomachs.

“This is…”

A spiritas elite suddenly pointed towards the skies. In that purple vortex, blue and black energies circulated, like a yin yang diagram.

These two energies twined together, mutually relying on and enhancing the other.

This scene continued for an incense stick of time. Slowly, these two energies dissipated, spreading out and becoming outlines of runes in the skies. These runes spread out far and wide into the horizon, each one containing the infinite charm of the Great Dao, making the heart race.

“These are runes condensed from the source Laws of the Concepts of Life and Death.”

The elites present included several World King level powerhouses. As they originated from large influences they had extraordinary experiences. When they saw these life and death runes form with their own eyes, their minds trembled.

As everyone heard a World King speak, they all turned to look at the spinning runes in the skies. Most of them were unable to ascertain the mysteries contained within the runes, but they could still clearly feel just how terrifying these runes were. This was because the aura of these runes was able to faintly affect their souls and blood energies, causing their entire beings to resonate with them!

These were the source Laws of Life and Death!

Many martial artists who came to the Fallen God Mountain Range might not be able to comprehend any profound principles, but they still knew that on the shrine platforms, the main focus was on the Laws of Life and Death.

When these two Laws joined together, they created existence itself.

Seeing these dancing runes in the air, these martial artists were left seething with jealousy. If they could just obtain a single rune and perceive it then the benefits to their cultivation could be imagined!

And as their eyes blazed with greed, they focused their vision on these Law runes in the wild hopes that they would be able to comprehend something. But suddenly, the vortex accelerated in speed before slowly settling down and converging on a single point.

Winds whipped up. With Lin Ming as the center, all of these Law runes swept into him, as if he were a whale drinking in water.

“Mm?”

“…This is - !!”

Everyone’s eyes widened. They watched helplessly as the hundreds and thousands of Law runes plunged into Lin Ming’s body, vanishing like snowflakes falling into water.

The highest truths of the Heavenly Dao had formed mystical runes that carved themselves into Lin Ming’s bones and blood.

Law fragments evolved into runes, burying themselves into his flesh.

“This… this…”

Many people felt their jaws drop down. They couldn’t come up with anything to say.

For many elites of large influences, their eyes were red with desire.

They would be more than satisfied with obtaining just a single one of these precious source runes. But what a pity, these wishes were nothing but a wild dream. All of them had been completely absorbed by Lin Ming!

Just what kind of lucky chance was this!? It left them jealous enough to vomit blood!

“I want one! Just a single one is fine!”

Some people whined and stomped their feet.

These life and death runes sealed themselves within Lin Ming, becoming a part of him. Even though he wasn’t able to perceive all of them now, as his cultivation increased he would slowly be able to master their mysteries with twice the results and half the effort. This was the lucky chance one obtained after thoroughly comprehending the principles atop the Fallen God Mountain Range. It was similar to when Lin Ming was baptized by the world Laws during his Ninefall.

Chapter 1856 – Win And Lose

Recalling the 12 years of grasping the principles, in particular opening the sixth soul sea mark, the difficulty of this trial left one dumbfounded. Even Sheng Mei had nearly fallen off the shrine platform, unable to continue.

If this had happened, Sheng Mei would no longer have been able to completely grasp the principles in a single attempt. It would inevitably have been a tremendous disappointment.

As all these thoughts raced through her mind, she looked towards Lin Ming. She saw that Lin Ming was still sitting on his shrine platform, not finished with his meditation.

Sheng Mei always believed that Lin Ming was strong, perhaps even stronger than she was at the same cultivation boundary, but in terms of understanding existence and the Laws of Existence, it was impossible for Lin Ming to compare with her.

In terms of grasping the principles atop the shrine platform, Sheng Mei had absolute confidence she could suppress Lin Ming.

Thus, when Lin Ming proposed conditions in forming an alliance with the humans and spiritas, that was the reason why her response had been so cold; because she didn’t believe that Lin Ming would be able to fulfill his conditions.

Now that she saw Lin Ming immersed in his meditation still, she wasn’t surprised at all. However, she didn’t feel any deep sense of achievement either, because in terms of the Existence Laws, it would be natural for her to win against Lin Ming.

But after several breaths of time passed, her expression froze.

Something was wrong!

She looked at the shrine platform Lin Ming sat upon and could see the seven soul sea marks shining brightly. Moreover, that final seventh soul sea mark was like a dazzling sun, illuminating the world.

“This is…”

Sheng Mei was startled. How could this be!?

Lin Ming had finished a step ahead of her and had thoroughly comprehended the Laws atop the shrine platform. And now, he had likely already obtained the golden page and was perceiving it as well as the life and death runes that had fused into his body. She had no idea just how long he had been in this state!

As for Sheng Mei, she had just lit up the seventh soul sea mark. That was equivalent to being utterly defeated by Lin Ming even with a home field advantage!

“This is…”

Although Sheng Mei was normally indifferent and blasé, the truth was that she had always possessed a proud heart. In the Asura Road’s final trial when she faced the Undying Polar Ice, it was Lin Ming who had performed the final strike. But in that battle, Sheng Mei had played an offensive and defensive role, and her performance went far beyond Lin Ming’s.

Thus, Sheng Mei hadn’t lost in the Asura Road.

But now, atop the Fallen God Mountain Range’s shrine platforms which should have been her specialty, the domain which she excelled in, she had actually lost.

She felt this was simply unbelievable.

She didn’t underestimate herself nor did she not accept the facts laid out before her. She just found it hard to believe…

“No wonder I didn’t obtain a golden page after completely grasping the principles here!”

Sheng Mei suddenly realized what happened. The golden page had been taken by Lin Ming first!

She took a deep breath and looked towards Jade Lifestone. She knew that Jade Lifestone was a disciple of her Soul Rapture Holy Lands.

“He… when did he light the seventh soul sea mark? How much earlier was he?”

Sheng Mei’s sound transmission startled Jade Lifestone. Of all people, Sheng Mei had sent him a sound transmission!

Although he was a disciple of the Soul Rapture Holy Lands, he had never exchanged words with Sheng Mei before. He had only seen her profile from a far off distance.

But now, Sheng Mei actually sent him a sound transmission. Although it was because of Lin Muk, this was more than enough to leave him bubbling with excitement.

It was just that Sheng Mei’s question left him a little depressed after the initial excitement wore off.

Sheng Mei had lost. In his opinion, she was an omnipotent existence, a talent that was unprecedented since ancient times even through the entire 33 Heavens. Even so, she had lost to a human.

“R-reporting to the Soul Empress… Lin Muk used ten years… he was earlier than the Empress by… two years.”

Because of his happiness, Jade Lifestone’s voice trembled.

“Two years…”

Sheng Mei’s pupils shrank. She was fully aware of just how difficult grasping the principles atop the shrine platform was. She thought she had reached the peak of possibilities in terms of speed, but she had been two years behind Lin Ming!

How had he accomplished this?

As she recalled the Concept of Death from the sixth soul sea mark as well as needing to fuse the Concepts of Life and Death together for the seventh soul sea mark, Sheng Mei was at a loss to explain just how Lin Ming had done this in a short ten years of time.

“How terrifying…”

This was the first time that Sheng Mei had felt such terror from Lin Ming. Besides the Soul Emperor, there had never been anyone who had given her such a feeling! And the reason she felt such a feeling from the Soul Emperor was because his strength was truly horrifying. When the Soul Emperor was young, the truth was that his achievements were similar to those of the Great Brahmic God King. It was only when he became an Empyrean that he soared into the heavens, and one of the chief reasons behind this was naturally the Spiritas Holy Scripture.

As for Lin Ming, his raw talent was frightening. It left anyone lost in his dust!

After composing herself, Sheng Mei sighed. Then, she sat down and began meditating on the shrine platform.

Faintly, a strange feeling appeared in her heart. She looked in Lin Ming’s direction, and the place she looked at was behind him.

“Mm?”

Sheng Mei lightly said, her eyebrows pressing together.

In that brief moment she had felt a faint life form behind Lin Ming, an incomparably pure power of soul force that was even purer than her own.

“Ah…”

Ruby was startled. She quickly hid in Lin Ming’s spiritual sea.

This was the first time that she had encountered someone able to sense her. When she saw Sheng Mei successfully grasp the principles, she had been filled with curiosity and had come out to take a look. But, she didn’t expect that she would be noticed by Sheng Mei.

Her keen divine sense far surpassed that of an Empyrean.

“An illusion…?” Sheng Mei slightly frowned. She didn’t believe there was a problem with her divine sense, so she attributed what she experienced just now to something on Lin Ming’s body.

She didn’t know that the reason she lost to Lin Ming wasn’t because her perception was inferior, but because of that incomparably pure soul force she had just felt.

Lin Ming had that mysterious little girl aiding him, but Sheng Mei had depended on herself alone.

If the two of them had fairly competed, the results would have been completely different.

Of course, no matter what the reason was, Lin Ming running into that red-dressed little girl could be called his lucky chance and Sheng Mei was defeated all the same.

At this time, many people felt pity for Sheng Mei.

They sighed deeply over the injustice of Sheng Mei losing. She should have been able to obtain the golden page and become a legend, but she was late by just a single step and had been suppressed by Lin Ming.

For at least 2-3 billion years, there had never been anyone who managed to take a golden page from the Fallen God Mountain Range. But now, because of a mere two years’ difference, Sheng Mei had missed out. How could everyone not feel regret for her?

“If Empress Sheng Mei completed the eighth revolution she would have definitely defeated Lin Muk.”

Sheng Mei’s fans secretly discussed, still not convinced of the results.

Sheng Mei naturally heard these discussions. She shook her head. By the time she had completed the eighth revolution, perhaps, Lin Ming’s achievements would have risen once more…

After realizing she lost, there was nothing Sheng Mei couldn’t accept. She sat in meditation, waiting for Lin Ming to comprehend that golden page.

Now, she had a great interest in the road that lay before Lin Ming. In humanity’s great calamity, just where would Lin Ming go?

Lin Ming’s comprehension of the golden page continued for another year.

A year later, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed open.

His eyes seemed to have infinite Laws circulating within them. The aura of life in his left eye, the aura of death in his right eye, the two auras connected together, bringing about the charm of the Great Dao.

After perceiving a third golden page, Lin Ming’s understandings into the universe of the body had reached new heights.

Moreover, the hidden dangers that existed within him because of his cultivation increasing too quickly were completely eliminated during these 13 years.

For these 13 years, Lin Ming had only comprehended the Laws and didn’t cultivate at all. Otherwise, breaking into the late Holy Lord realm wouldn’t have been difficult at all.

“If I have enough time, if I can see the complete Holy Scripture and then obtain the third emperor jade and the complete Asura Sutra, perhaps I will be able to fuse the inner and outer universes and reach unprecedented heights of martial arts…”

As these thoughts flashed through Lin Ming’s mind, his heart suddenly skipped a beat. In front of him, someone had locked their gaze onto him.

Lin Ming looked forwards and two pairs of eyes met, colliding in midair. Lin Ming saw the otherworldly Sheng Mei.

For this year she didn’t take even half a step off the shrine platform. She simply waited there, perceiving the Law runes that had integrated into her flesh and blood.

“How did you accomplish this?”

Sheng Mei asked, going straight to the point.

“Luck.”

Lin Ming didn’t lie nor did he clearly state the truth. Him finding the red-dressed little girl was indeed a stroke of luck.

“Very well.”

Sheng Mei shook her head. She waved her slender white hands and two golden pages flew out from her soul sea, fluttering like silk into Lin Ming’s hands.

“According to our previous agreement, these are for you. After perceiving all of them, return the four golden pages back to me. Afterwards you can take away two. However, I advise you not to have any wild dreams of saving humanity. The great war of the saints might be closer than you think...”

As Sheng Mei spoke these words, she floated upwards. All that was left over were four golden pages floating in Lin Ming’s hands. The soft pages were like silk to the touch, incomparably real…

Chapter 1857 – Samsara of Life and Death

Lin Ming left. He had obtained far too many comprehensions at the Fallen God Mountain Range and needed time to digest and fuse them.

During the 13 years, the True Divinity mark placed within him had slowly faded away. And with Sheng Mei’s appearance, few people were willing to target him in an obvious manner.

But Lin Ming was still careful. After leaving the Fallen God Mountain range had once more used the Bodily Rebirth Technique and created a new identity for himself before re-entering the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

After grasping the principles atop the Fallen God Mountain Range for so long, the Akashic Dream Battlefield had long since opened again.

But this time, Lin Ming didn’t come to the Akashic Dream Battlefield to kill others for their merit points. Rather, he went to the ancient galactic battlefield to cultivate.

Lin Ming didn’t alert anyone. He easily arrived at the ancient forest within the Akashic Dream Battlefield, bypassing the layers of spells to enter the ancient ruins.

This was where the Asura Road Master and the creator of the Holy Scripture had fought 10 billion years ago.

The reason he chose to come here was because this was a land where the auras of the Asura Road Master and Holy Scripture creator had fused together.

Lin Ming held great ambitions. He wanted to cultivate essence, energy, and soul, simultaneously fusing together the universe of the body with the universe of the world, creating a road of martial arts that had never been seen before!

Thus, this ancient galactic battlefield was the best training place for him.

The four golden pages had fused into his flesh and blood and divine soul. At this time, Lin Ming was like an elderly abbot, his thoughts clear and serene.

In his mind, only the vast texts of the golden pages as well as those vague runes of existence fused into his body appeared.

This time, he wanted to comprehend the true meaning of the runes of existence and blend them together with the four golden pages.

The ancient galactic battlefield was pitch black and filled with a deathly silence. Lin Ming wandered through the ruins of this galaxy, stepping over countless shattered stars and planets as he went towards the most central point.

In the area where the first ancestor of the spiritas had left the strongest spirit mark, Lin Ming found a broken star nucleus and sat down within it.

Not too far away, Ruby had manifested and was following him.

As Ruby appeared, the surrounding strange black runes were stirred up by her. They were like fish that saw food, swimming towards her before sinking into her body.

Lin Ming sighed upon seeing this. Ruby was like an inherent being born of the Laws. Not only could she see through all Laws but Law runes would chase after her on their own initiative. He really couldn’t imagine what her origins were.

Lin Ming quickly entered the fused martial intent state. Behind him, the Bodhi tree slowly spread out, its lush leaves shining as he started to perceive the runes of life and death.

Soon, Lin Ming immersed himself into a completely convoluted realm, becoming one with the icy darkness around him.

In his mind, the ancient texts recorded atop the golden pages thundered loudly. The endless writings floated up and down like mountains, containing limitless mysteries.

After thoroughly grasping the principles atop the shrine platform, it was far easier for Lin Ming to read these golden pages now. He didn’t feel the agonizing pain of needles stabbing his eyes nor was he in a situation where he couldn’t read the words. This was because he had already immersed himself in them and was able to extricate them.

The golden pages were things passed down from the infinite past, the essence of the legacy of someone who had been able to create their own universe. Wanting to completely master them in a short period of time was impossible.

Every time Lin Ming comprehended the golden pages he would only comprehend a small part of them. Much of their contents still slumbered deeply within him, shrouded in a thick fog, obscured and unclear.

The reason he came here now was to shorten the time it would take him to slowly digest these accumulations.

A ghostly light began shining out from between his eyebrows, as if an eye were opening.

This was a mystical light, one that seemed as if it could illuminate the past, present, and future. It shined upon the fighting runes left behind by the Asura Road Master and the spiritas ancestor, making them also release a bright luster.

This strange eye was the Daevic Eye Dao Palace that Lin Ming had recently opened.

As the Daevic Eye Dao Palace appeared, it seemed to illuminate the universe in all directions, clearing away the fog and uncertainty.

Many of the blurry texts of the golden pages that were shrouded by fog within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea began to shine as the endless light of the Daevic Eye Dao Palace warmed them. The texts began to become increasingly loud, and a large portion of the thick fog surrounding  them dissipated, as if a sun was breaking through the endless morning horizon.

Every word was like an ancient god king, whispering as they spoke of infinite true meanings.

Lin Ming didn’t understand these sounds of the Great Dao at the start. But gradually, his body and divine sea were impacted by the sounds of the Great Dao.

Some texts began to pervade his nearly indestructible body. On his skin that was as tough as stars, tiny characters appeared like tadpoles swimming in water, followed with innumerable images.

…Some supreme elders were soaking up stars in the center of the universe, turning into ancient suns that lit up the endless expanse…

…A god king used his flesh and blood to build up a world. His energy turned into rain that nourished all life…

More and more true meanings appeared that enlightened Lin Ming’s divine soul. The endless information was like raging rivers as it rushed into him.

As time passed, his understandings of the golden pages became increasingly profound.

The surrounding world, as well as the battle runes left behind in the ancient galactic battlefield by the ancestor of the spiritas, began to flicker once more after so many years of silence as they started to shine with a marvelous harmony.

These runes were faint traces of black energy, incomparably nimble and inspiring.

Every wisp of black energy contained a distant scene of the old spiritas ancestor. Every scene depicted a true meaning of the old spiritas ancestor displaying the Holy Scripture…

Black energy swirled around Lin Ming. The endless runes of the golden pages rumbled in response. Even the old battle runes left behind by the old spiritas ancestor were dyed in shining gold.

Lin Ming immersed himself within all of this, lost in waves of enlightenment that he couldn’t take himself out of.

…Universe… space and time… life and death…

Gradually, the ancient texts immersed in his skin began to glow. Then, his flesh and blood, bones, and even his divine soul began to roar out together.

As this thunderous sound spread out, he fell into a trance and went utterly still.

First his heart stopped and his blood flow came to a standstill. A single breath extended for such a long time that it seemed to completely vanish.

He sat solitarily in that icy dark ancient galactic battlefield. Within the void, he seemed to melt into the shattered star nucleus where he was.

An unknown period of time passed. His skin and flesh started to dry up, and rings began to appear around his bones like mysterious marks.

He remained motionless as before, even with his vitality seemingly cut off. If another martial artist were to see him in such a state they would definitely be surprised, because his current appearance resembled that of true death.

After another period of time, Lin Ming’s skin began to flake away, turning into dust that scattered into the world. However, from beneath this old skin, baby-like crystalline skin started to appear, filled with vitality, like the new spring after winter.

As time passed, Lin Ming’s blood vitality became increasingly vibrant. His body was like the most perfect heavenly material, sparkling with a brilliant light. His fires of life were a raging conflagration, filled with a potent strength. Every breath he took seemed to cause the essence energy of the world to tumble about, and if this essence energy were collected it could be refined into precious miracle medicines.

During the process of enlightenment, the runes of existence within his body had further fused with him, allowing him to experience a transformation of life and death.

First, the vitality of his mortal body was severed, and as he lay on the verge of death, new life emerged!

Lin Ming opened his eyes. In the endlessly dark galaxy, his two eyes seemed to radiate like twin stars.

His back flew upwards and his entire body was naked. However, he still sighed with emotion as he shook his head.

“What a pity, I only have the runes of life and death and the four golden pages. I don’t have the complete Holy Scripture nor the black book… the golden pages represent the Life of the Holy Scripture and the black book represents Death. Without having seen the book of death, it's impossible for me to comprehend death to the extreme!

After grasping the principles this time, Lin Ming’s understanding towards the meaning of life and death contained within the Holy Scripture had reached new heights.

If he could fuse together with the black book and become fully aware of the Concept of Death, then it wouldn’t be so simple as shedding off his old skin. Rather, he could allow his body to decay, his flesh and bones to completely collapse.

That was true death.

And when death reached the extreme, he could use the golden pages of life to undergo rebirth after death. He would glow with the strongest vitality and remold his mortal body to obtain new life.

This was the same as being reborn. In other words, reincarnation. Even his skeletal age would change; this was truly changing the rules of the heavens and earth.

This was the origin of the Grand Reincarnation Art that Sheng Mei cultivated.

After undergoing a cycle of death and rebirth, that was the same as being reincarnated through samsara once.

After that, if one could fuse together the Eternal Soul then they could cultivate the Law of Eternal Life and exist forever within the world.

That was the complete Holy Scripture.

“The black book… I’d really like to see it…”

Lin Ming thought with some regret. If he could cultivate both the black book and golden book, then every reincarnation would push his strength to new limits.

Unfortunately, he would never be able to obtain the black book. Even if he requested it from Sheng Mei, she wouldn’t be able to lend it to him. The key point here was that Sheng Mei also didn’t possess the black book, because the black book was in the hands of the Soul Emperor.

Perhaps this black book was the greatest lucky chance of the Soul Emperor’s life. How could the Soul Emperor politely pass off his life’s greatest lucky chance to others?

Out of everything Lin Ming possessed, only the value of the Magic Cube surpassed that of the black book. But wanting to trade away the Magic Cube was naturally impossible.

Helplessly shaking his head, Lin Ming waved his arm. Endless power of existence condensed on his body, forming a long light purple robe.

He called out for Ruby who hid herself in his body. Then, they left the galactic battlefield.

He thought that a long period of time had passed since his enlightenment. Perhaps the Akashic Dream Battlefield had opened and closed several times already.

Lin Ming left the ancient battlefield and also left the forest. He wanted to find someone to ask when the Akashic Dream Battlefield’s entrance would open.

At this time, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred and he froze where he was. Not too far away, he could see a lake. This lake was beautiful like liquid jade, and what was strange was that there wasn’t even the smallest wave. It could be called extremely peaceful, or even still to the point of death.

Around the lake, there was no grass, only a gray rocky shore. Someone was sitting on an embankment, a rod in his hands as he fished from the lake.

From afar, this person was a youth.

Lin Ming looked at this youth’s back, staring for a long time. He didn’t know why, but he could feel a strange aura from the youth’s back.

Chapter 1858 – The Old Youth

This youth didn’t have the aura of Laws around his body and his foundation was ordinary. His cultivation wasn’t high, but as he sat there fishing, he seemed to meld together with the surrounding environment in perfect harmony.

Lin Ming hesitated for a moment and then walked towards the youth.

The youth clearly sensed Lin Ming approach. However, he continued fishing as before, sitting on the side of this lake which was like a well that had never been touched.

“Are there fish here?”

Lin Ming suddenly asked. His understanding towards the Laws of Existence had reached an extremely high boundary and he could feel that this lake lacked any vitality at all. There was no life within it, and there weren’t even plants in the water or shrimp or fish within. It was just impossible to fish for anything here.

“There aren’t.”

The youth’s voice was a little dreary, without any emotion at all.

As the youth spoke, he didn’t turn his head. Lin Ming could see the youth’s hands that were grasping the fishing pole. His hands were as beautiful as a woman’s, his ten fingers were slender and his nails seemed made of crystal. As he held the fishing pole he seemed as stable as a sculpture.

On his right thumb, there was a simple jade ring. This ring had Law runes carved within it, seeming mysterious yet exceedingly simple.

“If there aren’t any fish, what are you fishing for?”

Lin Ming asked, puzzled. He could confirm that this youth wasn’t ordinary at all. This was a thought purely based on his intuition.

“Fishing for a Concept.”

The same dreary voice said. Listening to the youth made one feel strange.

“The Concept of Death?”

Lin Ming asked in return. In this lake that had no vitality at all, what it possessed the most was the Concept of Death. If one tried to comprehend the Concept of Death here, that was actually possible.

But, there was only a possibility. Compared to the shrine platforms of the Fallen God Mountain Range, the difference in the Concept of Death present there and here couldn’t even be described as the heavens and earth. The Concept of Death here was just far too shallow.

The youth in front of him had a mysterious identity and was clearly no ordinary mortal. Yet, he was still fishing here for a Concept. This left Lin Ming confused.

What could be perceived here? This was only a dead lake.

But Lin Ming didn’t rashly respond. He carefully felt the surrounding Laws and determined that there wasn’t anything strange about them. The location of this area was ordinary, near the outer boundaries of the forest, and the soul beasts nearby weren’t powerful either. At the bottom of the lake there were some corpses of dead animals, but most had been dead for hundreds of thousands of years and had turned into fragile fossils. Those animals had also been ordinary creatures when they were still alive.

Combining all of these factors together, this was still only an extremely ordinary dead lake.

Although Lin Ming had already determined the specifics of the lake, he didn’t randomly draw a conclusion. He just asked in response, “Is there something special about this lake?”

The youth shook his head, “There isn’t anything special; it’s quite ordinary.”

Then, the youth laid down the fishing pole and turned around.

Seeing this youth’s face, a look of amazement flashed in Lin Ming’s eyes.

The youth’s eyes were glazed and incomparably dirty. Only an old man on the verge of death would have such eyes.

Although the youth had fair and crystal-bright skin, Lin Ming could feel the endless years exuding from his body, as if he had walked here from the beginning of time.

As if… hidden within this youth, there was an unbelievably old soul.

“You are…”

Lin Ming subconsciously stepped backwards, maintaining absolute guard of his surroundings.

He felt that it wasn’t an accident that he ran into this old youth here.

But, he had no idea just who this old youth was.

The youth looked towards Lin Ming and didn’t respond to his surprise. Rather, he began to say, “Your sense of purpose is too strong. Things that are valuable to you, you will pursue. But things that are worthless, you will give up. For instance, this lake. If you had passed by this lake I’m afraid you wouldn’t even have spared it a single glance…”

Lin Ming fell silent. This was how things should be. It wasn’t just him, but every normal person in the world was basically the same.

Even for those eminent monks of Mount Potala that had obtained enlightenment, even though they stood aloof from the world and didn’t pursue any desires or emotions, that journey in itself could be called a pursuit.

The youth looked at Lin Ming. Although Lin Ming’s image didn’t even reflect in his dirty eyes, Lin Ming still felt as if he had been completely seen through.

Lin Ming held his breath, completely restraining his mind and raising his guard to the limit.

“Senior, who are you?”

Lin Ming changed his greeting. The youth only looked at Lin Ming and shook his head.

“Your life could be called breaking through all obstacles in your way, moving forwards with unstoppable momentum. You desperately rush towards the peak of martial arts and you far surpass all others of your generation. From the time you bloomed, you took few detours.

“But to gain this you also lost something. The road of martial arts is more than the most mysterious and the greatest of the Heavenly Dao Laws. There are also ordinary, everyday experiences. You are missing a section of your path…”

“Such as this lake?” Lin Ming quietly asked. He could feel that this old youth’s words contained some of the highest truths. But, he wasn’t able to immediately comprehend them all.

The so-called ordinary things, just what were they?

The youth gently smiled, not directly replying, “Your road might be called too smooth. In the past you might have experienced some setbacks, but those are far from enough. You are invincible amongst your peers. In battle you sing nothing but victory and have defeated countless rivals. It could even be said that you have never experienced true defeat. But, that might become your limitation, making it impossibly difficult for you to step onto the peak of martial arts!”

The youth’s words were like a bolt of lightning that lashed through Lin Ming’s mind.

Never experienced true defeat?

In Green Mulberry City, he had lost in emotions to Zhu Yan and had lost Lan Yunyue.

At Divine Phoenix Island he was forced to flee by Xuan Wuji and become a fugitive at the Holy Demon Continent.

Afterwards, when he visited the four Divine Kingdoms he had been plotted against by Yang Yun and nearly had his body wrested away by the Ancient Devil.

And when he reached the Divine Realm, he had fought with Tian Mingzi twice, knocking on death’s door both times.

And from the youth’s words, these weren’t true defeats, but only minor setbacks.

“For one whose road of martial arts is too smooth, for one who isn’t forced to take detours, for one who sings nothing but hymns of victory, it is instead easy to fall into a bottleneck, making one forever unable to step onto the peak of martial arts.”

Lin Ming realized what this youth was saying and didn’t continue trying to find out who he was.

He knew that if this other person intended to reveal his status, he would naturally know.

And at this time, the youth had already stood up.

He lifted the fishing pole. The ring on his thumb emitted a phantasmal green light. As he looked at Lin Ming, a thoughtful and intriguing light shined in his eyes.

Lin Ming and the youth looked at each other. This other person’s dirty eyes left a profound impression upon him.

“Were you especially waiting for me here?”

Lin Ming’s thoughts chilled. To come face to face with someone of unknown origins whose strength far surpassed his own, he naturally felt uneasy about it.

But the youth only gently smiled and disappeared without another word.

He stepped onto the lake and vanished into the fog.

Lin Ming took a deep breath. This mysterious old youth filled him with a deep sense of dread and apprehension.

“Brother Lin, that person is… terrifying…”

After the old youth left, Lin Ming heard a timid voice echo in his mind; it was Ruby.

“What did you see?” Lin Ming asked. Perhaps Ruby had seen things he could not.

“I don’t know… I didn’t even dare to look at him. I hid away and was too scared to breathe, because he might have discovered me…”

Ruby said, trying to gather her scattered wits.

“Mm… I understand. Don’t show up so frequently in the future…”

Ruby’s words left Lin Ming with some faint guesses.

He quickly asked a trial challenger in the Akashic Dream Battlefield and confirmed when the Akashic Dream Battlefield would be opening once more. He also discovered he had been here in seclusion for a full 16 years.

In other words, adding in the time he was on the shrine platform grasping the principles as well as the three years he spent in the Akashic Dream Battlefield, he had been at the Akashic Dream Universe for 32 years already.

To Lin Ming and other martial artists that lived long lives, 32 years was only a brief flicker of time. But, this was actually almost half the time until the great calamity of humanity would descend.

War could erupt at any moment.

Lin Ming left the Akashic Dream Battlefield and re-entered the Fallen God Mountain Range. This was the meeting area he had arranged with Sheng Mei. As long as he returned here, Sheng Mei would obtain news of it.

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei’s meeting was so that he could return the golden pages to her.

“You saw him?”

Sheng Mei arrived in the deep of night, appearing right behind Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s eyebrows arched up. He turned to look at her.

At this time, Sheng Mei was wearing long robes of deep dark red, her eyes seeming to contain shattered stars. Against the backdrop of the night, she was like a umbral goddess, exuding a mystical and noble air.

The night wind gently blew. Sheng Mei’s cloak fluttered about her. The atmosphere was chilling. It was hard for Lin Ming to tell what she was thinking from her expression.

“Him? That mysterious youth?”

Sheng Mei’s question confirmed Lin Ming’s guess. But, this confirmation sent a chill crawling up his spine.

Sheng Mei’s silence was the same as nodding her head.

“I saw him…” Lin Ming took a deep breath. He looked at Sheng Mei, his complexion having changed. “That old youth… is the Soul Emperor?”

Chapter 1859 – Sheng Mei’s Sigh

Sheng Mei’s question implied that she knew who the mysterious youth was. But someone that Sheng Mei knew who was so incredibly powerful that Lin Ming couldn’t understand him at all, and who also made him feel fear and apprehension, Lin Ming couldn’t think of anyone else besides the Soul Emperor.

“Yes.”

Sheng Mei slowly nodded. She wasn’t surprised that Lin Ming could guess the identity of that youth.

The Soul Emperor was the one who held ultimate control of the spiritas and the seven Heavens of the spiritas. Although the spiritas had many True Divinities, these True Divinities took the Soul Emperor as their ruler.

Towards this immeasurably deep and mysterious character, Lin Ming was filled with dread.

“If he didn’t discover Ruby, he shouldn’t have discovered the Magic Cube…”

Lin Ming felt his back drenched in a cold sweat. When he met the mysterious youth, Lin Ming had tried his best to restrain his every thought and emotion. Even so, he felt as if he had been completely seen through.

Luckily, the Magic Cube was originally a supreme divine tool of the universe and Ruby was also an extremely mysterious character who could even see through the Laws left behind by the creator of the Holy Scripture.

These were two existences that surpassed the imagination of others. If they hid their aura as best they could, it was normal if even a True Divinity couldn’t discover them.

Moreover, according to what Lin Ming learned before, the Soul Emperor should never have seen the Magic Cube before.

“The Soul Emperor… why is he here to especially see me?”

Lin Ming thought, awed. Without a doubt, the Soul Emperor had been deliberately waiting for him on the banks of that dead lake!

The Soul Emperor had said that Lin Ming’s road was too smooth and not conducive to him reaching the true peak of martial arts. These words had left a deep impression in Lin Ming’s mind, but he didn’t believe that the Soul Emperor had been there just to leave behind these words and help guide his cultivation.

As Lin Ming spoke, his eyes blazed and he stared at Sheng Mei. He waited for her response; this was something that concerned his life!

The Soul Emperor was far too powerful. Although humanity had no conflicts of interest with the spiritas right now, and could even be called loosely connected part-allies, Lin Ming was still alarmed by being noticed by this figure who possessed unimaginable strength and could control his life or death at any moment.

Sheng Mei sighed, not replying.

Lin Ming continued to stare at Sheng Mei. “Why are you sighing?”

“I’m sighing over your destiny…”

Sheng Mei quietly said.

Lin Ming grew increasingly cold. “Why are you sighing for my destiny?”

Sheng Mei shook her head, not saying anything.

Lin Ming also fell silent.

After the two remained quiet for a quarter hour, Sheng Mei suddenly looked at Lin Ming, her eyes glistening like stars.

“Lin Ming, let me ask you one more time. Are you willing to abandon humanity, abandon everything, and follow me in reaching the peak of martial arts, probing the limits of the road of martial arts, establishing a vast world that lies separate from the 33 Heavens and becoming the rulers of that world?

“You and I can even become like the Asura Road Master and Holy Scripture master from 10 billion years ago. We can cultivate the Law of Eternal Life and live forever in this world.”

Sheng Mei’s words were filled with a dark temptation. Moreover, as she spoke, Lin Ming could feel an invisible force field covering the both of them, isolating out all sounds.

He didn’t know why, but the look that Sheng Mei cast his way caused his heart to race.

In that moment, he intuitively felt that Sheng Mei’s eyes were filled with sincerity and hope, causing one to be unable to refuse her…

In Lin Ming’s impression, Sheng Mei was a strong woman filled with ambition and calculating plans. Through the time he had been in contact with Sheng Mei, on the surface it looked as if they got alone happily and when they cooperated it even seemed as if their thoughts were in sync.

But in the depths of his heart, Lin Ming had always been wary of Sheng Mei. If Lin Ming held 120% trust towards Xiao Moxian, Qin Xingxuan, and Mu Qianyu, then towards Sheng Mei he might not even have 20% trust.

But this time, for some unknown reason, Lin Ming thought that Sheng Mei’s words were true, words that came from her heart. Lin Ming wanted to refuse her, but he couldn’t seem to summon the words even though they lay near his lips.

This was because he could faintly feel that Sheng Mei had summoned a great determination to say what she said, and this might be the last time she asked. And that if he were to refuse her now, he would be refusing something important.

“The Soul Emperor… how can he allow my existence?”

Lin Ming slowly asked beneath Sheng Mei’s sound-blocking enchantment.

Without a doubt, the Soul Emperor was also someone who held vast ambitions. If the Soul Emperor still had a long time left to live, how could he allow a competitor from a different race to grow?

Even if the Soul Emperor didn’t have much lifespan remaining, he still needed to choose a descendant, and he absolutely wouldn’t choose a human to inherit his legacy.

“Me and the Soul Emperor are different from what you imagine. I am only asking you – will you agree?”

Sheng Mei’s words were ambiguous. She didn’t explain anything to Lin Ming, only continuing to look at him with sincere hope in her eyes.

In that moment it seemed as if she wasn’t the Soul Empress Sheng Mei that dominated the spiritas and looked down at the world, but a delicate woman who aroused one’s deepest sympathies.

“I don’t understand…”

Lin Ming quietly said. Sheng Mei’s actions today left him startled.

Sheng Mei shook her head. “I only want to ask you this and know your answer. If you agree then I will explain the doubts you have in your heart, but if you refuse, I’m afraid that in the future, perhaps…”

Sheng Mei didn’t continue speaking. Her last words left Lin Ming feeling something strange in the pit of her stomach, as if saying them would hurt her.

Lin Ming knew that if he agreed to Sheng Mei’s conditions, it was possible that she would teach him the nearly complete Holy Scripture!

To Lin Ming, this was an unimaginable advantage!

“You can’t wait?”

Lin Ming already took a step back. The so-called ‘wait’ was to wait until he grew into an extreme Empyrean that neared a True Divinity, to wait for him to possess enough strength to contend with the saints’ Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and even turn the tide of the war.

At that time, once humanity was safe then he would have more choices he could make. He could wholeheartedly chase the peak of martial arts.

However… Sheng Mei shook her head.

“No.”

She refused without brooking any compromise, leaving Lin Ming stunned.

“Why?”

“I don’t have time.”

A nervous look flashed in Sheng Mei’s eyes.

Didn’t have time?

Lin Ming took a deep breath, trying to compose his racing heart. At that moment, in his mind, images of his parents, Xiao Moxian, Mu Qianyu, Qin Xingxuan, Lin Xiaoge, Empyrean Divine Dream, Empyrean Vast Universe, and even Empyrean Primordius who left him his legacy, flashed like a panorama. There was the Black Dragon of the Eternal Demon Abyss and the countless individuals of humanity who had crossed paths with him, aiding him, supporting him…

These were things he could not discard.

A human was never an independent existence. They needed human society, and also to be recognized by others.

Lin Ming couldn’t allow himself to become independent, desolately climbing towards the peak of martial arts all by himself.

To withstand an immortal life of loneliness.

That was an unimaginably despairing fate.

Eventually… he grit his teeth and shook his head.

“I refuse!”

Hearing Lin Ming’s deep voice, a look of disappointment crossed Sheng Mei’s face. She looked at Lin Ming and slowly closed her eyes. Beneath the starlight, her long lashes seemed to shiver.

The truth was she had already expected Lin Ming’s answer. Otherwise he wouldn’t be Lin Ming at all.

With a sigh, Sheng Mei turned around, looking at the boundless starry skies.

Her outstanding figure was outlined with her dark red dress. As it fluttered in the wind, she exuded an infinitely beguiling charm.

She was like a goddess of the heavens and earth, controlling creation, perfect and immovable. But at that moment, within her star-bright eyes, she also revealed endless loss.

Why did she ask again?

Perhaps… she just needed a reason to give up…

“Lin Ming… you are a moth drawn to the flame. Although you know there is a raging fire in front of you, you still desperately plunge into the roaring flames…

“Me, I am also a moth…”

Sheng Mei’s voice was like flowing starlight that cut through the night sky.

Lin Ming was silent. Indeed, he was a moth.

The saints were strong to an incomprehensible point. Perhaps, no matter how hard he tried, even if he exhausted the totality of his potential and burned his life, he still might not be able to stop the invasion of the saints.

But Sheng Mei… what were the flames she faced?

“Your words, sound familiar…”

Lin Ming sighed. He remembered when he was 15 years old and had just stepped onto the road of martial arts, he had lacked raw medicines to help cleanse and heal his body. And for a mortal, if they lacked the materials and medicines to nourish their body, they might overdraw themselves and be disabled for the rest of their life.

In the past he had gathered money to purchase these medicines. He had drawn up inscription symbols and went to various city squares, auction houses, and inscription association stores, but because he wasn’t famous, he had received nothing but a cold shoulder.

As a result, the scene of his failure had been witnessed by his first love, Lan Yunyue.

At that time, the advice Lan Yunyue gave him was similar to Sheng Mei’s…

“I remember… that when I was a mortal, an old friend of mine warned me not to be stubborn and practice martial arts. She didn’t want me to spend the rest of my days disabled on a bed. But, my answer was…

“The path of the martial artist is like a flame. Practicing the martial arts will only cause pain. The dangers are countless and the road is filled with obstacles. Everyone who walks down it will eventually turn to ash, but the true martial artist will be reborn from these ashes. Even if I am only a small and weak moth, I will walk into the flames without hesitation. I will fight my destiny for a one in a million chance that I will experience my own samsara and be reborn as a flaming phoenix. And even now, I am no longer a moth…”

As Lin Ming spoke these words, he didn’t know what he felt in his heart.

He knew that he was discarding an easy road to take, and choosing to walk down one filled with thorns and obstacles, and he didn’t even know whether or not he could reach the end of this road.

And when he chose to take this road, he seemed to have hurt Sheng Mei. Even so, Lin Ming didn’t know what difficulties Sheng Mei had that she couldn’t bring up…

“Forget the words I’ve said tonight.”

Sheng Mei suddenly calmed down. She turned around, the disappointment in her eyes already completely vanished, replaced with cold indifference.

It was as if what Lin Ming had seen and heard was just an illusion. As if that pitiful Sheng Mei had never existed at all.

She was the same as she had always been, the Empress of the spiritas, dominating the world, looking down upon all others!

“Lin Ming, a worm that lives amongst the dead leaves and fallen branches will never understand the beauty and greatness of this world. You have far too many chains shackling you down. The road of martial arts is to struggle for life with the heavens, and to climb to the peak of martial arts is to crush the heavens beneath your feet. Since ancient times, those that were willing to discard all others naturally possessed extreme talents of their own, and yet they were still defeated, much less someone like you who has chosen to place such a great weight upon yourself and shoulder the destiny of your race. Don’t you know the story of Empyrean Divine Seal from 3.6 billion years ago? He was a truly peerless character, a True Dragon of the world, but he also chose to shoulder the destiny of humanity and in the end he died in battle. What a pity, what a loss!”

Sheng Mei softly sighed. Lin Ming shook his head. “I am not Empyrean Divine Seal. My road is one I will walk down myself. And the choices I make, I will not regret them in the future!”

Chapter 1861 – Struggle

Sheng Mei sighed deep with emotion, as if she were also sighing over her own destiny.

Lin Ming didn’t know what Sheng Mei had to face that she wanted to flee it for a hundred million years, but what he knew was that Sheng Mei was someone with great ambitions.

Just like she had said –

A worm that lives amongst the dead leaves and fallen branches will never understand the beauty and greatness of this world!

And a worm was a creature that wouldn’t live past the winter. Because of its short life, it didn’t know the dangers of a world filled with ice and snow.

But what about martial artists? Wasn’t it the same?

10 billion years ago, those supreme elders might have seemed heaven-shaking and world-breaking, but were they able to see the world 10 billion years later? The current Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was also all-powerful, but would he be able to see the future of 10 billion years from now?

Sheng Mei was unwilling to live for a mere several hundred million years. She wanted to live longer than that, to witness everything the universe had to offer!

“Although the primal god race didn’t have any True Divinities they were still able to contend with the saints for so long. Is it by virtue of the so-called ‘decree of the gods’?”

Lin Ming found it difficult to believe that a single decree could threaten the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

“The so-called ‘decree of the gods’, do you even know what they are? Do you know how deep their origins are? They are items left behind by the many peerless god sovereigns of the ancient past. It is even said that within these decrees of the gods, there are those left behind by the Asura Road Master. Because of this, there is a viewpoint that exists which believes the Asura Road Master came from the primal god race!”

“What!?”

Lin Ming was dumbfounded. The Asura Road Master was from the primal god race?

“What else do you think is possible? He is a character that existed 10 billion years ago. 10 billion years ago, humans, saints, and spiritas, the three great peak races of the current era had yet to rise. There were only the numerous ancient races that aren’t worthy of mention now. It's impossible that any of these small races possessed the destiny or background to give birth to unrivalled existences like the Asura Road Master or the Holy Scripture creator. The spiritas may have declared to the world that the creator of the Holy Scripture is the first ancestor of the spiritas, but the reality is that this is only a justification for them to thoroughly inherit the Akashic Dream Universe.”

Sheng Mei ruthlessly mocked. Her words caused Lin Ming’s thoughts to stir, as if she were contemptuously scoffing at the actions taken by the high level figures of the spiritas.

“So that’s how it is…”

Lin Ming recalled the Asura Road Master triple cultivated essence, energy, and divine. He had 33 avatars and studied the 33 Heavenly Daos each to the boundary of a True Divinity.

This was an unimaginable achievement! For the three races of humans, saints, and spiritas, this was especially true.

But the primal god race was different. Their souls, bodies, and inner worlds were all incredibly potent, and they were strong by birth alone, possessing the talent to cultivate essence, energy, and divine.

This point just happened to agree with the Asura Road Master’s road of cultivation!

The truth was that the Asura Road Maser existed 10 billion years ago. Through such a long period of time, the martial arts civilization of the universe had suffered numerous calamities and history had been lost to the sands of time, everything becoming vague and unknown.

It was hard for martial artists of the modern era to trace back what race the Asura Road Master originated from. But without a doubt, the primal god race was the likeliest choice.

Similarly, the creator of the Holy Scripture probably had a terrifying background.

Sheng Mei seemed to have seen through Lin Ming’s thoughts. She sighed and said, “The great emperors and sages of the ancient past almost all possessed inborn divine bodies and variation bloodlines. Lin Ming, if you wish to become a god and cast your own emperor’s road, leaving behind an eternal legend, then the premise of all of that is… you can become a god…”

Sheng Mei’s voice was calm but Lin Ming knew that the ‘become a god’ she referred to was not as simple as reaching the True Divinity realm, but was to reach the extreme True Divinity realm or even surpass it!

To surpass True Divinity, wasn’t that easier said than done? Even if humanity were at peace and he possessed the entire legacy and resources of his race, he still might not be able to accomplish that!

Much less now, when humanity was experiencing a great calamity soon. Lin Ming would lose his backing and struggle in the endless surging waves. If he were just a little bit careless, his body and soul would be destroyed…

“Empress, I have a question… how many Heavens do the saints control?”

Lin Ming asked. He wanted a rough approximation of the saints’ strength; that would be greatly helpful to him.

“Seven, the same as my spiritas, although their overall strength is slightly inferior!” Sheng Mei said with certainty. In a sense, the Akashic Dream Universe, to a race, was far more useful than the Primeval Realm Ruins. After all, the army-style training of the Akashic Dream Battlefield was something that the Primeval Realm Ruins didn’t have.

“Seven… then, if the spiritas and saints each possess seven Heavens, the numerous ancient races possess one, and the Divine Realm is also one, then I only know of 16 Heavens… there are also the universes of 17 Heavens remaining. Are there other races?”

Lin Ming asked, feeling a bit depressed. In the past, humanity stood on par with the saints and spiritas, but now they only possessed a single Heaven.

Of course, there was still a large number of humans. Many of them were distributed across the various territories of the saints and spiritas, and could be called slaves.

Now humanity, which had once been one of the three great peak races, only had the advantage of numbers left for them.

Sheng Mei shook her head, “There aren’t that many races. Of the 33 Heavens, many of them are gaping deathtraps or wildernesses. Some of them have chaotic Laws, some of them have thin origin energy, and some of them are even filled with powerful vicious beasts – all of these problems are the ongoing consequences left behind by the great wars of the hundred races from ancient times. But… the truth is that this isn’t a problem. Chaotic Laws can be sorted and straightened out, thin origin energy can be nourished and revived, and vicious beasts can be slain, however… the key factor is that for these universes, the God Lamenting Wall that separates the Heavens hasn’t weakened much, even during the last cycle of samsara 3.6 billion years ago. Because of this, it is difficult for anyone besides a True Divinity to enter the other Heavens. Thus, whether it is the saints or spiritas, it is difficult for any influence to expand into them and this is the reason that they are currently isolated. However, in the future there will definitely be races that rely on their background to slowly expand throughout the entire 33 Heavens!”

“I understand…”

Lin Ming took a deep breath. It was clear that the martial arts civilization was at its most glorious 10 billion years ago. At that time, it was likely that all 33 Heavens were fully developed.

But afterwards, due to certain reasons, many ancient races declined and even went extinct. The martial arts civilization devolved into its early stages and had to be redeveloped from the start. Now, the masters of the current era were far inferior in quality and quantity to those of 10 billion years ago.

Perhaps as time passed, the spiritas would really be able to restore the martial arts civilization to the golden age of 10 billion years ago. But perhaps after that, they might also wither away.

To rise, to fade, and then to begin the cycle once more, that seemed to be a kind of Heavenly Dao rule.

Facing such a great rule, even peerless characters like the Asura Road Master and the creator of the Holy Scripture were unable to prevent it.

“How do I go to the universe where the primal god race is?” Lim Ming asked Sheng Mei. Since the spiritas were able to wage war with the saints and the saints were able to wage war with the ancient races, that meant the spiritas must possess a method to reach the ancient races.

“You really wish to go?” Sheng Mei looked at Lin Ming, her eyebrows pressing together. She originally wanted to tell Lin Ming that the time of humanity was nearing its end, but she never imagined he would want to go to the primal god race.

“Yes!”

Lin Ming didn’t aimlessly want to go to the primal god race. The primal god race might be related to the Asura Road Master, and based on this point alone he had to go take a look, and at least see what the decree of the gods that the Asura Road Master left behind were.

Sheng Mei stared at Lin Ming. She knew that once Lin Ming made a decision it was nearly impossible to change his mind. This was just the sort of person he was.

She shook her head, “I have no idea if you’re brave or a fool. If there is a day when you really must face doom, then it is always better to die under my hands than to die to the saints…”

As Sheng Mei spoke, she flew upwards. Her graceful form was covered in endless moonlight, as if she were stepping on the wind as she floated to the skies.

Like this, she left, not even turning her head once as she brought her previous confusion and her new decisiveness away with her.

Lin Ming watched Sheng Mei disappear into the horizon. He felt a sense of sudden melancholy that he couldn’t explain…

The next time they met, what would the situation be like?

The vicissitudes of life were ever-changing, being flipped and turned in the surging waves. In this great world, no one was able to do as they liked.

Lin Ming was a young eagle that had just learned to fly. Facing the upcoming storm, he was unable to reach the lofty skies. However, Sheng Mei was powerful and had completed her seventh revolution of reincarnation. Once she stepped into the Empyrean realm once more, her true combat strength might reach the boundaries of a True Divinity!

Even so, in her life she was burdened by a tremendous weight, one that left her lonely and lost.

As Sheng Mei had said, whether it was him or her, they were both moths flying towards the fire. Even though they both clearly knew there was a raging flame in front of them, they still desperately rushed into it.

Beneath the arrangement of fate, even if the initial moments were happy, the results might surpass all imagination. Even friends could turn into foes, opposing each other to life and death.

However, even knowing this, they would still follow the paths they had chosen and walk down their roads. This was because… they both held fast to their hearts and possessed their own beliefs!

If only life stayed like the first time we met. Suddenly, looking back through the rivers of time, nothing fills the eyes but mist.

I must struggle in the dust and chaos. Even if I am only a small wave, I will still bravely move forwards…

Flight of the Ancient Races

Chapter 1862 – Primeval Universe

“Brother Lin, are you leaving?” A shy voice sounded out. It was Ruby.

“Mm… I must leave. If I have the chance to return then I will definitely help you solve the riddle of your life.” Sheng Mei had long since left the vast forest. Lin Ming had been standing beneath the great starry skies for several hours.

He didn’t want to bring Ruby away. She was an energy body formed from pure soul force and if she left the Akashic Dream Universe she wouldn’t have a physical body. Although she would still exist, it would feel like a bird losing its wings. If she went to the catastrophic universe where the hundred ancient races dwelled, she might not be able to play a major role and would easily fall into danger.

Plus, with the uncertainty of Lin Ming’s own continued existence lying on the edge, he decided to leave by himself.

“Mm… then I… will wait for you to return.”

Ruby clenched her small fists and vigorously nodded. Towards Lin Ming, she felt a natural affinity. This was because of the Magic Cube and the Eternal Soul…

Over the years, Lin Ming’s soul had been nourished by the Magic Cube and had become extremely pure. It now possessed a trace of never-changing attributes.

This was also another reason why Lin Ming was special in Sheng Mei’s eyes.

Lin Ming deeply looked at Ruby. Then, he floated upwards and decisively turned away, welcoming the endless night winds as he quickly flew.

………

This was a desolate and bleak universe.

In this universe, the heaven and earth origin energy was particularly thin, only 60-70% that of the Divine Realm’s. But this universe was actually flooded with a boundless primal aura, as if it had existed for a trillion years.

There weren’t many stars in this universe. As for those that still hung in the skies, they seemed gloomy and dark, as if they were on the verge of being extinguished.

Lin Ming calmly sent out his divine sense and discovered that in the starry skies, there were many hidden black holes. Black holes were formed from the death of stars and were one of the most terrifying types of celestial bodies to exist in the universe. They were condensed from the overwhelming might of the Heavenly Dao Laws and even an Empyrean wouldn’t be able to come out if they entered.

“This universe seems to be fading…”

Lin Ming stood before the porthole of a spirit ship. He sighed. In the boundless universe, there was life as well as death. When a universe had existed for a long time, many stars would begin to die out one after another, becoming black holes. This was one of the signs of a universe moving towards entropy.

This process took an incomparably long time, perhaps even a hundred billion years.

“I never thought that the universe of the primal god race and other ancient races would be like this…”

Although Sheng Mei was almost hostile with Lin Ming, she had still arranged for people from the Soul Rapture Holy Lands to help Lin Ming enter the universe that the saints ruled over and subsequently enter this Primeval Universe.

This was a long journey. They had to pass through several God Lamenting Walls and the process lasted for over a year.

Wishing to make a trip that crossed several universes wasn’t easy at all. One had to use great void shifts countless times, consuming endless amounts of energy stones like nine sun jades. Even a Great World King would lose all their wealth in this attempt.

And at this time, Lin Ming discovered that in the starry space there was a giant floating temple.

This temple shimmered all over, dazzling to the eyes.

From this temple, Lin Ming could feel a familiar aura. That was astral essence, an energy as deep and vibrant as the sea!

The saints!

“Halt, identify yourself!”

Thousands of miles away from Lin Ming, a group of martial artists rapidly flew towards him, blocking his way.

These saint martial artists wore golden combat armor and held thick halberds and lances in their hands. They surrounded Lin Ming’s spirit ship.

“Come out!”

The leading saint martial artist shouted, his voice causing space to shake.

Lin Ming calmly flew out from the spirit ship. He had already used the Bodily Rebirth Technique to change his appearance and had even concealed his status as a human. Even an Empyrean wouldn’t be able to see through Lin Ming.

“Mm? Someone of our race. What influence are you from?” This aggressive squad of saints had a Holy Lord as their leader. It was naturally impossible for them to see through Lin Ming’s disguise.

“I am just a lonely wandering martial artist. I came to the Primeval Universe in order to fight and temper myself.”

In a war that involved two races, it wasn’t something that could be accomplished by several influences. Rather, all martial artists within the race could freely enter as they please to sharpen their skills in battle and also obtain valuable war loot.

For instance, the attack on the primal god race was coordinated by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. It involved over 150 Empyrean influences participating in addition to countless World King and Holy Lord level influences.

With all of these influences gathered together, the temporary army they formed was incomparably massive and chaotic.

Many saint martial artists could temporarily enter the army and become members of the army. They could take this opportunity to temper themselves, just like Lin Ming had said. Thus, it wasn’t sudden or a surprise for Lin Ming to appear here.

“Don’t move.”

The leading Holy Lord martial artist said. He took out an array disc and scanned Lin Ming, confirming his status once more. This was to prevent any spies from infiltrating their ranks.

However, it was impossible for such an ordinary array disc to penetrate through Lin Ming’s Bodily Rebirth Technique.

The array disc didn’t have any response. The Holy Lord sergeant nodded and tossed a token towards Lin Ming.

Lin Ming took this token and glanced at it. The writing on it said – ‘Sergeant Number: Holy Lord level 12,968. Subordinate under Empyrean White Heaven, First Mixed Legion.”

Seeing these words, Lin Ming was shocked. In a battle between races, the scale was truly astronomical. In a legion led by an Empyrean, there were over 12,000 Holy Lords.

In the past when humanity fought with the saints, Empyrean Divine Seal had led several hundred Empyreans and over a million Holy Lords in battle. This left a deep impression on Lin Ming.

In such a dreadful war, unless one’s individual strength reached that of a peak Empyrean or True Divinity, it was difficult to display much of an effect.

Lin Ming received the token and like this joined the saints’ army.

The reason he joined the saints’ army was mainly to uncover information. He had come to the Primeval Universe alone. In such a vast world he didn’t have a map or a guide and he didn’t know anything at all.

If he continued like this, he could wander around for a thousand years without finding the primal god race.

But if he joined one of the saints’ legions, that was different.

Like this, Lin Ming stayed in the saints’ army for several days, carrying out training exercises and combat practice.

Fighting in a legion was completely different from fighting one-on-one. In a situation with outstanding martial artists present, a short period of training could improve the overall combat strength of the team.

During this training period, Lin Ming deliberately stayed far away from the giant temple. This was because he could faintly feel a horrifying aura emitting from the temple. It was likely that this Empyrean White Sky was in command of the temple.

With Lin Ming’s current level of strength he didn’t want to come into any contact with an Empyrean. If he had to face an Empyrean he wouldn’t be able to run, much less escape.

During training, Lin Ming was able to learn a great deal of information from the conversations between the sergeants.

The situation in the Primeval Universe was more complex than Lin Ming had first imagined.

In the Primeval Universe, there were over 70 ancient remnant races. These remnant races were the descendants of the races that had been incredibly prosperous 10 billion years ago. Even though they fell into decline, they still possessed deep backgrounds.

It wasn’t just the primal god race that possessed the decree of the gods; the other races also had them.

The most powerful of them was the primal celestial race.

10 billion years ago, the primal celestial race was also swollen with pride and power, unexcelled in the world.

According to the rumors, it was said that in the past, of the 33 Heavens, the god race occupied 18 Heavens and the celestial race occupied 15 Heavens!

The two races had divided the 33 Heavens between themselves, unlike today where many universes existed in a semi-obsolete state.

During ancient times, the other races were in truth races that co-existed in the universes that the god race and celestial race had captured.

Now, since the saints wanted to annihilate the Primeval Universe, their main threats came from the god race and celestial race. If the peak Empyreans of these two races desperately burned away their own lives and also used the decrees of god left behind by the Asura Road Master, they could absolutely cause heavy losses even to a True Divinity!

These so-called heavy losses weren’t as simple as injuries. At the level of an Empyrean or True Divinity, their vital essence energy reached unimaginable heights and it was difficult for even rare heavenly treasures to make up for the losses they suffered. If a True Divinity were to suffer grievous wounds that caused damage to their vital essence energy, it would likely have a tremendous influence on their remaining strength and lifespan.

But although Lin Ming learned so much information, he still didn’t figure out how to find the primal god race. The primal god race had united several races together and had gone into hiding in a place called the Chaos Star Ocean.

This Chaos Star Ocean had once been the core of a titanic galaxy. But, the galaxy had withered away, and this core region was flooded with numerous space storms and black holes. If one recklessly rushed in and was sucked in by a black hole, that would mean certain death!

After understanding all of this, Lin Ming wasn’t surprised at all. The races of the primeval race were able to struggle with the saints for so many years with so few numbers, so they naturally must have something they could rely on.

If these ancient remnant clans fought on equal ground with the saints, the war situation would likely be completely different.

Lin Ming patiently waited for a chance to contact the primal god race. Two months passed, and on one day, a chance appeared before Lin Ming.

A squad of the primal god race had their whereabouts scouted out by the saints. And the group who discovered them was the legion that Lin Ming was a part of.

Lin Ming was suddenly shifted to the front lines. He accompanied a crowd of saint martial artists to surround this primal god squad. As for their orders, they were to capture them alive!

“Gather up!”

Before the legion set off, a sergeant shouted out loud.

“Hurry up and don’t dawdle around. Do you think this is your hometown? If you join the army that means you must follow the mindset of the army! Those who disobey orders will be executed!”

A World King loudly roared. He came from the White Sky Holy Lands and could be called part of the true army. As for this mixed legion that had people of all various levels of strength, he loudly reprimanded them and even attacked them at times.

This was the tradition of an army, completely different from that of a sect.

In this hastily formed mission, the saints had transferred over a hundred Holy Lords. The one leading them was a red-clothed man, a direct disciple of Empyrean White Sky. He had a Great World King realm cultivation.

And behind him also followed three ordinary World Kings, amongst them the one who had just shouted. There were also other direct disciples of Empyrean White Sky, but their status and talent were inferior to that of the red-clothed man.

“Is everyone here? I am the commander of this troop, Red Leaf. Now, set off!”

The red-clothed man dispensed with all the small talk. He brought the mixed legion and soared to the skies!

Chapter 1869 – The Old God Sovereign

“What? You want to enter my people’s forbidden land?”

Hearing Lin Ming’s statement, the Great Elder’s complexion darkened.

Since it was called a forbidden land it was naturally of vital importance to the god race. How could they allow a human to enter as they pleased?

Moreover, entering the forbidden land this time wasn’t for youths to temper themselves, but involved the life or death of their race.

“A limited number of people can enter the forbidden land. Since it concerns the life or death of my race, those that can enter are essentially Empyrean level characters of my people, the powerhouses of the older generation. They enter in order to seek a turning point to bring back our race from the edge of destruction, and it is not for youths to grow and gain experience. There may even be Empyreans of the celestial race joining, so there is no spot for you!”

The Great Elder didn’t want to waste a precious spot. His refusal was clear.

However, as Lin Ming heard these words all he heard were loopholes. “So you are saying that those who can enter the forbidden land are ‘essentially’ Empyrean level characters of your race?” Lin Ming emphasized the word ‘essentially’. He looked at Heaven’s Son Morin and said, “Since you say ‘essentially’, that must mean there are exceptions. Will Heaven’s Son Morin be entering also?”

Lin Ming’s words were needles that drew blood. Heaven’s Son Morin was part of the younger generation so what use could he play in the great calamity? It was clear that he was entering to gain experience.

Lin Ming’s words caused Heaven’s Son Morin to scowl. He angrily said, “Whether I enter or not is an internal matter of my god race, it isn’t something that an outsider like you can be pointing fingers at!”

Lin Ming sneered. “I may be an outsider, but this Chain of Calamity was passed to me by Heavenly Empress Xuanqing. It was I who inherited her request and I who brought this necklace here. If it wasn’t for me, you wouldn’t be able to open the forbidden land to begin with!”

As Lin Ming spoke, energy spontaneously surged from his body. As for the Chain of Calamity in his hands, it faintly echoed with Lin Ming’s energy and emitted waves of blue light. This blue light was similar to the light of endless years, bringing with it a simple and boundless feeling, as if this blue light had flowed from the beginning of time.

Seeing this, the god race martial artists present felt their pulses quicken. They didn’t know whether or not the Chain of Calamity had truly recognized Lin Ming as its master, but they could confirm that it was indeed absolute truth that this human youth had received the will of Heavenly Empress Xuanqing.

“If you really disregard this human and ignore the will of Heavenly Empress Xuanqing, it is hard to imagine what could happen. If an accident occurs when we repair the chain of calamity…”

A god race Elder sent a sound transmission. It had to be known that this Chain of Calamity was a True Divinity spirit treasure. In ordinary circumstances, repairing a True Divinity spirit treasure required a True Divinity to do so. But, their god race lacked True Divinities and thus they could only have several Empyreans join forces and even use a part of the strength from the decrees of the gods to repair the necklace.

“Old Three, your thoughts are overwrought!” The Great Elder shook his head, “The Heavenly Empress once attempted to use the Samsara Road to snatch back our god race’s destiny and rid us of the curse that hinders us from reproducing. But, the result is that the saints stuck their foot in and caused everything to fall into failure. Even the Chain of Calamity was lost in the Divine Realm! In this case, the Empress shouldn’t have been able to find someone appropriate to return the Chain of Calamity to us, thus she was forced to choose this human boy. Heavenly Empress Xuanqing exhausted every method and all of her strength in order to restore our god race, so how could she possibly allow an accident to occur in a matter that concerns the life or death of our people just for a human boy? When we repair the Chain of Calamity, the Empress will surely bless us!”

The Great Elder said with utter confidence. Everyone also felt this was reasonable. But, the Third Elder frowned, “Your words may not be wrong, but the Empress was kind and this human has shown graciousness to our god race. It is unreasonable for us to directly refuse him like this. But… a spot is too precious, and after deducting the spots that we must give the celestials, we just don’t have any left over. How about we establish a qualifying test so that he can give up on his own…”

“Test?” The Great Elder’s fingers rapped against the armrest. He shook his head, “Don’t underestimate this human youth. He is an outstanding individual, and perhaps… he might not be much worse than Morin…”

As the Great Elder spoke, the god race Elders present were astounded. Some people felt incredulous and even Heaven’s Son Morin slightly frowned.

Heaven’s Son Morin acknowledged that Lin Ming was an outstanding young elite, but he wasn’t convinced that the difference between them wasn’t too far.

Lin Ming was a genius, but he was only at the middle Holy Lord Realm. As for Morin, he was a World King!

The difference in age and cultivation would both appear in a qualifications test.

“Great Elder…”

Heaven’s Son Morin spoke with a sound transmission but the Great Elder interrupted him. “I know you aren’t convinced of this, but we will not discuss this matter for now. First, let us consider a test. Old Three’s words have reminded me of something. There is one test that I believe he cannot pass, because… he is not of the god race.”

As the Great Elder spoke to here, he smiled. The other people immediately understood just what the Great Elder was plotting.

Lin Ming’s talent and potential were formidable, but in the end he couldn’t change his race. If a test concerned the god race bloodline, then Lin Ming would have to admit defeat.

“Lin Ming, If you want a spot, it is possible. However, you must pass the assessment of my people. The contents of the assessment are impartial, and if you cannot pass then I am sorry for that.”

The Great Elder leisurely said, already crossing out Lin Ming in his heart. Lin Ming frowned; he had no idea just what they were saying with sound transmissions just now.

As Lin Ming was thinking of what to say, the atmosphere in the entire grand hall suddenly changed.

A vast but gentle sea-like power slowly swelled forth. The pressure released by the Empyreans and the other Elders was completely washed away by this strength.

“Mm? This is…” Lin Ming was shocked. This was a terrifying strength…

He turned his head to see an old god race man slowly walking towards him, holding onto a walking stick made of withered wood.

This elderly man had long silver hair that shimmered with a brilliant luster. In contrast to that, his face appeared aged and his fires of life were fading away, as if on the precipice of death. Even so, he gave off an incomparably horrifying feeling, as if a universe were contained within him.

“Your Majesty God Sovereign!”

Seeing the old man enter, the other Elders all rose up in salute, deeply bowing in respect. As for the stubborn and unruly Heaven’s Son Morin, he knelt down on a knee, showing even deeper courtesy than the Elders. For a time, the only one standing tall and straight was Lin Ming.

This old man was the God Sovereign of the god race?

Lin Ming was amazed. As he looked at this old man he wasn’t able to distinguish his cultivation at all. But according to what Sheng Mei said, the god race shouldn’t have any True Divinities. In other words, this old man was an extreme Empyrean.

But for some reason, the feeling that this old man gave off was even more terrifying than other extreme Empyreans, as if the entirety of the universe had to submit to him!

“Since you’ve seen His Majesty the God Emperor, hurry up and kneel!”

The Great Elder angrily shouted.

Lin Ming bowed. This was the respect one owed to seniors and elders, as it should be.

Lin Ming’s bowing manners were the same as the god race Elders’. This caused Heaven’s Son Morin to feel ill at heart. His cultivation was clearly higher than Lin Ming’s and yet Lin Ming was standing while he was kneeling.

Just as Heaven’s Son Morin was about to say something, the god race God Sovereign heaved a deep sigh. He looked at Lin Ming, a profound sorrow in his eyes as he asked, “You saw Xuanqing?”

“Mm…” Lin Ming nodded. He knew that the god race God Sovereign was asking him whether or not he had seen Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s corpse. “Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s remains were calm and at peace. She was beautiful and vibrant, as if she had just fallen asleep…”

Although he already knew Xuanqing had died, as the God Sovereign heard this news from Lin Ming’s lips and that he had even seen her corpse, he felt a stabbing pain in his heart.

“Come with me, I will lead you to a place…”

The god race God Sovereign looked at Lin Ming and then slowly turned around. Lin Ming was startled – a place?

Lin Ming didn’t ask where they were going, and only followed close behind the god race God Sovereign. He could feel from this old God Sovereign’s body a deep compassion and empathy, and even a faintly heavy sorrow. This feeling left Lin Ming’s heart racing. He had never felt this feeling from anyone before.

Lin Ming left the grand hall, leaving the god race Elders staring at him with a look of complete loss in their eyes. Where was the old God Sovereign planning to take this human?

“Senior God Sovereign, you are Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s…”

“I am her father.”

The God Sovereign calmly said. After this, he no longer spoke.

The god race’s Heavenly Empress was the same as the spiritas’ Soul Empress; both were a title. Without a doubt, if Heavenly Empress Xuanqing still lived, she would be the next God Sovereign.

But what a pity, she perished far too early. As for the current god race, Lin Ming had only seen young elites like A’Gu and Heaven’s Son Morin. If Heaven’s Son Morin was the number one young elite of the god race, then the god race was in a worrying situation!

After all, their numbers were far too small. Even if the god race were extremely talented and everyone was a dragon, without a massive base population it was difficult to give birth to a true peerless character.

As Lin Ming thought this, he followed the God Sovereign through a series of corridors. The further he walked, the more he felt he was headed deep beneath the temple.

The God Sovereign’s pace was slow. Although he was capable of crossing tens of millions of miles with a single step, transferring through the void as he pleased, in this temple he moved a single step at a time. As his footsteps fell on the dark ground, light muffled echoing sounds filled the air.

Lin Ming felt that the deeper he went, the more ancient the surrounding atmosphere became. It seemed that no one had come to this place for a very long time already. The heavy and simple tiles on the ground were like thick history books that recorded the immeasurably long time that this temple had experienced.

At this time, the God Sovereign came to a stop. “We’re here…”

The old God Sovereign stood before a thick, ancient bronze gate. Behind this bronze gate, dreadful roars sounded out, filled with mourning and causing one’s courage to shake. Soon after, there was a loud rumbling sound of crashing metal, as if an unbelievably terrifying existence was locked in chains!

Lin Ming’s steps paused. He took a deep breath. As this horrifying roar fell into his ears, he didn’t know why but it summoned an inexplicable sadness in his heart, an emotion he couldn’t get over.

The old God Sovereign pointed to the bronze gate, “Go and see for yourself.”

Lin Ming took a deep breath and pushed open the bronze gate. In that moment, Lin Ming felt as if he wasn’t opening a gate, but a thick tombstone.

Behind the ancient gate was a dark and isolated world, similar to a pitch black abyss.

Chapter 1870A – Of the Heart

A chilling cold gloom rushed outwards. In this dark world, Lin Ming could see ancient bronze coffins. These ancient bronze coffins were shockingly large and wrapped in loud clanking chains. It was unknown just whose corpses lay inside.

“There are 12 ancient bronze coffins altogether!”

Lin Ming thought, startled. He could faintly feel that within each bronze coffin slumbered a horrifying existence, but he simply didn’t know what they were.

However, what caught Lin Ming’s attention was not these 12 ancient bronze coffins, but what lay at the end of these coffins; it was an incomparably fierce and hideous beast!

This vicious beast had four thick legs and alarmingly sharp claws. Its entire body was covered in scales and thick black hairs grew out from its body, making it seem like some legendary demon beast from hell.

Lin Ming could sense from within this vicious beast a smell of blood that was as deep as an ocean, as if this beast had taken countless lives.

At this time, the horrifying vicious beast was staring at Lin Ming with its ghostly green eyes. Its four limbs and its titanic form were entangled in layers of chains. When Lin Ming heard the crashing of metal from outside, it was clearly because this vicious beast had been struggling against the chains.

As Lin Ming looked at this demonic beast, he was inexplicably shocked. He didn’t know why, but he could feel a familiar aura from this vicious beast, one that left him filled with disbelief.

“This… this is…” Lin Ming stared at the demonic beast. It was wrapped in black energy, and this black energy was incomparably familiar.

“That is…”

Lin Ming looked at the god race’s God Sovereign, his eyes filling with fear.

Roarr!

At this time, the demonic beast let out an earth-shaking roar. The chains shackling its body tightened and emitted loud cracking sounds.

A terrifying momentum rushed out like a surging storm. Even its saber-sharp claws that were able to rend the void reached less than 10 feet away from Lin Ming.

But Lin Ming remained motionless. He looked at the god race’s God Sovereign, waiting for his answer.

Then, the God Sovereign opened his mouth and slowly spoke, as if he were speaking from across the shores of time. “Its name is… Yuan Chi. Before he became like this, he once had a title. His title was… Empyrean Primordius…”

The God Sovereign’s words were like a bolt of lightning that smashed into Lin Ming’s ears.

For a time, Lin Ming froze solid, unable to summon any words.

Empyrean Primordius… this was Empyrean Primordius?

Lin Ming looked at the demonic beast. It violently struggled against its chains. Its pupils had lost their clarity and it lacked any intelligence at all. It wildly roared, wanting to break free from the shackles of the chains and tear Lin Ming and the old God Sovereign to pieces.

“How could this be!?”

Lin Ming found this difficult to accept!

He had already guessed that Empyrean Primordius hadn’t died. Regarding this, the Black Dragon Sovereign living in the Eternal Demon Abyss had been unable to give him an absolute answer.

What Lin Ming was sure of though was that the corpse of Empyrean Primordius was not within the Eternal Demon Abyss.

But, Lin Ming would never have imagined that Empyrean Primordius, who domineeringly wandered the Divine Realm, nearly becoming a True Divinity, would actually turn into such an appearance.

Just what had happened?

“Your Majesty God Sovereign, this is…”

The God Sovereign shook his head, his withered face wrinkling like a walnut. “In the past, Primordius was heavily wounded by the saints and his mortal body was ruined. The saints wished to capture Primordius alive and refine his body, drawing out the essence of the Grandmist Spirit Bead. But, Primordius broke free from their siege and fled with his tattered body, finally escaping into the Primeval Realm Ruins’ Dark Abyss."

Dark Abyss?

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. He had no idea what the Primeval Realm Ruins were like. It was said that this land contained countless lucky chances and innumerable inheritances, and it was the most important reason the saints were able to prosper and rise to their current lofty heights. The reason the saints wished to exterminate all the remnants of the ancient races was because of these ruins.

“What sort of place is the Dark Abyss?” Lin Ming asked.

The old God Sovereign said, “It is the most dreadful place within the entire Primeval Realm Ruins. It is a bottomless abyss of space and time. Within it exists a massive number of abyssals, cruel and horrifying demons of the Dark Abyss. The deeper one goes, the more terrifying these abyssals are… it is said that the abyssals were sealed away by Heavenly God Asura and his rival, the master of the Holy Scripture. 10 billion years ago, the abyssals were responsible for the apocalypse that fell upon the ancient races.

“Whether these rumors are true or false, there is one thing which is certain, and that is that not even True Divinities dare tread into the innermost depths of the Dark Abyss. In the past, Empyrean Primordius was forced into the Dark Abyss, but because his mortal body was ruined and he himself was nothing but a lamp without oil, he was unable to survive in that land, let alone take revenge. So in order to live on, he did something that no one had ever done before…”

“What did he do?” Lin Ming looked at Empyrean Primordius, his heart racing with fear.

“He seized the body of an abyssal…” As the old God Sovereign spoke to here, he let out a long breath.

Normally, when a martial artist seized the body of another they would carefully consider the process again and again. First, a martial artist would make sure that the body they seized was far weaker than themselves, and their talent also had to reach the extremes. At the same time, all sorts of preparations were required in order to ensure that the spirit mark of the target was cleanly wiped away!

But even in such a situation, after successfully seizing the body of another, all sorts of residual leftovers would remain. After all, the body wasn’t their own to begin with. If body and soul weren’t perfectly compatible with each other, then that would cause one’s talent to drop and their cultivation to rise at a snail’s pace. If the will of the seized target was too strong and there were spirit marks remaining, these spirit marks would invade the soul of the seizer and cause a split personality.

For instance, the Ancient Devil that emerged from the Sea of Miracles hadn’t seized Yang Yun’s body in the past. Rather, he used Yang Yun as a chess piece and chose Lin Ming as his final target. But in the end, the Ancient Devil failed to seize Lin Ming’s body.

As for Empyrean Primordius, what he took over was an abyssal. In terms of soul force, mortal body, or inner energy, they were powerful in all aspects, like incarnations of demons. Wanting to seize their bodies was easier said than done!

The old God Sovereign said, “It is more accurate to say that Primordius fused his ruined body and soul with an abyssal, melting them together as one. Now… I fear that Primordius has lost any remnants of his mind and has completely fused with the abyssal’s soul, becoming like he is now.”

“He fused as one with the demon?” Lin Ming looked at Empyrean Primordius, unsure of what to say.

In the past he had fantasized that because of some reasons, Empyrean Primordius had hidden himself away in some corner of the universe. Or maybe, when the great calamity erupted, Empyrean Primordius might appear at a crucial moment, perhaps even making another breakthrough and coming close to the realm of True Divinity!

Although he might not have been able to turn the tide, his appearance would have at least given humanity a chance to recover!

But reality was cruel. A generation’s peerless proud son of heaven had ended up with such a fate!

Lin Ming silently stepped in front of Empyrean Primordius and deeply bowed.

However, even though Lin Ming’s body exuded a vague grandmist energy, the pupils of Empyrean Primordius were still filled with bloodthirst, completely disregarding Lin Ming’s status as the grandmist successor.

Roar!

Chapter 1874 – God Decrees

The first three spots were basically impossible to compete for, because Shenku, Lanlu, and Diwuhen had a momentum that was far too strong. It wasn’t difficult to imagine them being chosen.

But the fourth spot was different – there were far too many candidates!

Even Heaven’s Son Morin had a chance.

Although Lin Ming looked down on Morin’s talent, that was only because his level of judgment was far too high. Towards those geniuses that couldn’t become True Divinities in the future, he felt they were all so-so.

In fact, according to the current trend of development of those within the god race, Morin had high hopes of becoming a peak Empyrean.

The title of Heaven’s Son wasn’t in vain.

But, he was far too young and his cultivation was only at the World King realm. Even if his strength increased he still wouldn’t be helpful in the great calamity. Thus, he worried, afraid that the old God Sovereign wouldn’t choose him.

And now the old God Sovereign seemed to be particularly looking after Lin Ming, making him even more anxious.

“His Majesty God Sovereign shouldn’t have lost his mind so badly to give such an important spot to an outsider!”

At this time, many people were sharing the same thoughts as Morin. The Great Elder patted Morin’s shoulder, indicating for him not to be worried.

The Great Elder also fantasized about being chosen, but he felt his chances weren’t too high.

The high level figures of the god race were divided into internal an external positions. Internal positions were Elders; they managed internal affairs. The external positions were war generals, responsible for managing the battlefield.

The ones that the old God Sovereign chose were all war generals. Elders, even the highest of Elders, basically had no hopes.

“The last spot…” The old God Sovereign folded his hands behind his back, his profound eyes sweeping over the faces of those present. “The last person is… Lin Ming!”

The old God Sovereign’s voice was calm; this was something he had already long known about.

However, no one else had been aware of this. Their reactions were intense.

This was a single stone throw bringing up a thousand waves!

Lin Ming!?

Not to mention the god race, even the celestials weren’t able to conceal their astonishment. They were extremely familiar with the powerhouses of the primal god race, and those that entered the Asura forbidden land had to be the strongest powerhouses as well as those with the most latent potential.

For instance, although the old God Sovereign was powerful, his potential had come to an end, so he wouldn’t enter.

As for Lin Ming, he was clearly at the middle Holy Lord realm and they had never heard his name before.

“The one the God Sovereign chose… could he be a hidden bloodline descendant?” The celestials’ Battle Sovereign To Bagui asked. He looked at the old God Sovereign with puzzlement in his eyes. But in that wizened old face which looked like a well that had never been stirred, he couldn’t discover any useful information at all.

“No, something’s wrong, that youth isn’t of the god race, but… an alien race?”

This discovery astonished To Bagui.

As for the powerhouses of the god race, they were no longer able to sit still!

The invasion of the saints, the arrival of the great calamity – entering the Asura forbidden land could be called the final chance for the primal god race to resist the saints.

Priority for such a valuable chance first needed to be given to Empyreans that could help in the war.

And if a spot was to be given to a junior, that spot should at least be given to a genius of their own race. How could they give such a massive lucky chance to an outsider?

After the shock came the anger.

“Your Majesty God Sovereign, I cannot understand this!”

An Elder directly stood up. To question the God Sovereign was deeply disrespectful, but in such chaotic times many people couldn’t attend to these formalities.

“I beg Your Majesty God Sovereign to reconsider.”

Another Elder stood up.

The Great Elder and Heaven’s Son Morin were forcefully holding themselves back from standing up. Heaven’s Son Morin’s eyes had turned blood red and his fists were gripped so tightly that blue veins stuck out. He grit his teeth, holding in his words.

Other powerhouses of the primal god race spoke in turn, their words deeply sincere.

But, the old God Sovereign only said, “Have you all forgotten who brought back the main body of the Chain of Calamity?”

Without a doubt, Lin Ming had done a great favor for the god race.

“Of course I remember…” At this time, the Great Elder spoke up, “When Lin Ming first came to our god race, I was the one who received him, but… these matters must be separated. Lin Ming passed through multiple universes to return Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s Chain of Calamity to us – this benevolence, our god race will remember. But it cannot be forgotten that the Chain of Calamity originally belonged to our god race to begin with, so Lin Ming was simply returning something to its rightful owner. To pick up someone’s wealth and return it, isn’t that just the correct moral action?”

What the Great Elder said was absolutely justified. His eyes swept towards Lin Ming. Lin Ming only remained silent, not refuting this point.

The Great Elder smiled with victory. He continued to say, “Your Majesty God Sovereign, our god race aren’t those that forget favors or don’t know how to express thanks. Regarding Lin Ming, I believe we should heavily reward him. The god race has many treasures, and these can be granted to him at will, and even ancient divine techniques can be wholeheartedly taught to him. But, the Asura forbidden land was left behind by the ancestor of our people. In order to enter, one needs the accumulation of destiny. As a human, Lin Ming doesn’t possess the god race bloodline at all. If he enters the territory of the Asura forbidden land he will not be able to penetrate as deeply as the young elites of our primal god race. It is simply a waste of nature’s gifts.

“And with the great calamity approaching, Lin Ming is only a junior with a middle Holy Lord realm cultivation; there isn’t any use for him at all. The spots are limited… I ask Your Majesty God Sovereign to please think carefully of this decision.”

The Great Elder’s words were approved by many god race martial artists present.

Not to mention those that had hopes of struggling for the fourth spot, even those that didn’t have any hopes of entering the Asura forbidden land didn’t want to see a human like Lin Ming take away one of the lucky chances of their people.

For a time, many Elders stood up, opposing the God Sovereign.

Seeing this scene, the Great Elder was more than satisfied. His words were truly reasonable and matched common sense; they were sure to win the approval of the others.

At this time, Heaven’s Son Morin also stood up, his voice filled with energy, “Your Majesty God Sovereign, if you wish to compensate Sir Lin then I, Morin, am willing to help. My clan will contribute more than enough treasures…”

If he could enter the forbidden land, Morin didn’t mind bleeding a little. Regarding this, Lin Ming only faintly smiled. The treasures of Morin’s clan? To Lin Ming, they might only be dregs unworthy of mention.

However, he didn’t argue. He knew that with his current status, speaking was in vain.

At this time, the old God Sovereign straightened himself and lightly said, “I am only informing you of the decision I made, not discussing it with you all. I will not be reconsidering this matter. Those that oppose will be handled according to the rules of our people.”

The old God Sovereign’s voice was slow and meandering, as if he were talking about something immaterial. But, no one could raise their voice to resist him!

For a time, all the god race martial artists froze.

The old God Sovereign had mentioned the rules of their race!

If they followed the rules of the race, then this was naturally the rule that said the God Sovereign could not be disobeyed. This was no minor charge.

Within the god race, the old God Sovereign was kind and wise, loved by many. But if he became severe, he left people shivering in fear!

Although he was old, he possessed absolute authority within the god race. No one dared to disobey him.

One reason was that the other extreme Empyreans like Diwuhen were rocks that were found by the old God Sovereign’s sharp eyes and polished into the gems they were today. They had been personally taught by him.

And, the second reason was that the god decrees left behind by the Asura Road Master were in the old God Sovereign’s hands!

The words of the old God Sovereign seemed overbearing and unreasonable, just like some petty tyrant. But placed within the god race, these words represented the highest command; no one could violate them.

“But…”

Heaven’s Son Morin was anxious, but facing the old God Sovereign he wasn’t able to summon any courage.

The other Elders also didn’t dare to speak, even though the discontent in their hearts had accumulated to the maximum.

For a time, all their hatred turned to Lin Ming. Lin Ming could immediately feel each gaze, filled with hate and dripping with envy, lock onto his body. If looks could kill, he’d have died countless times already.

Under the eyes of so many people, Lin Ming remained silent as before, without losing his composure.

Seeing Lin Ming’s performance, To Bagui traced his chin, a thoughtful look in his eyes. Indeed, this youth was extraordinary.

However, this alone was surely not enough to have the old God Sovereign support him to such a degree. There had to be something special about this boy.

“Your Majesty God Sovereign, you remain as wise as ever!”

At this time, To Bagui stood up and spoke with a wide smile.

It had to be known that even if the old God Sovereign resisted all opposition and continued to support Lin Ming, although the others wouldn’t dare to say anything, they would still remain dissatisfied with what happened. This was the old God Sovereign overdrawing his authority!

Perhaps even the old God Sovereign’s several apprentices weren’t too happy about their master’s actions…

“Battle Sovereign, there is no need to exchange useless pleasantries. Let us get straight to the point. According to our earlier agreement, the god race and celestials will work together to repair the Chain of Calamity. I believe that the Battle Sovereign has already brought those things…”

“Of course!” To Bagui took out a small box from his spatial ring and placed it atop the table.

This box seemed common, but after it was brought out it affected the surrounding Laws, even causing tiny vortexes to gather around it.

It was clear that whatever was in the box was extraordinary!

“From ancient times, the ancestors of my people have left behind three god decrees!”

God decrees?

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred and he intently stared at the box. Repairing the Chain of Calamity required god decrees, and when fighting the saints, god decrees could also be used.

The god decrees left behind by the Asura Road Master, if used by a peak Empyrean, were enough to threaten the life of a True Divinity!

This sort of mysterious god decree left behind by the ancient supreme elders had far too many uses.

If he had the chance, Lin Ming certainly had to observe what it was.

He saw To Bagui carefully open the box and take out three withered and yellow symbol papers from a bed of yellow silk. These symbol papers looked ordinary, even somewhat rough. The paper used to make them was strangely thin, and the runes drawn atop them were like wriggling worms that exuded an incomparably ancient aura.

However, upon seeing these three symbol papers, Lin Ming was stunned.

These… these were the god decrees?

Weren’t these divine runic symbols he studied at the Asura Road?

These lines, these runes, they were far too familiar. Lin Ming was also familiar with the Laws inherent within them!

The so-called god decrees left behind by the ancient elites of the past were divine runic symbols?

If so, then the ancient supreme elders that left behind their god decrees likely stemmed from the same lineage as the Asura Road Master!

And the so-called Asura Road Master’s god decrees were divine runic symbols drawn up by him!

Chapter 1875 – Smokeless

The three ordinary and wrinkled yellow symbol papers seemed to contain an infinitely enchanting charm, gathering the gaze of all the primal god powerhouses present.

A strange light leapt into the old God Sovereign’s eyes. Inside, a black vortex seemed to swirl. A beam of black light shot out, lingering atop the pale yellow symbol paper.

His eyes contained the power of strange Laws. They were able to pierce through stars and gaze through the vastness of space, but upon touching the yellow symbol papers, they only shook a little before calming down.

“These really are god decrees left behind by ancient celestial God Sovereigns. The Laws inside can be used to repair the Chain of Calamity.” The old God Sovereign smiled, nodding his head.

As the other powerhouses of the primal god race saw how powerful these common-looking god decrees were, they let out sighs of relief.

The celestial powerhouses had smug expressions crossing their faces.

The Chain of Calamity was a True Divinity level magic tool. After being damaged, the Great Dao Laws inside would also be harmed.

And those Great Dao Laws were also of the True Divinity level. It was basically beyond the capabilities of an Empyrean level powerhouse to repair it.

Even if they used rare materials to bond the Chain of Calamity, in order to renew the Laws within they would have to use an upper True Divinity level god decree to make it whole once more.

Repairing the Chain of Calamity wasn’t a simple task.

Every step had to be brought to the peak of perfection.

First, one had to discern just how many threads of Great Dao Laws within the Chain of Calamity were damaged, and then one had to extract the corresponding Great Dao Laws from the god decrees, fusing them together with the True Divinity magic tool to repair it.

But in order to achieve perfect synchronization, the fusion process required a massive amount of time and effort. At the least three or four upper Empyreans would have to work together.

In the primal god race, they also had god decrees passed down through their people. But, the god decrees in the hands of the primal god race didn’t have sufficient Laws to repair the Chain of Calamity.

That was unless they used… the god decrees left behind by the Asura Road Master himself.

But the Asura Road Master’s god decrees were the greatest weapons the primal god race had to deter and frighten the saints. How could they possibly use them to repair the Chain of Calamity?

In this sort of situation, the primal god race could only seek help from the celestials.

And it was because of this that the primal god race readily agreed to the terms and gave two entry spots for the Asura forbidden land to the celestials.

Looking at the god decrees, the god race martial artists nodded together.

At this time, the old God Sovereign said, “If there is no problem, then we shall begin repairs now.”

To Bagui hesitated for a moment, not answering.

“Oh? Is there some problem?” The old God Sovereign’s eyes looked towards To Bagui. His eyes seemed as if they could see through everything.

“My apologies…”

To Bagui shook his head. The primal god race members were stunned. At this critical moment could it be that the celestials planned to renege on their previous agreement?

“A situation has arisen within my people. Before coming here, there was a meeting of the high level figures within my race…” To Bagui said, sounding a bit chagrined.

“Get to the point.”

The old God Sovereign still had a kindly expression, but his eyes became several points sharper and fiercer, making it so that others didn’t dare to look at him.

To Bagui took a deep breath and frankly said, “Everyone here should be aware just how precious the god decrees are to our ancient races. Using one means there is one less, and they aren’t things that can be duplicated. For numerous hundreds of millions of years, whether it is the celestials or god race, there were many superbly talented individuals who had given everything to research these god decrees. However, even True Divinities weren’t able to unravel their mysteries, as if something has always been missing…

“My celestial race has far too few of these god decrees remaining. With the saints invading the Primeval Universe, because of the bigger picture, we celestials are willing to take out these three god decrees to repair the Chain of Calamity. This is a great risk to us. So… I hope we can obtain another spot to enter the forbidden land…”

To Bagui’s words seemed as if he were trying to negotiate, and one could even sense an incomparably sincere and friendly tone to them. But from how overwhelming his eyes were, the god race martial artists knew that this matter was something the celestials had decided far in advance, and they also wouldn’t budge on this issue either.

For a time, the entire meeting site was stirred into a great uproar. Many primal god race martial artists felt suffocated within their chests, as if their hearts were being set on fire!

Just what sort of lucky chance was the Asura forbidden land? And there were only six spots! Moreover, it was originally a lucky chance that belonged to the primal god race. For them to give the celestials two spots was already showing them extreme favor. But, they didn’t think that the celestials would try to take a yard after taking an inch, and would ask for another spot.

“The conditions have already been decided beforehand!” The god race Elders angrily said.

“I understand that, but when the conditions were drawn up that was in a situation where the main body of the Chain of Calamity had yet to be found. That is something which concerns the previous generation, and at the time, the great calamity hadn’t begun yet. Aren’t the god decrees also precious? However, every situation has to be considered on its own merits. Now, the god decrees concern the survival of my people!

“As for violating the previous agreement, my race will provide sufficient compensation. Moreover, I believe that the juniors of my celestial race will not waste this spot. At least, they will be a far better choice than certain individuals.”

As To Bagui spoke, his eyes glanced towards Lin Ming.

Lin Ming frowned. He was perplexed at being suddenly drawn into this mess. But, with his cultivation and also as a human, it was normal for him to be rejected by others again and again.

He looked towards the three god decrees.

Without a doubt, these were divine runic symbols drawn and left behind by ancient True Divinities 10 billion years ago that were part of the Asura Road Master’s lineage.

And according to what To Bagui said, these divine runic symbols could not be reproduced. This was because even if there was a True Divinity present, none of them had the ability to use the Asura Heavenly Dao within the 33 Heavens.

Extrapolating from what To Bagui said, they had always been missing a certain ‘something’.

Thus, even if they studied the divine runic arts, none of them were able to copy the god decrees.

To Bagui looked at Lin Ming. Many others also turned to Lin Ming.

After the anger that flashed over the god race martial artists disappeared, a complex gloating expression reappeared in their wake. Although the celestials had broken their promise and slapped the god race in the face, this was a matter that didn’t concern them. The one that should be worrying the most was that young human boy.

Many people were already unhappy that the old God Sovereign had designated Lin Ming as one of the people to enter. But because they were overwhelmed by the old God Sovereign’s pressure, none of them dared to argue this point.

Now with the celestials exerting their own pressure, if one person had to be removed from the four chosen, that person would be Lin Ming!

Otherwise, the old God Sovereign’s apprentices wouldn’t agree with him either.

Now, how would the old God Sovereign deal with the situation?

“Battle Sovereign, your conditions are far too much!”

The Great Elder frowned as he spoke, but his tone was quite amiable. If this were before then he wouldn’t have shown such goodwill to the celestials. But now that the entire Primeval Universe was facing a great calamity, they really did need to win over the celestials.

“With the great calamity descending upon us, the god decrees are also important to my people. If we cannot obtain another spot then we would rather not enter at all. After all, it is unknown what any of us can obtain from the forbidden land! With the god decrees, a single additional one will guarantee the survival of my people that much more.”

To Bagui refuted, leaving no room for compromise. He wasn’t joking at all.

“And besides…”

To Bagui suddenly flicked his fingers and a mote of dazzling light shot out. The mote of light rapidly spun in the air, growing until it became a white jade palace.

The front doors of the palace opened and a peerless woman flew out. Her figure was extraordinary and her face was shrouded in mystical light. Countless runes flashed around her like a storm of sand, making one unable to see her clearly.

Her wings were shining red, like billowing flames. Her entire body exuded an unpredictable rhythm that seemed to beat in harmony with the surrounding world.

Her cultivation was at the Great World King realm.

“Celestial Goddess Smokeless greets the seniors of the god race.”

The woman’s voice was like the keening of a phoenix. Every word she spoke seemed to be condensed from the true meaning of the Great Dao, floating up and down in the void as they shined with infinite understandings.

It was clear she was displaying her strength to its limit. For a Great World King to expose their strength in front of a crowd of Empyreans, that was an extremely arrogant and bold move to begin with. But, this woman named Smokeless indeed had the capital to do so!

“At just the Great World King realm boundary, she has the momentum of an Empyrean. Moreover, just her words seem to resonate with the Laws in this ancient grand hall… this woman is terrifying. If she has enough time she will become a True Divinity!”

As Lin Ming observed this celestial woman, a brilliant light flashed in his eyes.

Whether it was the god race or the celestials, neither of them had True Divinity powerhouses any longer. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have remained passively taking the attacks of the saints. If there really was a junior with high hopes of becoming a True Divinity, then this was unimaginably valuable to the god race and the celestials!

As the other primal god race powerhouses saw the strength displayed by this woman, their lips began to twitch. What Lin Ming saw, they naturally could see too.

The celestials actually possessed a junior with the talent and potential to become a True Divinity in the future!

It was no wonder that they requested another spot; it seemed it was all to support this woman named Smokeless.

Heaven’s Son Morin tightly gripped his fists, goosebumps rising all over his body. Without a doubt, this celestial woman, whether it was in strength or talent, was far above him!

“How hateful… I am already faintly inferior to that Lin Ming, but I’ve never truly fought him so I might not necessarily lose. But now, I am an entire level lower than this Smokeless. I just cannot summon the courage to contend with her!”

Heaven’s Son Morin hated everything to the extreme. Being the number one junior of the god race sounded glorious, but the old God Sovereign hadn’t placed him in his eyes. Even the God Sovereign mark had been given to the outsider Lin Ming.

“Smokeless? I remember now…”

The old God Sovereign’s voice seemed to echo in the air. “The Celestial Patriarch found you, a little baby girl frozen in ice, within a land of extreme cold… your origins are strange and afterwards you went out to adventure but it was said that you died. I never imagined that when the great calamity arrived, you would return safely and your strength would have risen yet again…”

The old God Sovereign looked at Smokeless and slowly nodded. “How rare, how rare… after experiencing a catastrophe and not dying, you instead made a breakthrough. Your future achievements are without limit. In all my years, I didn’t expect such an outstanding character to appear once more…”

The old God Sovereign’s voice was touched with a trace of sadness. The ancient remnant races had indeed declined.

In the far off past, they once ruled the entirety of the 33 Heavens. Even if the saints and spiritas were added together, they had still been several of times stronger. But now, they didn’t even have a single True Divinity.

“Your Majesty God Sovereign, what do you think of Smokeless? Does she have the qualifications to enter the Asura forbidden land?” To Bagui asked with a smile.

Chapter 1877 – Repairing the Decree

Lin Ming stood before the black stone table, a mere three feet away from the god decrees. He stood still, allowing his divine sense to sink into them.

The celestial powerhouses all had thoughtful smiles on their faces. As for the primal god race powerhouses, they all had complex moods; they felt as if they were being seen as jokes by the celestials.

“What are you all thinking? This Lin Ming isn’t even a part of our god race. Even if he shames himself here, it has nothing to do with our god race!”

Heaven’s Son Morin indignantly said.

“Let him be. If he loses face then that is the same as his Majesty God Sovereign losing face, but since His Majesty had consented to this then there is nothing we can do.”

The Great Elder said with finality before composing his mind.

And at this time, Lin Ming didn’t pay attention to the reactions of the many powerhouses around him.

He had already entered into the fused martial intent state, his mind completely focused on the three wrinkled yellow god decrees before him. In his eyes, a mystical aura began to gradually flow over from them.

He could see the revolution of the Asura Heavenly Dao. Faint traces continuously circulated within the god decrees.

These three god decrees were the work of ancient upper True Divinities; they were far beyond normal. With Lin Ming’s current level of strength, it was absolutely impossible for him to create imitations of them.

But, just comprehending the truths within and polishing some of the flaws might actually be possible!

After all, the Laws were interlinked and Lin Ming had obtained the true legacy of the Asura Road Master. In particular, after he entered the ancient galactic battlefield within the Akashic Dream World, his comprehension of the Asura Sutra and his ability to utilize the power of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws had reached frightening degrees.

“Mm?”

Suddenly, a strange light flashed through Lin Ming’s face. He could feel his divine sense falling into an endless black hole, as if he were being sucked in by the energy of the god decrees.

“The celestials’ three god decrees have eroded through 10 billion years of time, and sections of the Great Dao that formed them have been damaged. Thus, in the lines, there are energy black holes that swallow my divine sense…”

Understanding what was happening, Lin Ming didn’t take back his sense. Instead, he allowed it to revolve around the energy black hole, constantly deducing how to repair it.

“These are True Divinity level god decrees after all. My ability is lacking, but I should be able to unravel some of the Laws…”

Lin Ming’s eyes became increasingly bright. Without noticing it, over an hour had passed.

To the martial artists present, this amount of time wasn’t anything at all. Since they believed Lin Ming was playing games with them, they started to become impatient.

“Your Majesty Battle Sovereign, how long will we continue waiting?”

Smokeless asked. She wasn’t impatient, but she simply felt that for so many powerhouses to surround a junior and watch him play around with treasures and also wait for such a long time, this scene was far too stupid.

And at this moment, Lin Ming suddenly stopped.

He looked towards the old God Sovereign and said, “Your Majesty God Sovereign, do you have a god decree drawn up by an ordinary True Divinity? I would like to reference it.”

Lin Ming had made far too many requests, again and again playing tricks. Many people felt they were nearing the limits of their endurance.

Looking at these three god decrees wasn’t enough, but now he wanted to play around with the old God Sovereign?

The old God Sovereign didn’t refuse him nor did he ask Lin Ming what he wanted to do with an ordinary True Divinity god decree. He simply flicked his fingers and with a flash, a god decree flew out from his spatial ring, shooting towards Lin Ming.

If a martial artist could break through to the realm of True Divinity, that meant their talent was enough to overwhelm all, far surpassing all others in the vastness of space.

There were few True Divinities as it was, and upper True Divinities were even rarer. Even in ancient times this was also true.

Thus, there were correspondingly few god decrees left behind by upper True Divinities. As for god decrees left behind by ordinary True Divinities, there were many more of them.

After the old God Sovereign tossed out the ordinary True Divinity god decree, Lin Ming grasped it in his hand. He placed it between his middle finger and index finger, probing it with his sense.

A god decree left behind by an ordinary True Divinity was far simpler.

And at the same time, over the last 10 billion years these god decrees had also been eroded by time. The Great Dao lines had received minor damages.

As for the strength within these god decrees, a great deal had leaked out!

However, a True Divinity was still a True Divinity. Even if the strength had leaked out, the god decrees drawn by a True Divinity could not be compared to those drawn by an Empyrean.

This was because the height of the Laws was completely different.

Lin Ming investigated this god decree for another hour. Many of the celestial martial artists had reached the end of their fuse.

“He’s playing so many tricks.”

Someone derided. But, seeing that To Bagui was calmly watching without any worry, these people also silently waited.

“Let him stumble around until he falls over. At that time, I wonder if the god race will still fight for his spot?”

“Mm, at that time the god race’s old God Sovereign won’t have anything to say about it either!”

Thinking that they would receive the spot from all of this, many of the celestial Empyreans began to warm up with happiness.

Of the three spots for the celestials, the Battle Sovereign would take one, and the second would undoubtedly go to Smokeless. But as for the last spot, they all had a chance to obtain it!

Such a lucky chance, who wouldn’t desire it?

As all these people were plotting their strategies, at this time, Lin Ming suddenly stirred. He placed the old God Sovereign’s god decree together with the three other god decrees.

The four god decrees were lined up together.

At the same time, Lin Ming began to activate the Asura Heavenly Dao Diagram within his body.

The dao diagram had been obtained from the Asura Road’s final trial and had fused together with his flesh and blood. It was equal to creating a miniature Asura Road world within his body, allowing him to utilize the power of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws as he pleased.

And most importantly, this dao diagram had been personally created by the Asura Road Master, and the Laws contained within it were the most primitive and fundamental true meanings of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws.

Omm –

As the Asura Heavenly Array Diagram began, Lin Ming’s aura started to change, as if the essence of the 33 Heavens’ Heavenly Daos was gathering unto him.

Within his skin, his flesh, his bones, infinite Asura Heavenly Dao Law runes began to sparkle, releasing limitless mystical strength.

“Mm… this is…”

In the grand hall, whether it was the primal god race or celestials, their ancestors were all from the lineage of the Asura Road Master. Now that Lin Ming suddenly erupted with the aura of the 33 Heavens, they were left bewildered.

This mysterious aura as well as these incomparably familiar yet plain-looking runes… how could Lin Ming be able to use them?

The most source Law runes of the Asura Heavenly Dao flashed, as if they were the peaks of towering mountains.

Each peak released endless light and a boundless might, as if a rumbling river of stars was surging into the middle of the god decree.

And the object Lin Ming chose was the god decree the old God Sovereign had lent to him.

As the originally silent and motionless god decree felt the most primitive power of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws, it began to awaken like a great beast stirring from its deep slumber.

With a loud humming sound, light shot out from the yellow god decree.

Each ray of light was as deep as a sea, shaking the world.

These beams of light seemed immensely powerful, but as they pierced Lin Ming they went straight through his body without affecting him at all.

As this strange scene fell into everyone’s eyes, even those that didn’t want to admit it couldn’t help but acknowledge that Lin Ming had his own peculiar methods.

As the power of the god decree was energized, Lin Ming found an opportunity. His hands traced exquisite arcs in the air, causing a wisp of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws to change paths and flow into the middle of the god decree.

The path of this wisp of light was unpredictable. The power of strange Laws surged, heartily wandering within the god decree.

“What is he doing?”

Many people felt that something was wrong. At this time, no one dared to look down on Lin Ming again.

They could clearly see that Lin Ming was carving a rune into the god decree!

This was a god decree left behind by a True Divinity? How could a mere Holy Lord leave a rune atop it?

Lin Ming’s ten fingers flashed, his face solemn. Beads of sweat ran down his forehead and temples. As his understandings into the internal structure of the god decree became more profound, he became increasingly alarmed.

A trace of his life essence followed along the ghostly path of the god decree’s Asura Heavenly Dao Laws. It was like he was continuously bumping into an endless wall of steel.

“Here…”

After a long period of time, he suddenly saw a trace of damage within the interior of the god decree.

In terms of repairing divine runic symbols, Lin Ming could be called a veteran. His fingers slowly swiveled in the air as he formed beautiful runes that constantly marked the area where the Law lines were broken.

Within each path, an infinite number of changes was possible.

To repair these divine runic symbols that had existed for 10 billion years already, Lin Ming didn’t even need materials, because the materials were already gathered and readied; they had all been incorporated into the symbol paper.

Everything would be fine as long as Lin Ming could rewrite the damaged Laws.

Lin Ming focused his mind, constantly deducing the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws and patching up the damages…

However, these were still god decrees drawn up by True Divinities. Even a minor repair not worthy of mention required Lin Ming to use up a tremendous amount of energy. Not only did he need to thoroughly comprehend the Laws, but he needed to supplement them with an enormous amount of the power of divinity.

To Lin Ming, this was a gigantic use of energy.

More and more sweat tumbled down Lin Ming’s forehead.

But at the same time, he continued to repair. The god decree emitted a brilliant light, blazing to the eyes and making one unable to look directly at it.

Lin Ming’s figure was enveloped in this radiance, making him seem blurry.

“He… what is he doing?”

Whether it was the martial artists of the god race or celestials, they were all stunned.

Even an Empyrean couldn’t understand Lin Ming or the Laws he was using.

Although they couldn’t understand, they were still all people with extremely sharp vision. This light and the charm of these Laws were not only mysterious but contained unimaginable truths within.

What Lin Ming was doing, none of them could understand.

“Something’s wrong! No… this… the power within the god decree is increasing!”

A celestial powerhouse’s eyes popped wide open. He could clearly feel that in the blazing light, the god decree beneath Lin Ming’s hands was slowly strengthening!

That ordinary True Divinity god decree was now slowly overtaking the three god decrees created by an upper True Divinity!

How was this possible!?

“Could this boy have referenced our celestial race’s god decrees to transform the old God Sovereign’s god decree and make it stronger!? Am I dreaming here!?”

To Bagui suddenly thought of this possibility. But, this was a completely absurd conclusion, one he couldn’t accept at all!

Chapter 1878 – New

The god decrees had existed for so many billions of years and yet no one had been able to completely understand them, much less improve or copy them.

But now, reality was laid out before them. Lin Ming had actually referenced the three upper True Divinity god decrees to transform an ordinary True Divinity god decree. This was simply incredible!

Let alone To Bagui, even the god race’s old God Sovereign was utterly shocked.

The old God Sovereign had lived for innumerable years and his judgment had reached a nearly omniscient level. He intuitively felt that Lin Ming was extraordinary.

But no matter what his intuition told him, he never would have imagined that Lin Ming could repair god decrees.

The light bloomed increasingly strongly, completely covering Lin Ming within it. The mysterious Asura Law runes danced in the air. Lin Ming’s hands raced through the skies, the speed of his movements becoming faster and faster!

Beneath the gaze of all present, the energy fluctuations within Lin Ming’s god decree also became increasingly strong!

In terms of energy, it would soon reach the three god decrees brought by To Bagui!

At this time the celestial powerhouses could no longer sit still.

For the ancient remnant races, these god decrees were incomparably precious. Using one meant one less in existence. Yet, they could be transformed by a Holy Lord junior?

The upper True Divinity god decrees brought by the celestials, ones that they were almost unwilling to give up, were now almost similar in energy fluctuations to an ordinary True Divinity god decree that had been fiddled around with by Lin Ming. Didn’t this mean that their previous protection and worship of these upper True Divinity god decrees was nothing but a joke?

If a junior could create and improve these god decrees, weren’t they just not valuable at all!?

“Your Majesty Battle Sovereign, if that human boy is able to complete the transformation and remake the ordinary god decree with the same level of strength as a peak god decree, then the primal god race won’t need us to open the forbidden land at all.”

A celestial Elder suddenly said.

As To Bagui heard this, his expression became far more interesting.

The reason that the primal god race would request the help of the celestials and ally with them was because they only had the strongest god decrees left behind by the Asura Road Master as well as those left behind by ordinary True Divinities; they were lacking god decrees left behind by upper and middle True Divinities.

This was because there were far too few upper True Divinities. The primal god race had also inherited god decrees left by upper True Divinities, but for various reasons they had used them up.

But with Lin Ming, this problem no longer existed.

The peak Empyreans of the primal god race would absolutely be able to repair the Chain of Calamity by themselves!

“How could this be, I just cannot understand…”

To Bagui felt his thoughts fall into utter chaos. He didn’t know how Lin Ming accomplished what he did, but this was the indisputable truth.

He originally wanted to blackmail the god race into giving up even another spot, but now, the god race didn’t need them at all. They might not even receive a single spot!

Everything had been lost!

To Bagui fell into depression. He madly desired this lucky chance, and Smokeless also needed this opportunity!

Smokeless was the hope that would stabilize their celestial race in the future.

“This boy must have some secret!”

To Bagui said with a voice dripping with hate as he gripped his fists. Even if someone killed him he would never have believed that Lin Ming’s perception was so powerful that he could unravel the god decrees that not even True Divinities could understand, and do so in a short two hours. In other words, the peerless God Sovereigns of the ancient remnant races were nothing but a joke before him!

But so what if he had a secret? Seeing how the old God Sovereign was supporting Lin Ming, Lin Ming would likely become a treasure of the primal god race.

To transform an ordinary god decree into a top god decree, he more than deserved such treatment!

Perhaps even the entire primal god race would prostrate themselves to this boy.

At this time, no matter what anyone else was thinking, Lin Ming paid no attention to any of them. His focus was tense and his forehead was dripping wet.

He had underestimated just how terrifying a True Divinity level divine runic symbol was.

Even if he thoroughly understood the Laws, he still lacked strength. Wanting to completely restore these divine runic symbols that had been eroded over 10 billion years was excruciatingly difficult.

Moreover, his physical condition was in a poor state!

His body shook. Because he was exhausting himself of his strength, Lin Ming’s fingers trembled and the runes nearly exploded around him.

If the runes collapsed, then even though the god decree would be fine, most of the work Lin Ming put into repairing it would be destroyed!

Lin Ming frightened himself for a moment. And, this scene was noticed by the old God Sovereign. The old God Sovereign was able to clearly feel that Lin Ming, wrapped in the blazing light, had a much weaker aura than before.

That’s right… Lin Ming was injured before, and he had yet to fully recover.

Many people recalled that when Lin Ming first entered the grand hall, his blood vitality had been unstable and his meridians and organs had been broken in various places!

His injuries were due to Empyrean Primordius.

These were deep wounds caused by a peak Empyrean. Even if Lin Ming had prepared himself earlier and had blocked over 95% of the damage, the remaining amount was still no laughing matter.

“This boy, he can still repair the god decree after being injured? This is…”

Heaven’s Son Morin was speechless. Lin Ming’s actions had left him lacking even a little bit of confidence. The difference was too great!

At this time, the old God Sovereign flung wide his sleeves and a great sun seemed to explode from within his body. Billowing strength rolled towards the old God Sovereign before transforming into a gentle divine light that shot into Lin Ming’s body.

This gentle divine light slowly sank into Lin Ming.

Normally speaking, the power of an Empyrean powerhouse was formidable and unruly. If it entered the body of a junior, they simply wouldn’t possess the ability to control it. But, the power shot out by the old God Sovereign was gentle to the extreme, allowing Lin Ming to freely use it as he wished.

For a time, Lin Ming felt like his body was a dry field that was suddenly experiencing a revitalizing rain. His strength immediately returned.

With the Laws guiding the way and with the support of the old God Sovereign’s power, the repair process of the god decree became extremely smooth.

Another two hours passed. Lin Ming’s repair process was nearing its finale.

In that moment within the void, endless Asura runes gathered together, forming a giant purple vortex, all of it being slowly sucked into the god decree.

For a time, divine light shot into the heavens. The runes of the god decree sparkled, each one resonating with each other.

The feeling this scene gave off was as if the god decree had been resurrected!

It formed a sharp contrast with the three withered yellow god decrees lying down beside it. Those three god decrees appeared dark and gloomy, as if they would turn to dust at any moment.

“Lin Ming… he revived the old God Sovereign’s god decree!”

Someone was able to see the essential difference. The god decree that Lin Ming repaired seemed entirely brand new.

Compared to the celestial race’s three god decrees, Lin Ming’s repaired god decree had even greater levels of energy!

“How could… this be…”

A celestial powerhouse cried out.

With any reasoning, Lin Ming being able to repair the god decrees should have been a major accomplishment worthy of all the ancient remnant races celebrating. But in this situation, the celestials weren’t able to summon any joy at all.

“Great!” Lin Ming had overdrawn his strength and propped himself up on the black stone table. He passed the god decree to the old God Sovereign.

As the old God Sovereign took the god decree in his hands, his face was full of smiles. As he looked at Lin Ming, his eyes were filled with praise, appreciation, and love.

He could feel that the god decree he passed Lin Ming had undergone a massive change.

“Good! Very good!”

The old God Sovereign loudly acclaimed.

At this time, the other god race martial artists also sent out their divine senses together, probing the god decree that Lin Ming had repaired. They were all left dumbfounded.

Even the Great Elder that had criticized Lin Ming before had completely shut up.

In the world of martial artists, strength was all!

With strength, one naturally obtained respect.

“This is incredible. My god race has many ordinary True Divinity level god decrees left. If they could be repaired by Lin Ming, just what scene would that be!”

A god decree drawn up by a True Divinity, if brand new, for example the one that Lin Ming had just repaired, if that were activated by a peak Empyrean then that was the same as the all-out attack of a True Divinity level powerhouse.

It could instantly kill a peak Empyrean of the same level. At the very least, their opponent would be severely wounded and lose all combat strength. Then, they could even be captured!

The significance of this was far too great!

It had to be known that the most threatening enemy to the ancient remnant races was not True Divinities like the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, but peak Empyreans!

The truth was that in this war, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had never fought at all.

This was because the primal god race still had the Asura god decrees left behind by the Asura Road Master! If the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign were to personally come, then the primal god race would be willing to take out all their Asura god decrees and bombard the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign with them. If they could kill the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign using such a method, then the world would be purified.

But if a peak Empyrean came, using an Asura god decree on them was a waste, and using other god decrees was useless. This was a worrying situation!

However, with the god decrees that Lin Ming repaired, restoring them to a brand new state, none of this was a problem anymore.

Chapter 1879 – The Celestials’ Concessions

Realizing the function that Lin Ming’s ability to repair the god decrees would have for the war situation, every god race Empyrean’s eyes began to shine.

At this time, even if those like the Great Elder were envious of Lin Ming, they were also excited. This was a monumental matter that concerned the life or death of their race!

Compared to the survival of their people, the interests of an individual were secondary.

“Lin Ming, did repairing the god decree cause any bodily harm to you?”

The old God Sovereign asked. He was worried that doing so had caused Lin Ming to overdraw on his life.

Lin Ming shook his head. “I’ve just used up a bit of my energy and soul force. I should be able to fully recover after several days.”

In the presence of so many people, Lin Ming extended the required recovery time a little.

The truth was that he only needed one or two days to restore himself, and if the old God Sovereign helped him then the time period needed would be even shorter.

“Great! Then you can sit in meditation and restore yourself. Afterwards I will give you another god decree for you to repair. Once we collect three, we will open the Asura forbidden land. This is a great favor that you have done for my god race; we shall never forget this!”

The old God Sovereign’s face lit up. With his usual demeanor, he rarely lost his calm like this.

“Your Majesty God Sovereign has no need to speak so seriously. The god race’s war with the saints originally concerns the fate of my human race. If junior helps the god race to the full extent of my abilities, that is also helping my own people. It’s something that should be done to begin with.”

Lin Ming’s voice was humble and without the least bit of trying to take credit. This point caused many god race powerhouses to develop a favorable impression towards Lin Ming. According to common sense, if Lin Ming were able to repair god decrees for the god race then he should also be able to propose any condition he wished; this was entirely within reason.

“Ningchu, Legion King, Skylift, Diwuhen! The four of you prepare yourselves! After Lin Ming repairs the three god decrees you will then repair the Chain of Calamity! With the Laws contained within the god decrees and the joint energies of your four, there shouldn’t be any problems repairing it!”

The old God Sovereign immediately spat out the names or titles of four Empyreans. These four Empyreans were the strongest within the entire primal god race. And amongst them, Diwuhen was the strongest but also the youngest.

The four Empyreans stepped forwards as one, respectfully standing behind the old God Sovereign.

Amongst the four of them, three were the old God Sovereign’s disciples.

Seeing this situation, To Bagui could no longer remain silent.

The worst possible situation had occurred – the old God Sovereign was planning to cast aside their celestial race!

In terms of inheritance lineage, the truth was that the celestials were also part of the Asura Road Master’s lineage. The difference was that 10 billion years ago, the celestials were nothing but a vassal race, a minor branch to the god race.

If they could enter the Asura forbidden land, that was naturally a tremendous advantage to the celestials.

But now, he watched as the god race members busily gathered around Lin Ming, as if the celestials had nothing to do with this matter.

“Your Majesty God Sovereign!”

To Bagui anxiously shouted.

“Oh? What matter does the Battle Sovereign have to say?” The old God Sovereign smiled, his expression filled with meaning.

The winds and the tides could change at a moment’s notice. The celestials had been aggressively pushing the god race, but now the roles had been overturned. Now it was the celestials that were struggling to find a foothold. And, this ridiculous change was all brought about by a junior; it was simply incredible.

To Bagui glanced at Lin Ming with a strange complexion. He said, “Your Majesty God Sovereign, there is no need for us to play around with words. My celestial race desires two spots. Any conditions Your Majesty wishes can be considered.”

To Bagui said, getting straight to the point. He was already prepared for a massive hemorrhage.

The truth was that the celestials and god race were brother races. With the great calamity before them, the two could be said to be dependent on each other. If uniting as one wasn’t enough to win the war, if they were to even fight, that would only mean defeat would come that much quicker.

It was impossible that the old God Sovereign didn’t understand this point. To Bagui didn’t want to waste his time with idle banter.

From looking at the allocation of resources alone, the god race only needed four spots; anyone else entering would be a waste. At the same time, what the celestials needed the most were two spots. For this reason they were willing to pay a deep price. After all, even blood brothers had to settle accounts between themselves.

“I want two of the three god decrees.”

The old God Sovereign said, pointing towards the three upper True Divinity god decrees laid in a row.

He didn’t intend to take advantage of someone when they were down. Before, the celestials had wanted to use these three god decrees to exchange for three spots, coming out to one spot per god decree.

Now that the celestials wanted two spots, the old God Sovereign demanded only two god decrees. This was a completely justified request.

“Thank you…” To Bagui said, feeling ashamed in his heart. His voice lacked energy. He didn’t know if Lin Ming had the ability to repair upper True Divinity god decrees, but if he did then their power would truly be heaven-defying!

After thinking for a little, he said, “I would like to ask Little Friend Lin here to repair the god decrees of my people. I wonder if…”

Because Lin Ming had exposed a part of his strength, To Bagui became increasingly respectful when he spoke of Lin Ming.

“This is something you can discuss directly with Lin Ming. I have no right to make decisions for him.” The old God Sovereign smiled, looking towards Lin Ming.

For a time, the eyes of the celestial martial artists turned towards Lin Ming.

“Little Friend Lin…”

To Bagui hesitated. As the number two figure within the entire celestial race, he eagerly yet helplessly looked at Lin Ming, as if begging with his eyes.

Lin Ming calmly responded, “I can naturally repair god decrees for the celestials, but… if I were to do so I would also have other conditions. We can discuss them in detail when the time comes.”

“Naturally… my celestial race won’t have Little Friend Lin help for nothing.”

To Bagui smiled as he spoke. But as this sight fell in Smokeless’ eyes, it made her feel uncomfortable.

The celestials were an ancient race and they had a once glorious history. Even though they had declined in the present era, the bloodline of the celestials was still not something that the spiritas, humans, or saints could hope to compare with. Thus, the celestials had a pride that belonged to them alone, a pride that was engraved into their bones!

But now, To Bagui as a peak Empyrean was actually speaking so politely to Lin Ming, a Holy Lord. And this Lin Ming didn’t even seem to be appreciating such kindness. This made Smokeless feel ill to her stomach.

“This boy… I have no idea what lucky chance he obtained that he is able to repair the god decrees, but he actually reaches for a yard after taking an inch…” Smokeless indignantly thought. “What a pity that his cultivation is too low. Otherwise, if he and I were at the same cultivation realm I would definitely have challenged him!”

Currently, Smokeless wasn’t convinced by Lin Ming at all. But she didn’t reveal her emotions, and instead only icily glared at Lin Ming.

At this time, Lin Ming had already moved towards a quiet room; he intended to meditate and restore himself.

…………………..

Several days passed. Lin Ming had repaired three god decrees!

And on this day, it was time to repair the Chain of Calamity!

The old God Sovereign’s black pupils sparkled with a mystic power, causing the surrounding palace to tremble in tune with him.

The air hummed. The massive pillars that rose up all over the palace emitted massive beams of energy, weaving together to form a pure energy space. From afar, it looked like a giant translucent crystal, isolating out everything with absolute certainty.

Repairing the Chain of Calamity was a monumental event that couldn’t receive any disturbances at all.

A crystalline enchantment shrouded down, covering the four strongest god race and celestial powerhouses, sheltering them from any outside influence.

Since the celestials had decided to join in, the people who would repair the Chain of Calamity had also changed. With the help of the celestial powerhouses, the chances of success were much higher.

Lin Ming stood at the side, his eyes gazing into the spherical energy crystal.

The four powerhouses stood above the Chain of Calamity. They held the three god decrees that Lin Ming had repaired in their hands.

Each god decree contained dense strands of the 33 Heavens’ Great Dao aura. This incomparably pure aura gushed out endlessly, making the hearts of those watching quicken.

Bang!

A god race Empyrean was the first to move. Blood shot out from the pores of his arms.

This was the pure god race bloodline. It contained the aura of endless years, standing testimony to the primal god race’s once glorious civilization.

The blood bloomed with incandescent light. In the midst of this light, one could hear dragons roaring and phoenixes keening.

Even though Lin Ming was standing a hundred feet away, he still felt a pressure as heavy as a mountain exude from that blood, making him feel oppressed.

“This is the pure bloodline strength of the god race… incredible, it far surpasses the bloodline inherited by the saints…”

Lin Ming’s eyes fixated on the blood, unblinking. His soul force surged within him and the surrounding pressure weakened by a great deal. The bloodline power released by a peak Empyrean was difficult for even an ordinary World King to withstand.

The pure drop of god race blood slowly floated in the air, as if it were an ancient and solemn star shining in the skies. It emitted a distant and boundless strength before hurtling into a god decree.

After the god decree absorbed the god race Empyrean’s blood essence, a crimson glow lit up the world. The mystic power of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws within turned into runes that rumbled like massive tumbling mountains.

Faintly, one could see towering and hulking god kings appear, sitting on the runes, their pupils shooting out a terrifying light even as their monstrous blood vitality raged within them.

The god decree emitted a phantasmal voice that seemed to come from times long past, as if the god decree were coming to life.

Soon after, the other powerhouses followed suit. They offered their own bloodline power to blend into the remaining god decrees.

The god decrees shined with an increasingly bright light, as if they were exploding stars. The entire grand hall was wrapped up in a blinding luminosity.

This was the power of a True Divinity spirit treasure. When Empyrean spirit treasures were born they would often summon heavenly tribulation, much less a True Divinity spirit treasure.

Light completely blinded Lin Ming for a moment. But, Lin Ming didn’t need to see with his eyes at all. Rather, he could sense that within the light, a terrifying amount of energy was being formed and destroyed along with all sorts of sparkling runes…

This white light shined for an entire day and night before slowly dimming down.

As the white light vanished, the energy sphere also faded away.

The four god race and celestial powerhouses were pale. Their auras had diminished compared to the start.

They all sat on the ground and began meditating, restoring themselves.

At this time, a faint sound rang through the air, as if it came from the world itself. It was remote and mysterious.

A snow white lotus flower flowed within these sound waves, blooming in the void.

At the furthest edges of the pitch black skies, a mysterious black road appeared, stretching all the way to the grand hall.

At the end of this great road, the Chain of Calamity glistened with endless power. It was wrapped in a mysterious aura as it suddenly appeared in front of everyone.

It was impossible to unravel the mysteries within.

“A True Divinity magic tool has been reborn. An auspicious sign appears.” On the old God Sovereign’s aged face, a happy smile appeared.

The Chain of Calamity had been repaired. Now, all that was left was to open the Asura forbidden land.

Perhaps the Asura forbidden land would offer them a chance to turn the tide in this great calamity!

Chapter 1880 – Entering the Forbidden Land

Ten days later, the Empyreans who helped repair the Chain of Calamity had fully recovered. Lin Ming had also restored himself to his peak state.

Today, the Asura forbidden land would be opened.

The list of people to enter the Asura forbidden land had also been finalized. They were – To Bagui, Smokeless, Lin Ming, Shenku, Lanlu, and Diwuhen.

The last four people had been personally chosen by the old God Sovereign. Smokeless didn’t need to be mentioned. Just the Battle Sovereign To Bagui was faintly the number one master of the entire celestial race, but he still had plenty of potential remaining. He was one of the main pillars in resisting this great calamity!

The old God Sovereign led the way. His right hand was held out in front, the Chain of Calamity hanging on the end of his index finger. The Chain of Calamity emitted a misty light that caused the surrounding space to change.

Somewhere in the far off distance, it was as if the end of space and time existed there. Thundering rumbles and vibrating hums continued without end.

This sort of shaking was like the ringing of a bell.

The fluctuations were like a tide. Everyone could feel the powerful fluctuations. These fluctuations even passed through the void, causing surrounding stars to resonate with it.

Within the white grand hall, the primal god race and celestial powerhouses were excited upon seeing this. They all peered deep into the endless void.

Although they couldn’t see anything and could only sense the aging universe and infinite darkness, this couldn’t stop their eyes from heating with enthusiasm.

“After the Chain of Calamity was repaired, the Asura forbidden zone already started to resonate with it.”

An old god race powerhouse said. In the history of the god race, the Asura forbidden land had been opened less than a handful of times. There were many True Divinities who didn’t have the good fortune to see it, and those present had never imagined they would be fortunate enough to live during a time when the Asura forbidden zone would be opened and personally bear witness to it.

“The Asura forbidden land is the holy land of my people. Unfortunately, this holy land will only appear when the god race stands on the precipice of life or death…

“In the past, many outstanding god race members that became True Divinities weren’t lucky enough to enter the Asura forbidden land. But now that it has been opened, my race is already declining and those chosen to enter barely meet the qualifications…”

The god race powerhouse deeply sighed with emotion.

“It’s time…”

The old God Sovereign’s robes whipped about around him. The light projecting from the Chain of Calamity grew ever bright, wrapping everyone within it.

In the next moment, Lin Ming felt the heavens and earth change positions as a spell of dizziness overtook him. As he opened his eyes again he could see that he had arrived in a mysterious realm.

This world was hot to the point where even he found it unbearable.

Looking around, the surroundings were empty. Only at the central region was there a surging mass of lava.

This lava continued without end, seeming as if it were larger than a great world.

Flames occasionally gushed into the air. Each plume of flame was like a burning star that roared into the world.

This sight awed the heart.

“Just what kind of lava is this? How terrifying, even my skin is finding it hard to withstand being baked by the heat…” Lin Ming mumbled, shocked, as he looked at the blazing flames.

The Chain of Calamity hovered above this mass of lava, releasing a mystical sound.

And the flows of lava also emitted shockwaves that stirred up an inexhaustible amount of lava. The sounds echoed into the air, resonating with the sound coming from the Chain of Calamity.

The movements within the flowing lava became increasingly intense. Waves of the dao appeared like twisting dragons – the Great Dao of Freezing Cold, the Great Dao of Deep Water, the Great Dao of the Heavens and Earth…

As these dao fluctuations appeared, the surrounding lava was frozen, swallowed, or neutralized with some other method. Soon, this area began to rapidly clear.

Rumble rumble rumble.

Slowly, as more dao fluctuations gushed out, waves of chilling and withering aura shot outwards. At the deepest depths of the lava, a vast mysterious space was revealed.

The entrance was dark and deep. Lin Ming could feel something familiar coming from it; the power of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws was overflowing from within.

The Asura forbidden zone, an ancient ruin left behind by the Asura Road Master, had finally been opened!

Lin Ming felt increasingly sure that the third emperor jade he was searching for was located in this ancient ruin.

“This feeling, could it be the ‘fate’ that the Asura Road Master spoke of? If so, then I must obtain this emperor jade of fate no matter what.”

Lin Ming gripped his fists. To him, the most valuable treasure within the Asura forbidden zone was the emperor jade of fate. It was something that involved the complete inheritance of the Asura Road Master. And with the complete inheritance of the Asura Road Master, Lin Ming could become that much stronger to fight the invasion of the saints!

“Enter.”

The old God Sovereign’s profound eyes touched over everyone’s faces. He waved his sleeves and an enormous strength caught hold of everyone. Lin Ming and the others were immediately sent tumbling into that vast space.

“Mm?”

After entering the Asura forbidden land, the moment that Lin Ming felt solid ground he couldn’t help but be surprised.

After all, he had gone to the Asura Road. That world could be considered as overflowing with life, countless existences freely wandering about. But in the world he was in now, there was only a pale yellow star above him that emitted a faint glow.

The surrounding light was dim. Dark gray clouds piled up high in the skies, locking out the light and casting the world into an eternal twilight.

This was a dead world. The feeling it gave off was that of a great world having reached the end of its existence, soon to collapse into nothing!

In everyone’s eyes, they could see giant obelisks rise into the heavens like towering mountains.

The Tomb of the Left King Longya, the Tomb of Heaven’s Son Yongun, the Tomb of God King Luho…

“Left King Longya was a peerless genius from almost 10 billion years ago. Afterwards he disappeared without a trace, but he actually died here…”

“Heaven’s Son Yongun was rumored to have been the strongest peerless genius of my race in ancient times. He had high hopes of following the Asura Road Master’s steps…”

The celestial and primal god race powerhouses were stirred to emotion as they looked upon these graces in front of them.

Those that died here were all once world-shaking existences of the primal god race.

It had to be known that they existed billions or even 10 billion years ago. Even through the unimaginably long river of time, they were still recorded here as before. It was obvious from this how strong they had been in life.

As a martial artist walked upon their own road, travelling their own journeys, they would often regard the great existences of the past as their own goal.

Now that they saw these once fabled characters quietly turned to grave soil in front of them, fading from the world, they felt 10,000 different emotions cross their hearts.

The passing of the years was the most terrifying weapon of all!

The tombstones that marked the graves were ominous, like mountains that pressed upon the hearts of those present. It was as if these tombstones were trying to show them that the destiny of the god race and celestials had already reached its natural end.

Strong winds howled, as sharp and grating as knives as they grinded against the rocks on the ground.

Although these strange winds wouldn’t injure these people, it still made them intuitively feel that this land was far bleaker and more dangerous than they had thought.

However, those that could enter here were all individuals with great wisdom and courage. Their hearts of martial arts were as solid as stone, almost without the slightest flaw.

Although this scene was depressing, it couldn’t shake their confidence.

Suddenly, from deep within the earth, an icy cold strength quietly spread out.

The sandy and rocky earth began to frost over at a speed visible to the eyes.

“Be careful.” Battle Sovereign To Bagui said.

A giant figure suddenly leapt out, its body was miles long. It hurtled into the group of people.

Lin Ming’s eyes shined with a sharp light as he immediately discerned what it was. This monster that leapt out was similar to a vicious beast, but it was invisible and intangible, nothing but a mass of shadows.

And in the shadows were two glowing red eyes, making it seem bizarre and horrifying.

Its strength was majestic and razor sharp. As soon as it appeared it lashed out, causing a shockingly deep fissure to be torn through the ground.

This sort of dreadful momentum that seemed as if it could split apart everything left everyone feeling chilled.

Within the group of people, a slim figure rushed out. Her hair flapped behind her like a black waterfall and her two eyes were like brilliant moons, emitting a dazzling coldness.

Her fingers flickered as she produced several seals. Red wings flashed behind her, breaking open the void as she collided with the shadow beast.

Bang!

A powerful shockwave blasted out and black blood spewed into the skies.

Even though the celestials’ proud elite Smokeless seemed delicate, she was able to erupt with an astonishing degree of strength.

She was like a god king that descended to the world. Her skin, flesh, and blood exuded a blinding brilliance. Her fists struck out so hard that even the air in front of her shook, as if she were some invincible being.

The horrifying shadow beast that seemed as if it could tear apart all actually cracked apart beneath her fists. It began to wail as its body disintegrated.

The shadows exploded at once. The many dark moon-shaped runes that covered its body dispersed into the air, even as they began to break apart beneath the furious strength.

With a loud bang, the massive shadow beast had been dissolved into countless runes that scattered into the world.

This monster was originally a being formed by a Law force field.

Seeing this, Lin Ming’s eyebrows shot up. He had clearly seen that Smokeless had used her body, in particular her fists, to commune with the world. She saved up a tremendous amount of the Great Dao’s primal power in order to make such an earth-shaking blow.

The intensity of her mortal body left one flabbergasted.

And the celestials were similar to the god race in that their essence, energy, and divine were all powerful. If Smokeless’ mortal body had been cultivated to such a degree, what heights did her ‘energy’ and ‘divine’ reach?

As Lin Ming observed Smokeless, he faintly felt that what she excelled in the most was not bodily strength but perhaps ‘energy’ or ‘divine’.

If she only used her mortal body to fight, then she was simply trying to hide her true talents.

“Truly worthy of being the ally of the primal god race. The celestials are also the favored children of the heavens and earth.”

Lin Ming exclaimed in his mind.

But at this time, after the strange shadow was eliminated, Smokeless’ lightning sharp gaze swept over Lin Ming, a light provocation within it.

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. He could see a slight smile on Smokeless’ lips.

Before repairing the Chain of Calamity, Lin Ming had stepped into the limelight by displaying his skills. Afterwards, even the celestials’ Battle Sovereign To Bagui had to speak to Lin Ming in a humble tone.

This had left Smokeless feeling ill in her heart.

But now, she was able to give vent to these feelings. This was because in the Asura forbidden land, one’s progress clearly depended on one’s martial strength. And in terms of her own strength, Smokeless was absolutely confident in herself!

By depending on her mortal body alone she was able to erupt with such strength. If she exhausted all of her hidden cards, then with her Great World King cultivation she would be able to protect herself and flee against the weakest of Empyreans.

“No wonder the Battle Sovereign was willing to pay such a deep price to bring Smokeless into the Asura forbidden land.”

Diwuhen nodded from beside To Bagui. His status wasn’t much different from To Bagui’s.

“Smokeless’ strength is far beyond this, let’s slowly watch. If this road isn’t too dangerous, then let’s not help. Allow the younger generation to clear the way.”

To Bagui folded his arms across his chest, a smile on his face. As he spoke, his gaze, either by design or accident, swept over Lin Ming.

In truth, there were only two of the so-called ‘younger generation’ here – Smokeless and Lin Ming.

Chapter 1881 – Tricks

The god race and celestials were brother races, but at the same time they also competed with each other. Previously, the celestials had been humbled and paid a sufficient price to barely obtain two spots to enter the Asura forbidden land. Naturally, they were tamping down the grievances in their heart.

After entering the Asura forbidden land with great difficulty, To Bagui hoped that his celestial race would be able to have proud results here.

To Bagui weighed his own strength and felt that he wasn’t much stronger than the god race’s Diwuhen, thus he placed his hopes on Smokeless instead. He hoped that Smokeless would be able to rely on her extraordinary talent to dazzle the world within the Asura forbidden land and obtain the greatest lucky chance here.

As for juniors, there was only Smokeless and Lin Ming.

These two people naturally had to be compared with each other.

Woosh woosh woosh!

From all directions, a number of shadow birds flew forth, blocking out the world. They rumbled towards the group like endless bolts of black lightning.

Now, it wasn’t just Smokeless that acted. To Bagui also moved, however, he didn’t kill these shadow birds but instead casually cut open space and split them up.

His intention was to help temper Smokeless. Isolating some of the shadow birds away was to prevent Smokeless from being surrounded on all sides and suffering too many dangers.

Ca!

Divine light surged out. Smokeless displayed her mighty supernatural powers. The power of divinity erupted from her body as her two slender palms emitted a brilliant light.

Her palms contained an inconceivable strength, as if they were the sharpest weapons in the world. With a slice of her palm, a massive tract of the void was torn apart like paper, causing an entire part of the sky to be cleared out.

The overwhelming shadow birds were sundered by a single strike of Smokeless’ palms, disintegrating into countless runes!

The god race Empyreans didn’t help, instead allowing Smokeless to do as she pleased. Her attacks were a work of art; it was hard to imagine that such a formidable strength was contained within her delicate body.

Kacha!

Three shadow birds were cut apart. Smokeless’ eyes shined with the light of six stars, as heavy as crashing mountains. All threats were completely blocked and broken by her.

During this process, Lin Ming simply watched from the side, carefully analyzing the Law runes that constituted the shadow birds even as he simultaneously appraised Smokeless’ strength.

Smokeless indeed had the capital to attack the True Divinity realm.

Chi!

With a light sound, the last shadow bird was shattered into runes. Smokeless drew back her powers, taking a light breath and remaining in high spirits as before.

She walked away from the battlefield. As she passed Lin Ming, she glanced at him.

A beautiful voice suddenly wafted into Lin Ming’s ears.

“This Asura forbidden land is a place to gain experience and temper yourself. Will you only look and not do anything? Then isn’t your trip here in vain?”

Smokeless loftily said. Lin Ming faintly smiled, “Very well. When I watched Miss Smokeless fight those shadow birds, I was also able to deduce some combat methods.”

Lin Ming’s words left the Empyreans surprised.

Smokeless was also a little stunned. In all fairness, Lin Ming’s cultivation was slightly low. For him to fight these shadow creatures was likely a bit too difficult.

Smokeless had intended to only taunt Lin Ming a little but she didn’t think that he would agree. To have him fight these shadow creatures was a tad unfair.

“There’s no need to be brave. You might end up injuring yourself.” Smokeless said. Although it seemed as if she were mocking him again, the truth was that there wasn’t any malice behind her words.

Lin Ming smiled in response. He fiddled with a symbol paper in his hands. After those shadow creatures had exploded, he had gathered their runes.

In the end, these shadow creatures were nothing but spontaneous manifestations of energy released from the array formation of the Asura forbidden land. They were not worth fearing at all.

As everyone moved on, many of them looked forwards to how Lin Ming’s performance would be.

Diwuhen kept his mind locked onto Lin Ming at all times. Taking care of him was an important mission that the old God Sovereign had personally handed down to him. Of everyone present, Lin Ming was the weakest and the Asura forbidden land still contained perilous dangers. As someone able to repair god decrees, Diwuhen couldn’t allow Lin Ming to fall into any danger.

As the group walked several miles forwards, dangers appeared once more.

This time it was no longer birds, but a massive demon wolf. From the aura of this demon wolf it was clearly far beyond the birds from before.

Its blood red eyes stared at Lin Ming and the others, overflowing with killing intent.

“Be careful!”

Diwuhen cautioned. The one to deal with this demon wolf should have been Lin Ming, but he felt that Lin Ming might find this task difficult so he reminded him.

Roar!

The demon wolf howled and rushed forwards like lightning.

In this instant, the Battle Sovereign and Smokeless’ pupils both shrank as they stared at Lin Ming!

By any reasoning, this demon wolf’s power and momentum was not something a Holy Lord realm genius could deal with. Smokeless believed that if she were at Lin Ming’s boundary, she wouldn’t be a match for this demon wolf.

This was the disparity brought by absolute strength!

If Lin Ming didn’t fight, he was well within his rights.

Smokeless was already prepared to help. But, the demon wolf was too fast. As it hurtled forwards, Lin Ming had already stepped up, standing in front of the group.

“Lin Ming!”

Diwuhen erupted with energy. If Lin Ming wasn’t a match for this demon wolf then he would immediately rescue him!

But in this brief instant, Lin Ming suddenly pressed out his palm and patted down on the demon wolf’s head!

“What!?”

Everyone was shocked. Lin Ming didn’t take out a weapon but instead planned to use his bare hand to deal with the demon wolf!

Even Smokeless rarely frontally collided with enemies when using her palm. Rather, she attacked from the sides.

But in that moment, Diwuhen discovered that Lin Ming’s hand was shining with a pale golden light.

Was that the light of Laws?

Clang!

For a time, the deafening ring of a bell thundered outwards. Above Lin Ming’s palm, a massive golden light erupted, followed by the energy of countless Laws. It formed a giant wall of sacred writings that blocked him off against the demon wolf!

Bang!

The demon wolf crashed into the golden wall of sacred writings and emitted a pained howl!

“God decree?”

Diwuhen, the Battle Sovereign, Smokeless, and the others were all shocked. So Lin Ming had been holding a symbol paper in his hands.

The moment that this symbol paper was shot out of Lin Ming’s palm it exploded, forming a golden wall of mantras that blocked the demon wolf.

“This symbol paper… is the one Lin Ming was holding just a moment ago!”

Diwuhen remembered. When Smokeless killed off a massive number of shadow creatures, the others had been watching from the side. Lin Ming was no exception. The only difference was that he held a symbol paper in his hands and collected the scattered runes released by the exploded shadow creatures. From the start, no one cared. They only thought that Lin Ming was collecting these runes to do some research when he returned. But they never thought that after an incense stick of time, the runes Lin Ming gathered could display such a terrifying strength!

As the demon wolf struck the golden wall of sacred writings, it also suffered severe injuries and was dazed for a moment. Lin Ming was quick of hand and eye. He quickly stepped forwards, the Law runes shining in his hands as he repeatedly slapped the demon wolf.

Each one of his attacks hit the weak point in the Laws of the demon wolf’s body!

The demon wolf was originally a spontaneous manifestation of Laws and energy that had seeped out from the Asura forbidden zone’s great array formation. This demon wolf and its body of Laws couldn’t be called solid and could even be said to be filled with holes. Simply put, there was no need for a melee of any sort. As long as he could break apart the rough Law structures then it would wither away and die by itself.

Peng!

With an explosive sound, the demon wolf blew apart, its body scattering into runes.

Lin Ming gripped a new symbol paper and waved his hand, gathering up all of the runes and sealing them into the symbol paper.

“This is…”

Seeing this, the martial artists present were left speechless.

The demon wolf had been destroyed this easily?

To them, this demon wolf wasn’t considered anything at all. But to a Holy Lord realm martial artist, it was a terrifying existence.

But Lin Ming didn’t seem to use any energy at all to kill the demon wolf. Moreover, he gathered the runes from when it died and exploded so that he could use them again.

This was just merciless!

“He absorbed the runes into the symbol paper and turned it into a god decree…”

An Empyrean said with disbelief. The powerhouses of the god race and celestials all had amazing eyesight. Although they didn’t understand the Asura Laws, they were able to see that Lin Ming didn’t frontally defeat the demon wolf by himself but had relied on certain tricks to do so.

This couldn’t be considered Lin Ming’s true strength.

“You… just where did you learn the inheritance of god decrees? Will you only use god decrees? You cannot rely on your own strength to fight?”

Smokeless said with a flushed face, her words lacking some energy.

When this demon wolf appeared, she didn’t expect Lin Ming to fulfill his words. In fact, she was a Great World King, and her competing like this with a middle Holy Lord realm martial artist was just senseless.

Smokeless only wanted Lin Ming to suffer a little loss once and consider it done, but she didn’t think he would display his skills once again and steal the limelight.

Naturally, Smokeless felt suffocated once again.

“If I have a way to easily handle my enemies, why would I choose a method that requires more work?”

Lin Ming rhetorically asked. Smokeless felt as if something had lodged in her throat.

She could only keep her mouth shut.

Diwuhen smiled. “Little Brother Lin, you obtained the true legacy of the god decrees? Then in this Asura forbidden zone, you should be like a fish in water. There are many dangers here you can use the power of Laws to avoid, right?”

Diwuhen’s thoughts were what the other Empyreans were thinking. If so, then Lin Ming had profited greatly.

Lin Ming shook his head, “Senior Wuhen must be joking with me. How could it be so easy? What I’ve studied is only the tip of the iceberg when it comes to the Asura Laws. Only at certain times can they display miraculous effects.

“Whether it was the shadow creatures or demon wolf that just appeared, they are all formed from energy that has leaked out from the Asura forbidden land’s great array formation and then spontaneously evolved into monsters. Their Law structures are simple and filled with hundreds of flaws. If I break open the Laws within their bodies I can naturally kill them. But, if I faced the true Asura array formation, my superficial skills would be of no use at all. I can only honestly continue forwards as the Asura Road Master intended, without skipping any steps.”

Lin Ming’s words caused the Empyreans to bow. Indeed, if they faced the complete array formation laid down by the Asura Road Master, then everything Lin Ming showed so far would be of no use. If Lin Ming followed them he would also have to accept the test of the array formation in a fair manner.

Chapter 1883 – Ancient Geniuses

Peerless geniuses from the ancient era, what kind of characters would they be?

It was far too distant a time, and they could no longer be judged. In the various ancient books, it was widely recognized that the ancient era was when the martial arts civilization was at its most glorious. The quality and quantity of geniuses that existed back then far outstripped the present era.

Thus, Lin Ming increasingly anticipated this battle.

“I never thought that I would be able to step into the array formation laid down by the Asura Road Master and cross over 10 billion years to fight geniuses from the ancient past.

“And my opponent’s cultivation is actually lower than mine, at the early Holy Lord realm.”

Lin Ming looked at the youth who gripped a heavy sword within the Cold Ice Mirror, a strange feeling in his heart.

The Cold Ice Mirror determined the cultivation of this virtual opponent based upon the intruder’s cultivation.

Over the years, although Lin Ming had fought those at a lower boundary than him, it had usually been as one-sided massacres. It had never been as today, where he faced a single opponent who had a lower cultivation than him, who he considered a worthy opponent that could even arouse his interest.

“So these are ancient geniuses from 10 billion years ago, and their cultivations are even lower than ours. This Cold Ice Mirror doesn’t seem to think much of us…”

To Bagui crossed his arms against his chest. As he stared at his opponent in the mirror, his aura began to surge and he gathered his potential!

Although his words seemed casual, the truth was that To Bagui didn’t dare to lower his guard in the slightest.

“Ancient geniuses, huh? I’ve long been wanting to experience them. Today is perfect to do so!”

Diwuhen’s eyes flashed with excitement. After all, even if these ancient geniuses were a small boundary lower than them, they were more than enough to arouse their fighting spirit.

“Let me take the lead.” At this time, a god race Empyrean stepped forth.

“Shenku…” Diwuhen’s eyes glittered.

Shenku waved his hand, laughing as he said, “I will explore the way. Let me take a good look at just what sort of strength these ancient geniuses have compared to us.”

As Shenku spoke he tightly gripped his fists, explosive crackling sounds emitting from them.

In the group of six, his talent was the lowest.

However, he was still an outstanding character amongst Empyreans. He had a confidence that was his alone!

Shenku stepped into the Cold Ice Mirror. The mirror gently shivered before swallowing in Shenku.

Shenku’s opponent was a black-caped youth; his cultivation was a lower Empyrean.

Although this virtual opponent appeared as a youth, if they were a real person they would definitely be at least 10,000 years old. Normally speaking, a young Empyrean would appear youthful because their cultivation rapidly advanced.

Hu – hu – hu!

In the Cold Ice Mirror, Shenku and the black-caped youth both spouted out countless flames from their flesh and blood. The aura of the Truefire Great Dao flowed out from them, sweeping across the world.

The two of them were both fire-attribute martial artists.

Moreover, they used the power of divinity.

The so-called power of divinity was a fusion of astral essence, true essence, and spirit essence, three different kinds of origin energy.

The fire that was catalyzed by the power of divinity could burn down the void.

Bang!

The two figures were surrounded by raging flames. Two brilliant suns smashed into each other!

In the world within the mirror’s surface, no matter how terrifying the fighting was, it wouldn’t affect the outside world.

Moreover, the mirror surface world was boundless beyond compare. It was more than enough for a powerhouse to display the full extent of their strength.

Inside the deep surface, Lin Ming saw flames erupt everywhere, fists and feet blazing about.

Every collision could pierce through a world and scatter the nebulous clouds.

Energy waves swept out in all directions like raging tsunamis, wreaking havoc wherever they went.

The fight was intense. Within the Cold Ice Mirror, Shenku gradually paled.

Purple flames suddenly spouted out from his nose. As they appeared, even the void was pierced through. The surface of the Cold Ice Mirror also faintly distorted.

Every wisp of purple flame turned into a massive purple bird that cut through space, hurtling towards the virtual opponent together.

Unexpectedly, the black-caped youth also spouted out purple flames from his nose. The power of these flames was faintly higher than those released by Shenku.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Another fierce round of combat began.

Shenku was forced back again and again. His physical strength was slowly being consumed, but as for that black-caped youth, the more he fought the more savage he became. The youth’s body burned like a sun and the power behind his strikes became increasingly wild and brutal.

“Hah!”

Shenku roared. Flames erupted from his body. He shot towards the black-caped youth like a meteor!

In the surging explosions, the black-caped youth was forced back dozens of miles. His body fluttered backwards like a piece of paper until he finally stabilized himself.

However, upon seeing this, Diwuhen, To Bagui, and the others all fell silent.

In that strike just now, Shenku had held the upper hand. But, the truth was that he had used the mightiest supernatural power that his bloodline could give him. This move could only be used a single time and it also consumed a tremendous amount of life force.

Even so, he hadn’t been able to injure his opponent but had only sent him flying away.

The opponent’s inner energy flow wasn’t disturbed at all. His blood vitality was still vibrant and there was the feeling that he could still fight as intensely as he did!

In comparison, Shenku had used up 60-70% of his strength, unable to continue for much longer. The disparity was clear!

Woosh!

The black-caped youth attacked once more. Shenku barely resisted the attack. This time, the truefire that surged from his bloodline had dimmed by a great deal.

His figure paused in the air. The flames around Shenku turned into wisps that resembled strange-looking tentacles that wanted to pierce through the virtual opponent.

However, as the youth saw this, a sly smile appeared on his face, as if he had a mind of his own.

From the youth’s flesh and blood, runes shined bright, forming a brilliant curtain of light that blocked out all the flames.

Peng!

With an explosive ring, Shenku gave a stuffy cough as his body was sent blasting away, directly ejected from the mirror world where he fell onto the floor!

Shenku, defeated!

Diwuhen had been quietly counting the time in his mind. That battle just now had only lasted for 20-30 breaths.

But, the requirements to pass the mirror world’s test were to defeat the opponent or last for 1000 breaths of time.

20-30 breaths of time to 1000 breaths of time, this disparity was a little too great.

“So difficult!”

Diwuhen’s complexion was ugly. As for Shenku, he had a bitter and rueful look on his face.

His opponent’s cultivation boundary had even been lower than his own.

The truth was he had already expected that this black-caped youth wouldn’t be easy to deal with. He wouldn’t be surprised even if he lost. But, he hadn’t expected that he would lose so miserably.

The others also felt awed in their hearts. The geniuses of ancient times were truly terrifying!

“Are you alright?” Diwuhen asked with concern.

Shenku shook his head, saying, “This place is for gaining experience; there shouldn’t be any life-threatening dangers.”

After being kicked out from the Cold Ice Mirror, Shenku didn’t immerse himself in the emotions of his loss. If he was able to enter here, that also meant he was one of the chosen prides of heaven; his heart of martial arts was as solid as a rock.

He didn’t say a word. Instead, he swallowed down a pill that overflowed with medicinal fragrance, then sat down and began to meditate to restore his wounds.

The Cold Ice Mirror’s surface began to surge like a flowing river. The virtual opponent that matched Shenku gradually faded away, leaving behind five other virtual opponents.

The people standing outside were momentarily at a loss for words.

Lin Ming’s eyes twinkled. He had deduced the entire fight just now again and again, recording every minute detail of the battle just then.

“This Cold Ice Mirror is indeed amazing. The virtual opponents it produces actually possess their own thoughts and wisdom…”

After a moment of thought, from the faction of the primal god race powerhouses, a slim figure flashed out.

The one fighting this time was Lanlu. Her pupils were like stars and her skin was pale like snow. Her slim and slender figure stood in the dim light of the mirror’s surface.

Across from her, reflected within the constantly changing water bright surface of the Cold Ice Mirror, another peerless woman appeared. This woman wore blue clothes that were in a very simple and plain style. From within her body, the atmosphere of 10 billion years flowed out.

Lanlu’s talent was higher than Shenku’s. But, no one thought she was a match for her virtual opponent.

“Lanlu!”

Diwuhen wanted to stop her but he was too late. Lanlu had already flown into the Cold Ice Mirror.

Her fingers twisted in the sign of an orchid, her thumb touching her middle finger. Where they touched, light began to shine.

One after another, runes began to bloom around her like fresh flowers.

These flowers were flowers of the Great Dao. They emitted beams of light that surged with a mystic strength, forming a solid defense of flower petals.

From the start she had been in a defensive stance; she had no intentions of going on the offensive.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Lanlu’s form divided into two, two into four, four into eight, with more and more appearing until over a thousand copies were there.

Lanlu was actually someone skilled in illusions, and her attainments in this field were extremely high!

“Smart choice.”

Lin Ming nodded.

From the information they were told, one only needed to last within the Cold Ice Mirror for 1000 breaths of time; they didn’t necessarily need to defeat their opponents.

Lanlu judged her own strength and knew she wasn’t a match for her opponent. Then, her decision was to delay for as long as possible.

Thus when facing this unfathomably deep ancient genius, going on the defensive was undoubtedly the best way to preserve the most strength as well as last as long as possible.

Within the Cold Ice Mirror, ripples appeared. A mysterious rhythm of the Great Dao appeared.

The blue-clothed woman stepped forwards. An ice lotus appeared on her fingertip. The attribute she cultivated was the same as Lanlu.

Ca!

The ice lotus instantly expanded. In a moment, the Great Dao flower blocked out the skies, covering one part of the world.

Countless ice crystals shot out, carrying with them a horrifying power of Laws. They pierced through the void, striking Lanlu’s illusions and crushing them to pieces.

Peng!

Lanlu’s true self managed to block the ice crystals, but at the same time she exposed her position!

The ice lotus revolved and came suppressing down on Lanlu.

A blinding blue light instantly flooded everyone’s vision.

In the following battle, Lanlu didn’t attack at all. She used all sorts of clever tricks and resourceful defensive techniques and methods to resist the unending onslaught of her opponent.

However, the absolute disparity in their strengths was still there. In just 200 breaths of time, Lanlu exhausted her energy. She flew away, tumbling out of the Cold Ice Mirror in an embarrassing state.

Lanlu had also been defeated. Although she lasted for a longer period, it was still far too distant from 1000 breaths of time.

She had chosen not to attack, but rather rely on her illusion skills to stand on the defensive and delay for time. Even so, she failed!

“What a terrifying opponent…”

“This is the strength of an ancient genius?”

Everyone exclaimed in surprise. Lanlu’s opponent had a lower cultivation boundary and Lanlu had clearly been trying to delay for time. Even so, she had been defeated!

“Even illusions don’t work. Breaking through Lanlu’s illusions requires a great deal of strength, and to destroy Lanlu’s 1000 illusions, there has to be at least 1000 attacks. If it were an ordinary martial artist, the first salvo of attacks would have drained most of their strength. But, the virtual opponent didn’t seem affected at all, and continued to launch a wild barrage of attacks afterwards.”

“The enemy is too strong, this is going to be difficult for us to do!”

Chapter 1884 – The Past Versus the Present

After Shenku and Lanlu suffered continuous defeats, there were only four people left who had yet to take the challenge.

But in To Bagui’s eyes, of these four people, Smokeless had the highest hopes of success.

His right hand fell on Diwuhen’s shoulder. “I must ask Brother Wuhen, do you think you can win?”

Diwuhen wryly smiled and shook his head. “My talent isn’t much better than Lanlu’s, and my cultivation method is primarily focused on being on the offensive. This virtual opponent in the Cold Ice Mirror doesn’t seem as if my attack method will work on it. The chances of me winning are near zero. But you, your bloodline power is quite special… perhaps… if you bet it all perhaps you might be able to last for a thousand breaths of time?”

As Diwuhen spoke, To Bagui’s complexion also turned earnest. His chances weren’t high, but what he wanted was to further explore the road ahead so that Smokeless would have more time to prepare herself.

“Brother Wuhen, if all of us fail then what will happen? Will we have come to the forbidden land in vain?” To Bagui said, voicing his worries.

They had come to the Asura forbidden land to struggle for lucky chances. But more importantly, they wanted to find a path for the primal god race and celestials in the great calamity!

If they were to fail advancing forwards because of the Cold Ice Mirror and were forced back with nothing in hand, then they would become the eternal sinners of the ancient races for the rest of time, shaming all of their ancestors!

Diwuhen said, “It shouldn’t be like that. When the Asura forbidden zone was opened in the past, there had always been two types of things able to be obtained in the forbidden land. One was a method to rescue our people and another was an individual lucky chance.

“As long as we enter the Asura forbidden land, even if we cannot pass the test set down by Heavenly God Asura, we should still be able to find a way for our races to survive.

“But… if we can pass Heavenly God Asura’s test, then we will each obtain our own lucky chances. In other words, they will be the inheritances that Heavenly God Asura left behind in the past as rewards.”

“I see…” To Bagui let out a breath of relief. “That’s good. Even if we cannot pass the Cold Ice Mirror, it will only be our own loss. It won’t be something that affects our races…”

Speaking here, To Bagui could only force a smile. He laughed, “Heavenly God Asura shouldn’t have thought that 10 billion years later, his descendants would be reduced to our standard…”

To Bagui shook his head, mocking himself. Then, he headed towards the Cold Ice Mirror.

“Senior-apprentice Brother…”

Smokeless called out to To Bagui. Although there was a giant age gap between them, they were actually fellow apprentice brother and sister.

To Bagui turned and smiled at Smokeless, saying, “If I am defeated then you will be the only celestial left. Watch my battle carefully and make sure you come up with some good countermeasures. Your talent far surpasses all others’ amongst the celestials. You should be able to win!”

As To Bagui spoke, he stepped into the Cold Ice Mirror!

To Bagui’s opponent was a middle-aged man. This man wore a plain set of war armor and had a pair of light wings floating behind him.

His entire body was wrapped in flames, and these flames contained runes of the Great Dao that emitted light through the world.

In that moment, To Bagui’s aura changed, as if a God Beast were awakening within him.

He had been renowned amongst the celestials as the Battle Sovereign for a long time already. As a peak Empyrean, his background was as deep as a sea and impossible to discern.

“Too strong, the Battle Sovereign, he… how could he be so strong!?”

Shenku gasped in surprise, his eyes filled with shock. As a middle Empyrean, the difference in strength between him and a peak Empyrean wasn’t considered too far; he could feel just how strong To Bagui was.

He had seen Diwuhen in his peak state before, and he felt that even Diwuhen was much weaker than To Bagui was.

Diwuhen said, “What To Bagui is using is the power of the Sovereign Sun bloodline. His bloodline can light up like a sun and for a short time stimulate all of his hidden potential. But after using this ability, his strength will rapidly disappear, and even his boundary will temporarily drop. It will be hard to restore himself even with ten days of time.

“This is an all-out method that can only be used in desperate times. Normally speaking, To Bagui won’t use it, because once the period passes in which his full potential is released, he will have no further way to defeat his enemy and can only allow himself to be destroyed.”

Diwuhen explained to Shenku.

Shenku said, “So that’s how it is. The Sovereign Sun bloodline… this sort of bloodline is indeed suited for using within the Cold Ice Mirror. As long as he can last for a thousand breaths of time then he’ll be fine. Whether or not To Bagui’s boundary drops afterwards doesn’t matter.

As Shenku spoke, To Bagui had already stopped before his opponent. He was like a towering mountain, his strength boundless. His snow white light wings were as taut as swords, projecting an incomparable sharpness that seemed as if they could cut apart light.

He advanced forwards a step at a time, his footsteps meandering with a strange rhythm. The entire Cold Ice Mirror seemed as if it would shatter, and the light within twisted and rippled.

The two pupils of the two opponents each clearly reflected each other.

In the next moment, a sharp light flashed in their pupils as they both cried out.

They rushed forwards at an incredibly fast speed, carrying with them a dreadful momentum that seemed as if it could trample down everything as they collided together.

With a rise of their hands, their attacks were like violent storms clashing.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Within the Cold Ice Mirror, splendid sparks of light shot out. Violent strength boiled over, crashing forth like tides. Countless arcs of thunder twined on their fists as they collided again and again.

This incredible supernatural might of thunder turned into a torrential rainstorm that fell unto the earth. The entirety of space seemed to be filled with an endless cloud of blinding white lightning.

As if the apocalypse had arrived.

“Senior-apprentice Brother going all-out is… really strong!”

Smokeless held her hands together. Because of To Bagui’s arrogant and fierce stance, she was infected by his zeal, her fighting spirit seething within her blood.

Indomitable, fierce, and not fearing death, this was To Bagui’s martial arts.

He wouldn’t delay for time. Rather, he would use the strength granted by burning his bloodline to brutally fight for 1000 breaths of time!

“The celestials’ Battle Sovereign is really formidable.”

The several god race martial artists couldn’t help but exclaim as they looked on at the battle.

Bang!

A terrifying power of divinity exploded. Even the void was torn apart by To Bagui’s astonishing attack, with cracks appearing everywhere. The space here was unexpectedly like glass, cracking upon breaking.

However, these spatial cracks soon regenerated, as if they had never existed at all.

400 breaths of time. To Bagui’s attack just then had wounded the virtual opponent for the first time.

A little bit of blood leaked out from the virtual opponent’s chest.

From the first battle until now, this was the first time that the virtual phantom of an ancient genius had been injured.

“He has the upper hand!”

Smokeless shouted, her thoughts tightening. There were still 600 breaths of time left but To Bagui hadn’t shown any trend of slowing down at all. As long as the Sovereign Sun bloodline could last for the full 1000 breaths of time, then he really might be able to pass!

At that time, the virtual opponent changed. The man stood up, his body carrying a deeper, more indistinct aura.

In that instant, it was as if he had changed.

His body was covered with dense runes and electric lights shot out from his eyes. His aura became as deep as the nine nether abyss, impossible to predict.

To Bagui’s pupils shrank. Within his opponent’s eyes, he could feel a horrifying killing intent!

Woosh!

The virtual phantom attacked. Its speed was far faster, nearly impossible to respond to!

Endless supernatural powers turned into all kinds of Great Dao Laws that tore through the void.

Behind the blurry man’s figure, the phantom of a war god appeared, 1000 feet high. This war god was pitch black and it emitted boundless mystic strength, bathed in a mysterious halo of light.

The war god phantom wielded a massive axe that came smashing down at To Bagui.

Bang!

The void cracked like glass once more. To Bagui spat out a mouthful of blood as he was sent tumbling away. Horror and panic filled his eyes.

His body and mind shook. This virtual opponent was only an upper Empyrean, someone with an inferior cultivation to his own, and yet he was so strong!

After suffering a single wound, this virtual opponent had erupted with an even greater strength to directly and heavily wound To Bagui.

To Bagui had seen countless proud children of heaven before, and yet none of them were able to stand side-by-side to the phantom of this ancient genius!

After burning his bloodline strength, he had still been heavily wounded by his opponent. It was then that To Bagui realized he had been defeated, utterly defeated!

In the past, he had once been defeated after burning his Sovereign Sun bloodline. But that was only when his bloodline strength had vanished and he had been extremely weakened.

He had never experienced a moment like today, where he would be defeated by someone else even when he burned his bloodline and was in his most powerful state!

To Bagui gloomily left the Cold Ice Mirror.

His Sovereign Sun bloodline had already dissipated and his entire body felt feeble. He knew that his trip into the Asura forbidden zone had ended; it was impossible for him to go any further.

Just this Cold Ice Mirror was so difficult. Or, perhaps they were just that bad.

“Don’t be disheartened. These virtual phantoms should be almost the strongest geniuses from the ancient era, according to the standards of that time. If this phantom were a real person, they would easily become a True Divinity in the future. It’s not surprising that we cannot compete with it.”

Diwuhen patted To Bagui’s shoulder. He felt that he shouldn’t even try to enter. To Bagui had resorted to using his bloodline strength but even then he had been defeated at his peak state, much less Diwuhen.

“Lin Ming, my god race only has you left.”

Diwuhen ruefully smiled. Lin Ming’s talent had been recognized and strongly approved of by the old God Sovereign. He might be able to create a miracle here.

“Will the Laws you understand be of use here?”

Lin Ming shook his head, “Not a bit.”

Lin Ming’s answer was already expected. Before this Cold Ice Mirror, one could only depend on their true ability. It was impossible to take any shortcuts.

Diwuhen lightly sighed. Their group had been chosen after such a ruckus and they had paid a considerable price in order to enter the Asura forbidden land. If they were only barely able to obtain the method to save their people but returned with nothing else, the resources would really be wasted.

“Smokeless!” To Bagui looked towards Smokeless.

“I understand.” Smokeless nodded. “I won’t lose!”

Smokeless’ voice was confident.

“Good!” To Bagui took a deep breath. He knew that Smokeless would only say this if she were sure of herself. She wasn’t someone to joke around during such times.

At this time, Smokeless had already moved towards the Cold Ice Mirror. She turned and glanced at Lin Ming, a strange expression on her face.

Then, she lifted her foot and stepped into the surface of the Cold Ice Mirror.

Ripples spread out as if on the surface of a still lake. Within the world of the Cold Ice Mirror, Smokeless faced her opponent, another peerless woman who was of similar age. This woman wore a veil and her aura was swift and sharp.

“Even if you are an ancient genius that will become a True Divinity, your cultivation is still lower than mine. I don’t believe that you will defeat me!”

As Smokeless spoke, she took out a four foot long sword from her spatial ring. This sword blade glimmered, seeming as if it could pierce through the hearts of those watching!

Hu - !

Smokeless’ aura erupted. A blue tornado appeared around her. Although this tornado seemed gentle, it contained a dreadful strength. It could tear down a person’s flesh and blood and blow apart their bones!

“Finally, she shows her true skills…”

Lin Ming watched closely. When Smokeless had fought those monsters formed from energy and Law runes, she had only used the strength of her mortal body to fight them.

But now, Smokeless used the full strength of her power of divinity.

Chapter 1885 – True Divinity Spirit Treasure

“Smokeless isn’t planning to passively defend, but to go on the offensive…”

Lanlu commented. In her opinion, delaying for time was a slightly safer choice. After all, victory was there as long as they could pass a thousand breaths of time.

To Bagui remained silent. Lin Ming quietly said, “Delaying for time seems like the safer choice, but the truth is that before the battle has begun, it is the same as already acquiescing that you are weaker than your opponent. That means the battle is already half lost!”

Lin Ming’s words left Lanlu surprised. She reddened a little with shame.

Indeed, to a peak genius, drawing out time would only end in their defeat. For them, what they should do was use their peak strength to confront these ancient geniuses!

However, this was based upon believing in one’s own strength, otherwise it would be the same as trying to break a rock with an egg.

At that time, Smokeless’ opponent stood tall, her face blurry and her body burning with blue-white flames. These flames didn’t emit any heat at all, but rather exuded a chilling cold that made the surrounding void freeze over.

This was a duel between a Great World King and a peak ordinary World King!

Smokeless was the first to move. Her aura suddenly soared once more and her black waterfall-like hair danced in the wind. A blue drop of blood leaked down from her finger, merging into the tornado around her. The wind in front of Smokeless began to gather, condensing into a lance made of wild winds!

“Heavenly God Lance!”

Lanlu was stunned. This was the legendary weapon left behind by the number one powerhouse of the celestials during the ancient era. But, this Heavenly God Lance had never been passed down.

According to rumors, the Heavenly God Lance had Laws carved in it by the number one powerhouse of the celestials.

And the chart of these Laws was left behind to the celestials. Now, Smokeless should have been using the chart left behind to the celestials to summon a phantom of the Heavenly God Lance.

Although this was only a phantom, it had the dao rhythm of the Laws from the past number one celestial powerhouse. Its might was no trifling matter!

Woosh!

Smokeless grabbed the Heavenly God Spear and shot forwards. Her body was like a meteor that tore through the clear skies.

And then, Smokeless’ opponent also moved.

The blue-white flames on her body suddenly blazed upwards. From the flame a blue bird flew out, bringing with it an endless freezing cold energy.

The bird flapped its wings, rushing towards Smokeless.

Smokeless’ complexion was cold and decisive. She thrust out towards the bird’s chest.

The spirit bird emitted a shrill cry as its body was pierced through, as if it had suffered a tremendous attack.

However, upon seeing this, the blue-clothed female phantom tauntingly smiled, thinking little of it.

In that moment, blue light sparkled around her and blue war armor covered her body.

Her skin was like transparent crystal. As her hair fluttered upwards, she looked like an unrivalled goddess.

In her hands was another black sword.

As this sword appeared, it emitted a keening cry and absorbed all the Laws in the surrounding space.

For a time, the icy flames tangling around the woman burned even brighter. They expanded outwards, forming a domain!

It wasn’t strange for such a peerless genius to possess a domain, but the domain this blue-clothed woman used was beyond ordinary. The Laws unified within it had reached a mind-bogglingly high boundary, even putting an ordinary Empyrean to shame.

This ice flame domain wildly swallowed up Smokeless.

Smokeless grit her teeth. Behind her, blue wind gathered into wings, making her speed reach the limit.

“Hah!”

Winds whipped up in all directions. Law runes recklessly swirled around Smokeless. The ice flames were torn apart; Smokeless had opened her own domain.

Cold wind domain and ice flame domain, these two great domains brutally smashed into each other.

For a time, the world within the mirror was flooded with endless blue light. The skies changed color and icy flames tumbled about. Cold winds dashed through the world, like a gorgeous scene of art!

These two domains interwove.

Smokeless gripped the war lance formed from the Wind Laws and began to fiercely battle the blue-clothed woman!

Two peerless women fought. One real, one virtual, they began to engage in a crazy melee within the twin domains!

This was a world-shaking battle.

Outside the Cold Ice Mirror the celestial and god race powerhouses were all left speechless!

In particular, To Bagui. He had watched with his own eyes as Smokeless returned to the celestials after disappearing for so many years and then revealing her formidable strength. Amongst the juniors of the celestials, no one could stand on par with her. It could even be said that they were all left far behind!

Even so, Smokeless was only barely able to draw equal to an ancient genius that had a lower cultivation than she did.

“The geniuses of the ancient era, just how much stronger were they…”

To Bagui deeply sighed. It had to be known that most of these ancient geniuses came from the god race and only a small minority came from the celestials. The two races once had an incomparably glorious history in the past, but they had slowly declined over the eons. It was said that the Heavenly Dao simply didn’t abide their existence any longer.

“She’s even burnt her Bluesilver blood. Smokeless is giving this everything she has.”

Smokeless’ blood was different from other normal celestial martial artists’. Her blood was dark blue and formed ice crystals in the air. This sort of bloodline was a variation bloodline amongst the celestials. A single drop could freeze a raging river.

If Smokeless could rise to become a peak Empyrean, then her blood alone could leave an entire world trapped in ice.

But now, even when Smokeless used her bloodline strength, she was only able to barely fight to a draw with this ancient genius.

The combat became increasingly intense.

Smokeless’ hair flew upwards like a war goddess. But across from her, the blue-clothed woman released a blinding blue light from all over her body, her body burning with flames as she almost transformed into a phoenix.

She was using her phoenix body to wildly fight with Smokeless.

The flames on her body, after being cut apart by Smokeless, turned into small spirit birds in the sky that continued to attack Smokeless.

These flames each seemed to have a mind of their own and carried with them an attribute of endlessness!

Smokeless soon fell into a siege of flames!

“This endlessly growing flame is too difficult to deal with. If she cannot extinguish them then there will only be more and more!”

Lin Ming saw through what was happening. The flames emitted by the ancient genius were in a way similar to the Holy Scripture creator’s Concept of Life.

If one could cultivate this Concept to large success, that would be incredible!

Flames turbulently surged. Smokeless also realized the danger she was in. If this continued she would be thoroughly swallowed up by the flames.

She grit her teeth, relying on her willpower to erupt with the strength of her bloodline once more.

Chi-la!

Thick ice flames were cut apart. Surrounded by whistling winds, Smokeless launched her icy blue wind-attribute wings outwards, impacting into the blue skies!

The blue-clothed woman frowned. She hurtled upwards, chasing after Smokeless. However, in that moment, a mystical black light covered the blue-clothed woman. Countless Asura runes danced within that black light.

As the blue-clothed woman was shrouded, her body shook. Then, beneath the eyes of those watching, she turned into a wisp of blue smoke that scattered into the wind, vanishing without a trace left behind.

All that was left over was Smokeless flying alone in the air, watching with a stunned expression.

“Mm? What happened?” Shenku was startled. The blue-clothed woman was clearly winning and yet she had suddenly vanished.

“The time was reached, 1000 breaths!”

Standing beside Shenku, To Bagui finally relaxed. Although the others hadn’t been counting, To Bagui had been keeping track of every single second in his heart, hoping that the time limit would quickly be reached.

Although they had barely won, they had still won in the end.

A smile appeared on To Bagui’s face.

“Smokeless, good job.”

To Bagui shouted.

“Truly terrifying. It's hard to find anyone in my god race that can compare with Smokeless’ talent…”

Diwuhen praised in his heart.

However, completely different from the excited Diwuhen and To Bagui, as Smokeless came fluttering down from the skies her expression was a bit depressed, and even unhappy.

She was well aware that if the time limit didn’t exist, her chances of winning didn’t surpass 20%.

Ultimately, she was a loser.

She had lost to an opponent of a lower cultivation boundary.

As Smokeless grew up, she had always been the one jumping ranks to fight others. Today was the only time when someone else had jumped ranks to suppress her.

She had only been able to win by utilizing favorable rules. Such a victory naturally couldn’t make her happy.

To Bagui was able to see Smokeless’ thoughts. He said, “You still won. Out of all of us, you’re the only one to have won. Isn’t that enough?”

To Bagui was able to say from a different perspective.

“Smokeless, don’t be so harsh on yourself. During the ancient era, the martial arts civilization was much more prosperous than it is now. Their inheritances were far more powerful and it was a time when countless heroic rivals rose up together. In an environment with so many geniuses fighting together, that would also affect their rate of growth. It’s not something that the conditions of the current era can compare with. If you were born in ancient times, you would certainly be no worse than that woman you faced in the mirror.”

The civilization of martial arts had its rises and declines. The essential reason for such a cycle was because the inheritance of martial arts was easy to sever.

This was because it was impossible to easily copy cultivation method jade slips.

For instance, take True Divinity cultivation methods as an example. These mostly existed as singularly unique copies left behind by their creators. If their descendants wanted to copy it, then they would have to fully comprehend and train in the True Divinity cultivation method. In other words, this was equal to asking someone to cultivate all the way to a True Divinity. The conditions for copying a jade slip of this level were simply too harsh.

In this situation, if a True Divinity died in battle without passing down a jade slip, it was possible for the line of their inheritance to be broken.

In 10 billion years, for all sorts of different reasons, there were many broken inheritances.

It was also because of this reason that some peerless powerhouses would spend a tremendous amount of effort to construct a land of inheritance before their death. This was so they could choose an appropriate successor and permanently preserve their legacy.

As To Bagui comforted Smokeless, the Cold Ice Mirror trembled once more.

A stream of light flashed. This stream of light flew out from the Cold Ice Mirror’s profound surface and into Smokeless’ hand.

“Mm? This is…?”

Everyone was shocked. They quickly looked over.

They could see the light slowly converging into Smokeless’ hand, forming into a circle-shaped object.

This was a bracelet!

Seeing this, To Bagui already guessed what it was. His breathing quickened.

“This is something left behind by Heavenly God Asura!”

“Incredible!”

The god race martial artists all widened their eyes, their complexions changing. A treasure left behind by Heavenly God Asura; that was serious!

“What is it?”

Everyone circled around Smokeless.

To Bagui excitedly caught Smokeless’ hand, “Let us see!”

Within Smokeless’ hand was a strangely shaped bracelet. This bracelet was like two snakes twisted together. It was dark gold in color and flooded with a mysterious aura.

“True Divinity spirit treasure!”

Diwuhen sucked in a deep breath, a look of envy crossing his face.

Smokeless’ victory had been rewarded with a True Divinity spirit treasure.

Chapter 1886 – Lin Ming Fights

True Divinity spirit treasures were also divided into grades. The True Divinity spirit treasures left behind by lower True Divinities were naturally ordinary.

But for some outstanding True Divinities, for instance upper True Divinities, or those that had surpassed True Divinity such as the Asura Road Master and the creator of the Holy Scripture, the True Divinity spirit treasures they left behind would be of a completely different level. This bracelet in front of everyone was such an example.

As something that came from the Asura forbidden land’s Cold Ice Mirror, any rewards here would have come from the Asura Road Master. It must be something extraordinary.

The functions behind this True Divinity spirit treasure had yet to be revealed, but without a doubt it would prove a great boost to Smokeless in the great calamity.

“It should be a treasure that Heavenly God Asura left behind in the past. Any True Divinity spirit treasures were long since useless to him. He must have placed these treasures in the Cold Ice Mirror for his descendants.”

“Those that can last 1000 breaths of time against their opponent can obtain a True Divinity spirit treasure. Then what if they killed their opponent? What then?”

Diwuhen and To Bagui asked, filled with anticipation.

But unfortunately, they could only fantasize about the possibilities. Wanting to find out the truth was far too difficult.

Diwuhen shook his head. He looked at Lin Ming and said, “Lin Ming, everything is up to you now. You are someone who His Majesty God Sovereign favors. I believe you will be able to create your own miracle.”

Diwuhen was only able to sigh in admiration as he saw Smokeless last 1000 breaths of time within the mirror.

He also had high hopes for Lin Ming. This was because the old God Sovereign had said that Lin Ming might be the most talented individual he had ever seen in his life.

Diwuhen had absolute faith in the judgments of his master. He was sure that Lin Ming’s performance would be no worse than Smokeless’.

As long as Lin Ming could last for 1000 breaths of time, their god race could also obtain a True Divinity spirit treasure on their side.

Otherwise, if only the celestials obtained a treasure and the god race were to return empty-handed, that would be far too ugly a sight.

“Don’t feel pressured. It’s fine as long as you try your best!”

Diwuhen slapped Lin Ming’s shoulder. Lin Ming nodded and moved towards the Cold Ice Mirror.

He passed by Smokeless. Smokeless’ eyes moved from her True Divinity bracelet that she wore on her right wrist to Lin Ming’s face.

“This time you don’t have the support of the Laws and the difference in our boundaries is also wiped away. This is a fair competition for the both of us. Since the god race’s God Sovereign has given you such a high estimation, I am also looking forwards to seeing your strength.”

A smile hung on Smokeless’ lips. In her eyes, everything about Lin Ming was a puzzle.

She didn’t know where Lin Ming had obtained an inheritance concerning god decrees, nor how he managed to learn it.

His opportunities and his luck left one seething with envy. But besides luck, Smokeless believed that this human youth must have some remarkable aspect to him. But as to what that was, she had no idea.

Now was the time when she could see his true strength.

Lin Ming glanced at Smokeless and faintly smiled. Without responding, he calmly stepped into the Cold Ice Mirror, as if he were simply crossing through a door.

Lin Ming’s opponent was a youth wielding a heavy sword, his eyes filled with a gloomy yin chill and his aura restrained. The feeling this youth gave off was like that of a cheetah ready to burst into action. Once prey appeared, this youth would ferociously pounce forwards, striking down his enemy!

Without a doubt, this was a peerless genius!

Ca!

The Black Dragon Spear appeared. The pitch black divine spear shimmered with an icy cold godly light.

Presently, Lin Ming was able to use the Black Dragon Spear with skill and relative ease. Although he couldn’t display the true potential of the Black Dragon Spear, he also wouldn’t be drained of strength after using it several times.

Seeing the Black Dragon Spear appear, the god race and celestial powerhouses were startled.

This was also a True Divinity spirit treasure. Moreover, this didn’t seem like an ordinary True Divinity spirit treasure at all.

“This boy, he has so many lucky chances!”

Shenku cried in alarm.

To Bagui said with some envy, “His luck is too good. But, good luck is only one of the conditions to become a peerless powerhouse. Besides that, you also have to look at one’s true abilities. Otherwise, no matter how many lucky chances you have they will all be wasted.”

As To Bagui spoke, Lin Ming rushed forwards!

The Black Dragon Spear was pointed straight towards the heavy sword-wielding youth’s chest. Behind Lin Ming, nine stars floated in the skies, the vast power of stars pouring into Lin Ming like an endless waterfall. The strength within his mortal body instantly climbed to unbelievable heights!

Ka ka ka!

Space shattered. In front of Lin Ming, that heavy sword youth also stepped forwards, his face still gloomy and his eyes filled with killing intent. The pure black heavy sword was like the scythe of a death god, cutting down all life.

The two people hurtled towards each other like meteors. As they collided, spear and sword clashed.

For a time, a terrifying strength erupted in front of Lin Ming and the heavy sword youth!

In that instant, Lin Ming opened the Heretical God Force. The power of thunder and fire wildly erupted from his body and a terrifying vortex of energy fell down from the clouds, swallowing everything!

Peng!

The heavy sword flew away. The black-clothed youth’s right palm cracked open, blood gushing out. Lin Ming’s gigantic strength had forcefully knocked the heavy sword from the youth’s hand.

This was the disparity of absolute strength!

The moment the heavy sword was sent tumbling away, the black-clothed youth’s sword light also weakened a tremendous amount. With a light cracking sound, Lin Ming’s spear light had already invaded the youth’s protective power of divinity.

The black-clothed youth’s complexion changed. He rapidly drew back, wanting to escape from Lin Ming’s attack range.

However…

It was too late!

Lin Ming stepped forwards, his movements containing unbelievable Laws. The grandmist force field erupted, locking down the surrounding space!

Immediately, the black-clothed youth was shackled by this formidable strength!

The black-clothed youth was only able to stare helplessly on as the Black Dragon Spear thrust towards him.

Puff!

With a faint sound, the black-clothed youth’s protective power of divinity tore apart like paper. The long spear thrust towards him. The black-clothed youth wanted to summon a shield, but the Black Dragon Spear’s momentum was too fast, too great. The black-clothed youth’s body had been tempered for a long time, but even so, before the sharp Black Dragon Spear it had no ability to resist at all.

Blood shot out!

The Black Dragon Spear broke into the black-clothed youth’s chest, piercing right through him!

The black-clothed youth hurtled backwards with Lin Ming. Beneath the incredible impulse of Lin Ming’s strike, both of them went hurtling downwards like a meteor!

With an explosion, the two people soared through the wide skies until they smashed into a 100,000 foot high glacier.

A turbulent strength erupted, crazily blowing into the glacier. With a crackling rumble, the 100,000 foot high glacier began to collapse!

The earth trembled. Massive chunks of ice fell to the floor. Countless pieces of ice, mist and dust soared into the air, blocking out the skies!

The black-clothed youth vomited a mouthful of blood. His body had been torn open and his organs broken. He had been buried in the endless slurry of ice, his body long since lost deep within it.

Peng!

With a loud crack the black-clothed youth’s body exploded beneath the ice, turning into countless runes that scattered in the air.

Lin Ming grasped the Black Dragon Spear and floated high in the skies. Beneath his feet, an endless river of ice wildly raged.

Like this, the battle ended.

Outside the Cold Ice Mirror, To Bagui, Diwuhen, Shenku, Lanlu, and Smokeless were utterly shocked. Smokeless’ eyes were as wide as moons and filled with disbelief.

Everything had been like a dream.

Lin Ming’s opponent was an ancient genius. Before this, she had also personally experienced how terrifying an ancient genius was.

Even though their opponents had been at a lower cultivation, they still weren’t able to slay them.

But in front of Lin Ming, a similar ancient genius had been instantly cut down!

The entire fight had lasted less than two breaths of time. Lin Ming himself had barely made two attacks.

In fact, he had only summoned his true essence. One could even consider that just one move.

“This… what is this?” To Bagui’s jaw fell down. He turned and asked Diwuhen.

Diwuhen was also lost in a daze. He had heard the old God Sovereign say that Lin Ming’s talent was beyond ordinary, and because of his faith and trust in the old God Sovereign, he also believed Lin Ming was special.

But this ‘beyond ordinary’ was a bit too beyond the ordinary!

“The one he killed just now, was that really a similar opponent to ours?”

A woman’s voice asked, filled with hesitation and uncertainty. Smokeless was simply unable to believe her eyes.

When the four previous people entered the Cold Ice Mirror, they had all faced inconceivably formidable opponents. Their strength seemed endless, their defensive capabilities extraordinary, and no matter what ultimate moves were used, these opponents blocked them all.

But Lin Ming’s opponent was like a piece of mud, dead upon touch.

The disparity was far too great.

If their opponents were really the same, then Smokeless felt that she was nothing but a joke.

To Bagui took a deep breath and looked deeply at Lin Ming in the Cold Ice Mirror. He forced a smile and said, “When Heavenly God Asura laid down this array formation he certainly made it impartial towards anyone that entered. It’s true that Lin Ming’s opponent was strong, and we also felt that. But, Lin Ming was simply stronger; he has already surpassed the standard of an ancient genius. In such a situation, for someone with a lower cultivation boundary to challenge him is simply asking to be instantly killed.”

To Bagui sighed as he spoke.

For such a genius like Lin Ming, if an opponent of a lower cultivation boundary were to fight him, that was simply the same as tossing vegetables in his face. It was nothing more than committing suicide. This was the same even for ancient geniuses!

This was because Lin Ming might be described as the most amazing genius to appear within the 33 Heavens for the last several billions of years!

“Surpassed the standard of ancient geniuses?”

Smokeless’ heart shook. She felt that the current her was far worse than the ancient geniuses, but Lin Ming had already surpassed them.

The disparity was far too great.

At this time, Lin Ming had already flown towards the entrance of the Cold Ice Mirror. He put away the Black Dragon Spear and stepped out from the Cold Ice Mirror.

As the five others waiting outside looked at Lin Ming, their eyes looked as if they were staring at a monster.

This Lin Ming, it was far too simple to describe him as someone ‘sure to become a True Divinity in the future’!

Even though they were both geniuses, the evaluation that the celestials and god race had given Smokeless was – ‘someone that had a chance of becoming a True Divinity in the future’.

“Let alone becoming a True Divinity, he will not be a normal True Divinity. Even when the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was young, he absolutely wasn’t Lin Ming’s match…”

Diwuhen thought. He increasingly felt that Lin Ming would play an unimaginable role in this great calamity. Perhaps… he might be able to shoulder the task of reversing the fate of the god race. Of course, this was all under the premise that Lin Ming was willing to shoulder such a heavy burden.

As everyone was lost in their own thoughts, Lin Ming looked towards the Cold Ice Mirror, waiting for his reward.

Smokeless had lasted for a full 1000 breaths of time. Although she wasn’t a match for the ancient genius, she had still obtained a True Divinity spirit treasure left behind by the Asura Road Master as a reward.

Then what would he obtain?

Lin Ming waited, but the Cold Ice Mirror remained quiet, not sending out any reward. Instead, Lin Ming could faintly feel a trace of unusual aura percolating within the Cold Ice Mirror.

Chapter 1887 – Another Battle

“Reward? How come there’s no movement? There should at least be a True Divinity spirit treasure, and it should also be of a higher grade.”

Shenku asked, a bit puzzled. This was because the Cold Ice Mirror remained quiet for far too long.

“The situation isn’t as simple as it seems. I feel that the Laws within the Cold Ice Mirror are throbbing.”

Diwuhen said. Lin Ming was a bit startled. He had discovered something strange with the Cold Ice Mirror, but that was because he was extremely sensitive to the Asura Laws.

But Diwuhen didn’t understand the Asura Laws at all, yet he was still able to feel the palpitations within the Cold Ice Mirror. This was likely the so-called intuition that masters had.

Once someone reached the level of a peak Empyrean, even if their talent wasn’t considered too high by Lin Ming’s standards, they still had amazing experience and intuition.

Lin Ming traced his ring and moved towards the Cold Ice Mirror.

“Lin Ming?”

Diwuhen asked. At this time, countless Asura runes danced in the air in the world of the Cold Ice Mirror, gathering in the skies to form a runic tornado.

From these runes, a youth ran out. Black lightning curled around his body and he grasped a saber as he stepped on the wind.

This saber had a ghost head carved into the hilt, and beneath this ghost head were two words – Evil God!

These two words were written in the language of the ancient god race. The strokes were long and winding, revealing a mystical aura. The two words joined along with the youth’s blood red pupils. A pair of black wings flashed out from his back. He was like a true evil god that had flown out from the depths of hell!

“This is…”

Everyone was stunned; there was another opponent!

Lin Ming stepped into the world of the Cold Ice Mirror, grasping the Black Dragon Spear and facing this new enemy.

This new opponent’s cultivation was at the late Holy Lord realm.

A small boundary higher than Lin Ming.

From the early Holy Lord heavy sword youth to this current evil god with his saber, there was a sudden increase of two small boundaries, completely passing over the middle Holy Lord realm.

This scene left the Empyreans watching staring at each other in blank dismay.

They originally that after defeating the opponent in the Cold Ice Mirror, that would be considered as passing the test. They didn’t think that after killing their opponent, a stronger opponent would appear, emerging without end!

“So that’s how it is. Before Lin Ming’s reward is handed out, he has to fight more opponents. According to his success, that will decide what his final reward will be?”

Diwuhen guessed. This guess was highly reasonable. If so, then Lin Ming’s reward would truly be extraordinary. It would absolutely not be something that an ordinary True Divinity spirit treasure could compare with!

“Lin Ming’s strength should have been assessed by the Asura Laws. If he is facing a late Holy Lord realm martial artist, that means the Laws here have determined that Lin Ming’s talent has surpassed the standard of ancient geniuses!”

To Bagui uttered, his heart filled with shock.

Currently, Lin Ming was jumping ranks to fight ancient geniuses.

It had to be said that these ancient genius phantoms were all manifested from the standard of a True Divinity. If Lin Ming could jump ranks to fight these people, what sort of future achievements would he have?

Perhaps he might become an extreme True Divinity.

Or even…

As To Bagui thought to here, his mind shivered. He didn’t dare to continue with this line of thinking. Above extreme True Divinity existed those like the Asura Road Master and the creator of the Holy Scripture. The strength of those two individuals was impossible to estimate, as they had already surpassed the scope of his understanding.

At this time, within the mirror world, black thunder surged without end around the evil god youth.

Even from a distance, one could feel a strange eeriness from this black thunder, as if it could scorch away one’s marrow.

“Evil god and thunder?”

Lin Ming chuckled, a brilliant fighting spirit leaping into his eyes. “When I was in the lower realms in the past, I once obtained the title of Evil God. And today, it’s a coincidence that you are also called Evil God and use thunder. To cross 10 billion years and for us to fight here, this could be considered fate.”

Lin Ming felt that these martial artist phantoms within the Cold Ice Mirror weren’t purely virtual creations. Rather, the Asura Road Master had used some ancient geniuses as templates and adjusted their various strength levels and Laws.

10 billion years ago, these phantoms were likely real people, but they weren’t necessarily so outstanding.

Lin Ming stepped on the void, moving forwards one step at a time. Then, suddenly, he attacked.

Spear light erupted. Within the void of the mirror, faint cracks appeared and regenerated. Lin Ming’s speed rapidly drew to the extreme!

But at the same time, in front of Lin Ming, the evil god youth’s eyes also flashed with a brilliant divine light.

The saber in his hands chopped down. A dreadful saber intent wrapped around the saber blade. A saber strike that seemed as if it could sunder the skies smashed into Lin Ming’s spear light.

Bang!

The terrifying collision caused energy to wildly shoot outwards.

As for Lin Ming and the evil god youth, neither of them were forced a single step back. That brief exchange just now had only been a probing strike.

Lin Ming discovered that the thunder which twined around the evil god youth had merged into the surrounding space. The faint aura of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws gathered along with the thunder, all of it pouring into the evil god youth’s body to slowly supplement his strength.

“Thunder Laws’ Concept of Life?”

Thunder could grow endlessly and even form life. In the legends, in the most primeval of times when the world was just born and everything was in chaos, it was a bolt of thunder striking the ancient seas that caused life to be born.

If one understood the Concepts of Thunder, then a martial artist with extremely high attainments in the Laws could derive energy from thunder to restore themselves. This wasn’t strange at all.

However, this caused Lin Ming to frown. He didn’t want to waste too much energy on this youth. So, he intended to cut off this youth’s ability to communicate with the surrounding heaven and earth origin energy.

In the blink of an eye, Lin Ming instantly made a decision.

The Asura Heavenly Array Diagram within his body rose like crystal columns, the tinkling sound sweeping out in all directions.

On these crystal columns, the endless power of the Asura Laws flooded outwards, wrapped in the melody of the Great Dao.

Amongst the sparkling light, the Asura Heavenly Array Diagram wrapped around Lin Ming and the evil god youth.

Weng!

The array diagram emitted a boundless mystic strength, pressing down on the power of thunder. The Asura Heavenly Array Diagram within Lin Ming had been personally carved by the Asura Road Master, and the heights of the Laws within had reached the peak of possibility.

The two strengths constantly collided, at the same time isolating the evil god youth from his connection with the mirror world.

This sudden change caused a look of surprise to cross the youth’s face.

Although his communication with the world had been severed, he still fearlessly threw himself towards Lin Ming.

The saber in his hands surged with black thunder, sweeping through the world. This thunder wove together, forming endless numbers of black lotus flowers within.

Lotuses were born in the sea of thunder; this was the substantialization of the Thunder Laws. Lin Ming knew that in terms of Thunder Laws alone, this youth’s attainments were higher than his own!

Up to now, Lin Ming had placed the entirety of his efforts on cultivating the Asura Laws and Holy Scripture Laws, thus he had temporarily postponed his advancement in the Thunder and Fire Laws as well as the Space and Time Laws.

This was because he felt that the Asura Sutra and the Holy Scripture were the foundation of all Laws within the world. One representing the outer universe, one representing the inner universe – the two great Laws covered nearly all the learnings of martial arts, encompassing everything.

As for the Thunder and Fire Laws, Space and Time Laws, they were simply branches.

To lay down the foundation was the most important objective of all!

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Each black lotus flower emitted a terrifying aura, as if they were stars.

Even Lin Ming’s heart shook. He knew that his opponent was uncommon.

All the black lotus flowers shook together, releasing Great Dao runes that billowed with ghastly black flames, all of them sweeping towards Lin Ming.

“Mm?”

Just from facing this, Lin Ming felt a tremendous pressure. It was as if an endless river of stars was violently impacting towards him, continuously striking his flesh and blood!

The black lotuses bloomed with thunder. Their strength was incomparably strange. Not only did they attack his flesh and blood, they also struck at his divine soul.

In that moment, within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, thunder recklessly blazed through even as black flames ignited everywhere.

Each arc of thunder, each black flame, constantly wore down his soul force.

However, when Lin Ming had cultivated in the Soul World, he had experienced a transformation near rebirth several times. His soul force was as fathomless as a sea; it was impossible for a normal divine soul attack to wound him.

Although he had been restrained, Lin Ming didn’t panic at all. Waves of soul force gushed out from his spiritual sea. Wild waves rose up, resisting those black flames.

Without hesitation, Lin Ming opened the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. The Black Dragon Spear fused with the power of the nine stars. A spear thrust out, smashing through space with an overwhelming momentum.

Shua! Shua! Shua!

Countless black lotus flowers were smashed apart by the Black Dragon Spear.

The Black Dragon Spear carried with it a tremendous blood vitality, forcefully pushing out the thunder that eroded Lin Ming’s divine soul.

The two intensely collided in the skies. Lin Ming constantly battled with the phantom youth.

The brutal battle scene caused the celestial and god race martial artists to cry out in surprise.  They found it hard to imagine that humanity could produce a genius that reached such a degree of talent.

They had no idea what Lin Ming cultivated, how his background was so deep, or why his strength seemed endless. Even the strongest talent born in the last 10 billion years within the god race and celestial race would have to be inferior to Lin Ming.

At this time, the phantom youth’s saber thrust into a black lotus within the sea of thunder. Countless black runes scattered out, all of them pouring into the black lotus.

All of the lotuses hummed, quickly transforming into a singular massive black lotus. It was like a crashing world, rapidly suppressing Lin Ming.

As those outside watched this sudden reversal, they were left stunned.

And then, they noticed that the boundless black lotus flower experienced another change.

Dazzling black light emerged from within the lotus flower. A black spear tore through it like a fierce dragon, forcefully breaking it apart.

The black lotus flower exploded. Endless runes dimmed and were destroyed, dissipating in droves.

The phantom youth’s complexion changed. He rapidly retreated.

But it was too late. A bolt of black lightning slammed into his body, screaming and shooting out with endless power.

The phantom youth was shocked. His body violently trembled and black blood sprayed out from his chest. His skin and inner organs began to rapidly collapse.

The phantom youth had suffered grievous wounds. Using the last of his strength, he gathered all of the Thunder Laws within his body. For a time, a wave of even more powerful black thunder hurtled towards Lin Ming, bringing with it the pressure of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Behind Lin Ming, a giant Asura war god phantom appeared. It held two great wheels, blocking the entirety of this attack!

This impact continued for several breaths of time. Behind Lin Ming, the Asura phantom was like a peerless demon god, blocking everything.

Peng!

The phantom youth could no longer persist. His heavily wounded body had finally been completely exhausted of all energy.

His body began to disintegrate, turning into countless Asura runes that faded into the skies…

Chapter 1889 – Mysterious Woman

The mysterious woman who extracted the black sword from the void floated in the air, overflowing with peerless grace and measure.

What surprised Lin Ming was that the black sword in the woman’s hand was clearly a supreme divine weapon, but as she held it, she didn’t exude the least bit aura of fierceness, nor did she emit any killing intent.

Even her aura began to turn ethereal, becoming one with the heavens and earth.

If Lin Ming closed his eyes, he might have thought that there wasn’t anyone in front of him at all.

With sword in hand, the woman simply raised her arm and slashed it straight down at Lin Ming.

Shua!

The sword broke through space. For a time, all the starlight in the skies was swallowed up by this sword.

The sword light contracted together, forming a thin line no thicker than a baby’s finger. But within this thin line was infinite strength. This strength twisted space and time, killing straight forwards!

The strength contained within this sword light was no longer purely the power of divinity, but also contained the sword master’s killing intent, combined with the will of the Heavenly Dao!

A single gesture, a single command, a raise of the hand to summon the Great Dao of the world!

When the opponent was heaven, when the opponent was the Dao, then fighting her was the same as fighting against the world.

Facing this strike, Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. He rapidly drew backwards. He was unable to understand how an ethereal being without the slightest killing intent he could sense could emit such a disastrously terrifying attack.

He didn’t use his spear to resist this attack but instead traced his ring. In front of him, a massive gate made of chaos stones appeared.

This was the Primordius Gate.

Chi!

The thin sword light thrust into the Primordius Gate, causing it to violently shake!

Although this woman held unparalleled talent and elegance, her cultivation was simply far too low; she was unable to pierce through the Primordius Gate. But at this moment, something bizarre occurred.

The sword light that she shot out scattered as it struck the Primordius Gate, spreading out like a spider web as it covered the entire gate and passed around it, gathering and reforming behind the gate.

Woosh!

The sword light separated from the Primordius Gate and continue slashing towards Lin Ming!

“What!?”

Lin Ming’s eyes widened.

The celestial and god race powerhouses were also panic-stricken. This sword light seemed to have a mind of its own!

This woman could actually control her sword light to such a degree…

“You are not my match. Although your talent could even dominate the rivals of the ancient past, the Laws you cultivate are far too vast. With your boundary, you are unable to control them. With such shallow comprehensions, you cannot compete against me.

“My comprehensions of the Laws are far deeper than yours. I have the incarnation of the Heavenly Dao. You fighting me is the same as you fighting against the vastness of the universe. You will lose here!”

The woman’s sound transmission instantly reached Lin Ming’s mind. And at this time, the sword light also reached him.

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. At that moment, an Asura war god phantom appeared behind him.

This Asura war god was grand and majestic, an indomitable being. It stood tall, gripping a massive black wheel that crushed all before it.

This black wheel was the fusion of the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel and the Myriad Essence Reincarnation Wheel.

Zhi zhi zhi zhi!

A fierce collision sounded in the air. As the sword light stabbed into the black wheel, it emitted an eye-piercing sound that made one’s teeth ache.

Lin Ming’s eyes were solemn. Behind him, nine stars emerged from thin air, emitting endless starlight that covered him.

He immediately opened four Dao Palaces from the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. His muscles bulged out and the power of his bloodline billowed from his body, impacting straight into the deep skies.

Ka ka ka!

Under the support of this formidable power, the two fused wheels forcefully obliterated the woman’s sword light.

Seeing this, the mysterious woman was startled.

“A terrifying bloodline and a dreadful mortal bodily strength. With them you can actually surpass the boundaries of your Laws and block my strike. Still, what I said remains true. The Laws you cultivate are too grand and you cannot control them. Facing the incarnation of the Heavenly Dao, you will still lose to me!”

The mysterious woman caressed the black sword’s blade. The black sword emitted a bass howl like a dragon.

In the next moment, she slashed out her sword once more. Sword light tore through the void. This time it was no longer a thin line but a 10 foot wide column of divine light. This divine light of the Great Dao ripped open the void, pouring downwards!

It was clear that this sword light was far stronger than the condensed finger-thin sword light from before!

Lin Ming gripped the Black Dragon Spear, staring right at the sword light. A brilliant divine light burst from his eyes like a crackle of thunder. He sneered.

“So what if you’re the incarnation of the Heavenly Dao? Defying the will of the heavens, it’s not as if this is my first or second time.”

In that instant, Lin Ming cried out loud. His muscles rapidly grew and his joints emitted explosive crackling sounds. His body grew taller as black scales began appearing all over him.

His hair grew longer, turning blood red. Above his two hands, the phantom of a True Dragon and True Phoenix appeared. Behind him the Asura war god holding the black wheel appeared!

Lin Ming had activated the power of the Asura blood. For a time, the Asura Laws shook, affecting the entire mirror world!

After all, the heaven and earth origin energy within this mirror world was all controlled by the Asura Laws. Now that Lin Ming galvanized the Asura blood within him, it caused the surrounding Laws to resonate with him!

Bang!

With a terrifying explosion, Lin Ming grasped the Black Dragon Spear and smashed it onto the mysterious woman’s sword light!

The brilliant sword light was sundered in half by Lin Ming’s strike!

A storm of energy wildly swept outwards!

“What!? This is!!!?”

Outside of the Cold Ice Mirror, everyone watching was bewildered.

The aura that Lin Ming released just then was similar to their ancestors’!

“Impossible… isn’t he a human!? How come the feeling he gives off is a bloodline at least a hundred times purer than our god race’s!”

Diwuhen’s voice trembled as he spoke. After becoming an extreme Empyrean, there was little that could shake his composure like this.

But now, with the great calamity before them and the life or death of his people on the line, in the darkness when they couldn’t find the path to take, they had discovered that Lin Ming had an aura similar to their ancestors’. How could they not be excited!

This was because the bloodline of their primal god race had been at its most magnificent 10 billion years ago, when their ancestors ruled all. From that point on, they had slowly declined as their reproductive abilities grew worse and worse.

If the current primal god race could recover their bloodline from 10 billion years ago, they might also be able to recover their glory from 10 billion years ago!

“Incredible, how could this be?”

To Bagui was also left shell-shocked.

Their celestial race originated from the Asura lineage, and in the past he had gone to the land of inheritance for those of the Asura lineage.

The inheritance totem in that land was similar to the present Lin Ming.

And, what was even more inconceivable was that the aura on Lin Ming’s body seemed even purer than the inheritance totem, making them want to kneel and prostrate themselves before him!

“This Lin Ming, just what is he…”

Everyone glanced at each other. Lin Ming was simply a box of riddles.

He was the first to understand the Asura Heavenly Dao and have the ability to repair god decrees.

Then, he had displayed a combat strength far surpassing his boundary. Now he revealed his Asura bloodline.

Before this, even when Lin Ming was able to repair god decrees, Smokeless was still able to maintain a faint arrogance in front of him. This was because she was part of the ancient races, and she was proud of her bloodline!

Even though her race’s bloodline had already declined from the past, it still wasn’t something that other races like the humans, saints, or spiritas could compare with. Her people could naturally use the power of divinity and they had a superior talent for cultivation. They were a proud race.

But now, facing Lin Ming’s Asura blood, Smokeless felt that her own bloodline was nothing but a little firefly in front of the brilliant moon, simply not worthy of mentioning at all.

All of her previous pride and ego had been crushed. She was thoroughly ashamed of herself.

As everyone was shocked, Lin Ming hurtled forwards. He opened the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, the Heretical God Force erupting to its limits!

Fighting intent fused onto the Black Dragon Spear. Lin Ming became one with his spear, shooting towards the mysterious woman like a blazing meteor.

The mysterious woman grasped her peerless black sword, a light leaping into her watery eyes.

A thin layer of divine light covered her body. She wielded her sword and thrust it towards Lin Ming’s Black Dragon Spear.

Bang!

Spear and sword crossed. The void shattered, breaking open like an endlessly growing spider web.

The mysterious woman was forced backwards. Her hair flew up and her cloak fluttered about her. She finally stabilized herself after drawing back several hundred feet.

As she held her black sword, a wisp of blood flowed out from between her slender jade fingers.

This wisp of blood was like a red plum blossom blooming in stark white snow, containing a monstrously alluring beauty!

“I didn’t think you’d have such strength…”

The mysterious woman’s expression finally changed. As she looked at Lin Ming, a strange light appeared in her eyes.

“The blood of Asura. It seems you have already obtained a part of his true legacy.”

The mysterious woman had used the word ‘his’.

The ‘his’ she referred to was naturally the Asura Road Master.

But this term caused Lin Ming to feel confused. The Asura Road Master, just how was he related to this woman before him?

Chapter 1890 - Veil

Lin Ming could confirm that this mysterious woman before him really did exist 10 billion years ago.

She was a phantom, an illusion left behind by an ancient genius. Rather, perhaps it could be said that her strength and her Laws hadn’t been adjusted by the array formation but completely reflected her past state.

Such a peerless character, just what was her identity?

Her eyes were so similar to Sheng Mei’s. If so, then beneath that veil, would her face also be the same as Sheng Mei’s?

Lin Ming’s eyes were brilliant as he looked at the woman, as if his gaze and sense could pierce through her concealment. Unfortunately, no matter how he tried he couldn’t see past the Laws that covered her veil.

After being stared at so impolitely by Lin Ming, the mysterious woman didn’t seem to care at all. She raised the black sword in her hand and wiped the sliver of blood that had leaked from her jade-like hands onto it.

This caused Lin Ming to be startled.

However, when the blood was smeared across the sword’s blade, another shocking incident occurred. The black sword absorbed it like a sponge absorbing water, and in the next moment, the sword blade changed color, from black to red!

The sword glowed blood red, as if it had been soaking in a blood pond for thousands of years.

The sword blade revolved with the aura of the Great Dao. A bass rumbling sound echoed in it, as if wild demons were roaring out from within.

In that moment, the mysterious woman’s aura changed once more.

It was no longer ethereal, but now it was filled with… killing intent!

Her vision turned sharp and fierce, piercing through the void!

As her eyes locked onto Lin Ming, the mysterious woman said, “Asura’s legacy, are you his descendant? Good, I have waited in the Cold Ice Mirror for so many years, and I’ve long been wanting to experience your strength. Let me see just what sort of character the lineage of Asura is like!”

This mysterious woman’s voice held a light taunting tone. Her words left Lin Ming shocked.

“Let me see just what sort of character the lineage of Asura is like?”

These words were clearly dripping with disdain. It seemed that this mysterious woman had a grudge with the lineage of Asura?

It wasn’t just Lin Ming, but Diwuhen, To Bagui, and the others outside were all bewildered. They originally believed that this mysterious woman had some significant relation to the Asura Road Master, perhaps even his wife, concubine, daughter, true lineage disciple, or something similar to that. Otherwise, how could she possibly be so mind-numbingly strong?

But now it seemed that she was opposed to the Asura Road Master.

If they were opposed, how would she appear in the Cold Ice Mirror?

Before they could think of a possibility, the mysterious woman had already lashed out.

After being dyed with her fresh blood, her blade had reached incomprehensible levels of speed!

This sword strike didn’t bloom with any sword light. But, that bright red sword blade seemed to come to life, as if a blood pond from hell was sealed within it, containing infinite killing intent!

Facing this sword, Lin Ming felt as if his life force would be cut apart by the blade; this would be impossible to survive.

“This is… death?”

Lin Ming was alarmed. The move that the mysterious woman displayed contained inherent Laws that didn’t come from the Asura Road Master, but came from the Holy Scripture!

“Holy Scripture – death book!?”

Lin Ming was panic-stricken. Still, even though he was shocked his movements didn’t slow down.

The Black Dragon Spear howled, carrying with it the supernatural might of the Asura blood. Laws gathered upon it, violently clashing with the mysterious woman!

His cultivation was lower than hers, but by relying on the great power of his bloodline and his mortal bodily strength, he didn’t fall behind at all.

The woman’s sword cut apart life force, but Lin Ming’s blood vitality was like a fiercely blazing sun. It simply could not be cut in half, could not be extinguished.

However, the longer the battle continued, the more startled Lin Ming became.

The mysterious woman’s understandings of the Holy Scripture’s Life and Death Concepts had already completely surpassed Lin Ming’s imagination, reaching unbelievable heights!

Although the mysterious woman had said he would be defeated no matter what, Lin Ming had thought little of it. But, there was one point she was right about.

That was that the Laws Lin Ming cultivated were far too vast. He cultivated essence, energy, and divine, and the inner and outer universes. It could be said that Lin Ming was dabbling with every Great Dao in the world!

In this sort of situation, with Lin Ming’s low cultivation it was impossible for him to have deep attainments.

From either the Heavenly Sutra or Holy Scripture, Lin Ming had only comprehended the tip of the iceberg. If he wanted to fuse the two of them any time soon, that would be impossible.

If so, then facing this mysterious woman who only cultivated the inner universe, when it came to Laws, Lin Ming certainly fell into a disadvantage.

Bang!

A terrifying explosion rang through the world. Lin Ming and the mysterious woman clashed once more.

The two of them drew backwards. The entire surrounding sky had been devastated as if a hammer had been smashing onto a pane of glass, splitting the skies open again and again.

The mysterious woman’s complexion was flushed with blood. The wound on her hand grew, with more and more blood streaming out.

As for Lin Ming, scales had broken all over his body and his inner aura was in disorder.

This was a brutal battle.

On both sides, one was an ancient genius and one was a modern genius. Moreover, they were evenly matched!

Outside the Cold Ice Mirror, Smokeless was long since unable to express the shock she felt. Just the mysterious woman’s titanic strength left her crying out in praise. But what was even more incredible was that in the current era of martial arts that had long since declined, how could a miracle like Lin Ming be born in the 33 Heavens?

This was really a battle between Holy Lord realm opponents?

“You… your Laws are lower than mine, and your cultivation is lower than mine, yet you can fight to a draw with me. I believe this is because you utilize the power of the Asura blood. But soon you will exhaust your strength. I don’t think your blood vitality can remain so potent for much longer. Your life force is exuberant so you have lasted until now, but… you don’t seem as if you can drag things out to a 1000 breaths of time?”

There was still a long time until 1000 breaths of time passed. And as the mysterious woman said, because Lin Ming had used the Asura blood and erupted with so much power, he consumed his strength that much more quickly. Even though he had a terrifying endurance ability, it would be difficult for him to continue this battle much longer.

“If things continue like this, then you can last for another 100 breaths of time before my attacks wear down the rest of your strength. If so, then I will have won by default. However, I don’t wish for this to happen. I want to defeat you while you are still propped up by the power of the Asura blood and defeat you at your full strength!”

As the mysterious woman spoke, her black hair fluttered upwards and a dao pagoda appeared behind her.

This dao pagoda had six levels, and the pagoda seemed to be suppressing countless races, gods, and even demons.

After the dao pagoda appeared, the mysterious woman’s aura rapidly climbed to an astonishing height. Moreover, this time it was no longer just the Concept of Life or just the Concept of Death, but a fusion of them both.

The mysterious woman had never attacked with the fused power of life and death. But now, she was going to attack with the entirety of her strength. In fact, with her present cultivation it was incredibly difficult for her to perfectly fuse together the Concepts of Life and Death, but once she did, then with her profound attainments in the Laws the power behind this strike could be imagined.

Facing this strike, Lin Ming’s complexion was solemn. Two figures rushed out from his inner world, standing beside him. These were his avatars.

With the appearance of these two avatars, the mysterious woman was left stunned. “Essence, energy, soul, three embryonic bodies, of them, you have two… to think your Asura Heavenly Dao was originally already cultivated to such a degree. I suppose your next step will be to fuse together the Laws of the 33 Heavens. Really, you have surprised me. However, that is as far as you go. You cannot block my final strike. You have already consumed more than half of your strength, but I am still gathering my potential to strike you with everything I have!”

No matter what the mysterious woman said, it didn’t affect her attack.

The majestic dao pagoda carried with it the ancient and boundless will of the Great Dao as it came hurtling down at Lin Ming!

“Life and Death Samsara!”

The mysterious woman brought her hands down. Like a star crashing to earth, the vastness of space seemed to fall down with it!

For a time, the surrounding void was completely fixed in place. The entire mirror world seemed to have solidified, making it impossible to struggle.

In that moment, Lin Ming moved.

He knew just how dreadful this woman’s attack was and he didn’t plan to avoid it in the least. He grasped the Black Dragon Spear and hurtled towards it!

The mysterious woman had spoken correctly. Even if Lin Ming displayed his full strength and burned his blood essence, he still wouldn’t be a match for this strike!

Whether it was the Holy Scripture or Heavenly Sutra, the degree to which Lin Ming cultivated them was far inferior to the mysterious woman!

With the great disparity between their Laws as well as the massive amount of strength he had already used up, he would lose without a doubt!

Then, in that moment, Lin Ming made a decision – he planned to simultaneously use the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra Laws!

But… to simultaneously use two Laws, that was the same as unifying the Heavenly Sutra and Holy Scripture. Wasn’t that easier said than done?

With Lin Ming’s current cultivation and his comprehension of Laws, it was impossible for him to achieve this.

However, he had another method.

He didn’t need to completely fuse together the two great Laws. Rather, he only needed to temporarily join them together for use.

He himself couldn’t use the two Laws at the same time, but… he had his avatars!

At that instant, Lin Ming moved!

He burned his blood essence. His blood vitality boiled over, growing without end. And then in the next moment, it returned to a deathly silence!

These were the Concepts of Life and Death. They rushed through his body along with the ten golden pages and the Laws he had grasped atop the shrine platform at the Fallen God Mountain Range. Everything ran through his heart like a raging river.

And at the same time, on both sides, his two avatars revolved their energies accordingly. The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel and Myriad Essence Reincarnation Wheel revolved in their hands.

With his true self as the inner universe and his two avatars as the outer universe, together they simultaneously utilized the two Laws. Like this, all of Lin Ming’s strengths erupted to their limits!

This was also the strongest attack that Lin Ming could use!

Woosh!

The Black Dragon Spear howled, guiding the two great Laws and Lin Ming’s martial arts will to fire towards the mysterious woman.

“What? Not only do you understand the Holy Scripture but you’ve cultivated it to such a degree!?”

The mysterious woman was startled. She never thought Lin Ming, who had fallen into a perilous state and would lose without a doubt, during his final moments would actually use the Holy Scripture Laws and fuse them together with the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws to emit such a terrifying strike!

Lin Ming’s Laws were inferior to her own, but by combining these two Laws together, he was able to make up for the disparity!

At this time, the mysterious woman had no time to think about how Lin Ming, as the descendant to the Asura legacy, would have managed to cultivate the Holy Scripture to such a degree, nor did she have time to discern whose attack was stronger. At this moment all she could do was attack with everything she had, striking out with the God Demon Samsara Pagoda!

Rumble rumble rumble!

The Samsara Pagoda howled, crushing the world!

But facing this titanic force, Lin Ming showed no fear. Holding the Black Dragon Spear, he broke into the pagoda!

The Samsara Pagoda violently shook. Countless runes broke apart, disintegrating!

As for the gods, demons, and intelligent lives sealed within the pagoda, they were also killed off by the terrifying spear light!

Laws danced in the air. Energy howled. Lin Ming’s mortal body forcefully withstood with dreadful energy storm. The black scales that covered his body splintered off, dripping with blood!

But by relying on his will alone, he courageously moved forwards, unstoppable!

Peng! Peng! Peng!

Floor after floor of the God Demon Samsara Pagoda was pierced through by Lin Ming!

In that intense collision, Lin Ming’s arms were left covered with blood. The bones of his arms nearly revealed themselves beneath his wounds. But he grit his teeth, recklessly rushing forth.

“Open for me!”

Lin Ming roared. The roof of the Samsara Pagoda violently exploded open and Lin Ming broke out like an unsealed dragon, soaring into the air!

Gripping the Black Dragon Spear, his momentum was like a ray of light, thrusting straight towards the mysterious woman’s throat!

His speed reached the extreme. With the Samsara Pagoda broken and her attack just used, the mysterious woman couldn’t summon any new energy; it was impossible for her to defend!

Seeing Lin Ming’s disheveled hair and his entire body stained with blood, he rushed forwards like an ominous Asura war god. The mysterious woman’s complexion paled!

Even with the absolute disparity between the depths of their Laws, Lin Ming had actually managed to break through her Life and Death Samsara!

His terrifying conviction and momentum left her bewildered.

The Black Dragon Spear’s spear point was already less than ten feet away from her jade-white neck; she could already feel the chilling cold of the spear point in the air.

In the next thousandth of the moment, her protective power of divinity would be relentlessly torn open by the Black Dragon Spear and her throat would be pierced through!

Even if she had far more strength remaining than Lin Ming, even if her background was far deeper than Lin Ming’s, facing this spear light, none of that was useful!

Peng!

With an explosive sound, the mysterious woman’s protective power of divinity shattered open. The Black Dragon Spear continued unabated!

Her face paled. But, she didn’t cry out in alarm; she simply closed her eyes.

Yet in that last moment, Lin Ming veered the angle of his spear point, changing the trajectory so that the spear instead scratched the mysterious woman’s cheek!

The mysterious woman simply felt a cool feeling pass her face. Startled, she subconsciously traced her cheek. She discovered that her veil had been torn away by the Black Dragon Spear!

A trace of blood flowed down her cheek.

And at this time, Lin Ming had already rushed past the mysterious woman like a bolt of lightning.

The veil had been torn to pieces by the Black Dragon Spear’s terrifying spear light. Lin Ming himself continued for another thousand feet before he came to a stop in the void. He fell to his knees, nearly every drop of his strength used up.

He was no longer able to maintain the power of the Asura blood. The shattered scales on Lin Ming’s body slowly faded back into him. With a deep breath, he turned around and looked towards the mysterious woman.

The mysterious woman’s back was to him. Her cloak was ripped apart and there were many tears in her clothes. But, she didn’t look distressed or embarrassed at all. Rather, she gave off a chilling and poignant atmosphere.

The mysterious woman slowly turned around and looked at Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s final act of mercy had allowed her to live. Although Lin Ming no longer had the strength to fight back, she knew that she had been defeated.

“You… are truly incredible. Even though your strength is beneath mine, you were actually the one to win…”

As the woman spoke, Lin Ming also saw her face. Her appearance was as perfect as a bright moon, almost completely similar to Sheng Mei’s…

Chapter 1891 – Reward

“Just who are you…”

Lin Ming looked at the mysterious woman. After tearing off her veil with the Black Dragon Spear, he was able to confirm the guess he had all along. Her appearance was almost an exact copy of Sheng Mei’s, and it was impossible for such a coincidence to occur.

This woman had some unknown connection to Sheng Mei.

Was Sheng Mei also someone from the god race?

As this thought crossed through Lin Ming’s mind, he immediately thought it impossible.

In his impression, Sheng Mei cultivated spirit essence as well as the cultivation methods of the spiritas. If she was someone from the god race, she would have cultivated the power of divinity. This would have made her even stronger.

The mysterious woman looked to Lin Ming and faintly smiled. “You asked who I am. Is there a meaning to that? You and I are divided by the endless river of time, we have never crossed paths…”

As the woman spoke, she turned to leave.

But at this time, Lin Ming said, “I have seen a woman. Her appearance is exactly the same as yours. And, she is someone from my era.”

Lin Ming’s words caused the woman to pause. She turned around and stared at Lin Ming with surprise.

“Is that so…”

The woman’s voice was light and airy, without any hint of what she was thinking in her heart. She stepped upon the wind and vanished into the boundless mirror world, melting into the world and disappearing without a trace.

Lin Ming watched as the mysterious woman left. For a long time he remained silent.

The mysterious woman’s appearance was a mystery left behind in Lin Ming’s heart.

Sheng Mei’s life, just what had she gone through?

Lin Ming recalled that after he finished cultivating in the ancient galactic battlefield of the Akashic Dream Universe, he had run into the Soul Emperor, and then afterwards he had met Sheng Mei.

Sheng Mei asked him whether or not he was willing to abandon humanity and leave alone with her, going to some distant place for a hundred million years.

At that time, Sheng Mei seemed to have things she couldn’t bring up.

But Lin Ming also had things he couldn’t lay down. Thus, he chose to refuse her.

Now, in this Asura forbidden land, Lin Ming recalled all the words that Sheng Mei had said to him and had various thoughts in his heart.

All these complicated ideas gathered together, and Lin Ming didn’t know where the truth lay.

As for Sheng Mei, he didn’t know when they would next be able to meet, or whether he would be able to ask her all the questions he had.

“Lin Ming, are you okay!”

Outside of the Cold Ice Mirror, Diwuhen and the others rushed over, all of them unable to calm their mood.

In particular, the god race martial artists; they understood that the primal god race had really picked up a treasure this time.

Lin Ming took the saints as his enemy. His appearance had brought a tremendously favorable turn for the god race.

“That last spear strike, does it have a name?”

Smokeless asked. Before that final strike she had thought Lin Ming was likely to lose. But in the final showdown, the battle had experienced a sudden reversal. That spear strike was simply stunning!

Lin Ming shook his head. At this time, he felt something. He looked up into the skies.

Within the skies of the mirror world, the floating sphere of light was falling down towards Lin Ming.

For a time, everyone held their breath. They knew that this sphere of light was Lin Ming’s reward!

People didn’t know what this reward was, but they could feel the terrifying aura of a true emperor rolling off from it.

As if the grade of this treasure already surpassed the True Divinity level.

“Could this be an ultimate weapon used by the Asura Road Master?”

Everyone thought, their eyes earnest and curious. Although this was Lin Ming’s treasure and wasn’t too related to them, they were still all excited at the chance of being able to experience such a divine object.

The sphere of light slowly fell into Lin Ming’s palm, gradually manifesting into reality.

Everyone looked closely. All they saw was that the space in Lin Ming’s palm seemed to have collapsed. Infinite energy wrapped around Lin Ming’s palm, as if he were holding a universe within his grasp.

And in the center of this universe was a black vortex that sucked in all light as well as isolated out everyone’s senses. No matter how hard they tried, they couldn’t see what was within.

However, Lin Ming had a faint feeling of what it was. The energy in his palm caused him to feel a summoning from the Laws.

If it was said that he was grasping a universe in his palm, that wasn’t wrong. Yet this was no ordinary universe, but a self-made inner universe.

Contained within was the inherent aura of the Laws – these were the Existence Laws.

It was like countless lives were born and then extinguished in this universe, life and death spinning round and round…

In a flash, all the aura of the Laws converged. Lin Ming finally realized that the truth was the object in his palm was a drop of blood.

This was the blood drop of a great emperor. It exuded an endlessly terrifying aura, floating up and down like a star.

Within it was the deep meaning of the Life and Death Laws as well as the dreadful will of a great emperor.

The aura of this blood drop was extremely familiar to Lin Ming. And, this familiarity caused his mind to shake.

In the Akashic Dream Universe, from the golden pages that Lin Ming had obtained, the aura within those pages was the exact same as that exuding from this drop of blood.

If he wasn’t wrong, then this drop of blood was left behind by the creator of the Holy Scripture.

“It’s not Asura blood, but blood of the Holy Scripture creator…”

This left Lin Ming extremely shocked.

Why would blood from the creator of the Holy Scripture be left in the Asura Road Master’s forbidden land?

Lin Ming couldn’t help but recall the grand battle he had witnessed in the ancient galactic battlefield between the Asura Road Master and the creator of the Holy Scripture.

In that battle, the creator of the Holy Scripture had been wounded by the Asura Road Master. The Holy Scripture had shattered and he had lost a great deal of his divine blood.

Could it be that the Asura Road Master collected the divine blood from the Holy Scripture creator and sealed it away in his own forbidden land so that his successors could take it as their lucky chance?

Lin Ming stared at this drop of blood. This was no ordinary drop of blood, but was the essence congealed from a tremendous amount of blood.

After 10 billion years, not only had the essence energy within it not diminished, but because of the Laws of Life and Death, it actually grew stronger and stronger, like an aged wine. The more time passed, the more precious it would become.

“I have already absorbed the Asura blood. If I absorbed a drop of blood from the creator of the Holy Scripture, what would happen then?”

Lin Ming hesitated for a moment. The drop of blood fell onto his palm and melted into his body without the slightest ripple.

He planned to absorb and refine this drop of blood here. By doing so, he would be stronger in case there something else he needed to face in this Asura forbidden land.

As for Diwuhen and the others, since their interests were so closely intertwined with his own, they would naturally serve as his protectors.

Lin Ming sat cross-legged in the void, calmly composing himself. He felt the great currents of energy within his body. At this time, within his spiritual sea, dreadful waves were rising up into the air.

In that moment it was like he hadn’t fused with a drop of blood, but had fused with a vast and profound universe.

This drop of blood seemed to have numerous trembling galaxies, trillions of stars glistening together.

Each star was a complex and exhausting character. With the countless stars gathered together, they formed an endless scripture.

On this ancient scripture, there was a dim figure sitting above it all.

Just by sitting there, he seemed to be sitting in the infinite past, sitting at the end of all time. It was like he had died, without the least bit of life vitality.

Around him, the limitless void began to shake and collapse. Death energy lingered around him without end.

Massive galaxies were annihilated beneath his feet, decaying to tatters, turned into ashes that scattered in the icy cold of space.

At this time, the ancient scripture gently shivered and began to emit a gentle, luminous light. At the end of this universe, standing in hazy opposition, there was another silhouette.

This figure was that of a woman.

Compared to the man that seemed dead, this woman was as bright as a moon. Her body exuded a magnificent brilliance. Each wisp of brilliance that she released seemed to have a small figure sitting within it, chanting holy texts and filling the air with life. Her light swept through the galaxies, illuminating the pitch black cosmos.

Covered by the curtain of her light, many dim and gloomy stars began to shine with a potent life force. Many of the dead stars began to experience a wondrous change. Grass filled with life burst out from the ground and towering trees drilled up from the rocks. Birds flew through the wide skies and beasts galloped through the fields. Leviathans swam through the waters, submerging and stretching out without end…

“A single drop of blood contained the two different mystic strengths and boundaries of life and death. They oppose each other, but coexist in the same universe…” Lin Ming began to enlighten himself on this ancient sutra, his mind seeming to have risen above the mortal coil.

This blood contained the deep meanings behind the Holy Scripture. Compared to the golden pages, it was even more precious!

This was an extraordinary lucky chance! The advantages that this had for Lin Ming comprehending the Laws of the inner universe were unimaginable!

“Before this, I’ve only looked at the life section of the Holy Scripture. In other words, the golden pages. But, I’ve never looked at the death pages. Yet this drop of blood has not only deepened my understanding of the life pages but also allowed me to faintly extrapolate what is contained in the death pages, obtaining a deeper meaning of death…”

Lin Ming had once grasped the principles upon the shrine platform at the Phantom God Spirit Cliff. He had resonated with the world and had seen many different sceneries of time. His comprehensions of the Holy Scripture were no trifling matter.

Now, within his spiritual sea, some of those golden page texts that he hadn’t yet comprehended began to rumble, resonating with the mysterious and vibrant power within the blood he had absorbed.

Lin Ming knew to take advantage of this chance. The Daevic Eye Dao Palace opened and a dazzling light shot out, bringing with it a power that could pierce through all mysteries, shining upon the ancient scriptures.

Some obscure and unknown texts began to shine. The mists that shrouded them retreated, revealing a cold and weak light beneath it all.

This cold light was bizarre. Although it was weak, it continued without end, like an eternal flame that would never extinguish. It shot through the endless darkness… slowly breaking through time and space until it reached the Soul World and then delved into the Akashic Dream Universe.

As the mysterious Akashic Dream Universe was shot through with this cold light, from all parts of the Akashic Dream Universe, wisps of incomparably pure and boundless mystic power shot back out, following the path of the cold light and gathering into Lin Ming’s mind.

Bang!

Lin Ming’s entire body shook. From his flesh and blood, light began to emit, resonating with the ancient scriptures all around him, completely enveloping him.

This strange light was black on one side and white on the other, like a yin yang diagram. It contained the true meanings of life and death as it wrapped around Lin Ming…

Gradually, the Laws turned into a black and white cocoon of light.

Nestled within, Lin Ming would beat with life from time to time, and other times he would be deathly still…

Chapter 1892 – Peak Holy Lord

Within the cocoon, Lin Ming experienced a long, long dream. In this dream, he witnessed a great calamity sweep through cosmos!

The scale of this great calamity was far more terrifying than the invasion of god race by the saints; it was one that affected nearly every race in every universe!

He saw demons rampaging, he saw countless lives perishing, trillions of quadrillions of miles of space being wiped clean of life as great worlds were destroyed one after another.

This horror of this calamity even changed the rules of the Heavenly Dao. It caused some universes within the 33 Heavens to be annihilated of civilization, turned to wilderness…

And this era was the era in which the Asura Road Master and the creator of the Holy Scripture lived.

Lin Ming seemed to pass through 10 billion years of time to witness all of this.

There were blurred fragments, but the scenes within left Lin Ming shocked beyond comprehension.

Those dreadful devils overwhelmed the skies. The worst amongst them were Holy Lords, and there were countless additional World King and Great World King demons.

Not just that, but there were numerous Empyrean level and True Divinity level demons.

The greatest powerhouses of the ancient races fiercely warred with these demons, exhausting all of their energy.

Many races were completely exterminated…

But for humans, saints, and spiritas, during this time they were still small races. Through virtue of their weakness they survived and multiplied, slowly seizing the 33 Heavens and developing their own martial arts civilization.

The accumulated wisdom of the universe declined, but rose again and began to vigorously flourish…

This process was like the alternating pattern of life and death.

Glory was life, destruction was death…

Lin Ming felt that without a doubt, the scenes he saw were memories within the drop of blood.

“These demons… are they the so-called abyssal devils? The Primeval Realm that stands separate from the 33 Heavens… could it be the entrance connecting the abyss and the 33 Heavens?”

This explanation was the most reasonable. The Primeval Realm was likely to be the entrance to the abyss, thus it wasn’t able to be destroyed. This was why it remained for 10 billion years, eventually becoming a ruin.

“The boundless universe, all lives in the cosmos, the civilization of martial arts… in this world, nothing can escape the samsara of life and death. Life and Death Laws are the most common Laws in the universe; they are everywhere. If so, then can the Law of Eternal Life really exist?”

All sorts of thoughts flashed through Lin Ming’s mind. Unconsciously, he saw his mortal body slowly fuse together with the blood cocoon, gradually transforming.

On the surface of the blood cocoon, innumerable runes appeared. They faintly circulated with a bright light, emitting a dense rosy glow.

This scene continued for an unknown period of time. At a certain moment, the Asura Laws within the mirror world began to gather together.

These Law fragments formed a giant vortex that funneled into the blood cocoon. At the same time, in the blood cocoon, the Asura blood within Lin Ming began to resonate with the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws!

Hum –

A dreadful sound reverberated outwards. From time to time, black scales appeared on Lin Ming’s body and then hid themselves again. His joints emitted crackling explosive sounds as if the Asura blood within him was violently clashing with the blood of the Holy Scripture creator.

The two different bloodlines waged war with each other, nearly taking Lin Ming’s body as their battlefield.

An agonizing pain echoed through Lin Ming like a tide. His flesh and blood tore apart again and again, collapsing and disintegrating. A massive amount of blood leaked out, flowing into the cocoon.

At that moment, it was like Lin Ming’s body was soaked within a blood pond.

However, even watching his body being ruined, Lin Ming’s heart was as still as placid water, without any panic at all.

This was similar to the deep meanings of the Life and Death Laws. To break something down and then reform it. Without experiencing destruction, how could one experience new life?

As for those endless waves of pain, Lin Ming relied on his willpower to endure every last bit of it. Thus, even in such a situation he was able to remain in an ethereal condition.

His cultivation rapidly rose!

He instantly broke past the barrier of the late Holy Lord realm. But, his cultivation continued to dramatically increase!

His mortal body continued to break down, until even white bone was exposed. Lin Ming only staunchly defended his inner world and spiritual sea, allowing his mortal body to undergo all of these transformations and allowing the two surging energies within him to continue washing away his meridians.

He believed that these two strengths within him would inevitably fuse together. Otherwise, wouldn’t the Asura Road Master have left behind a death trap in his forbidden land instead of a reward? If his successor who inherited the Asura Heavenly Dao legacy was to obtain this drop of blood from the creator of the Holy Scripture, would it really be poison?

The pain of fusion continued for a long time. Lin Ming’s flesh and blood, and even the black scales, slowly rotted away, scorched black until they finally fell off.

But beneath this ruined flesh and blood was new flesh and blood, crystalline and pure white, like warm jade.

Ten days passed. The Asura Heavenly Dao Laws had completely gathered into the blood cocoon.

And at this time, with a snapping sound, a visible crack presented itself on the surface of the blood cocoon.

Diwuhen and the others had been constantly keeping watch over the surroundings. As they noticed this change, they all turned to look. Lin Ming was emerging!

The blood cocoon split a little at a time until it completely tore open. Within, Lin Ming was sitting down, drenched in blood and mucus.

Feeling the aura of the outside Laws, Lin Ming opened his eyes and slowly stood up. His clothing had already been completely destroyed but his body was wrapped in the light of the Great Dao Laws. He looked like a blazing sun, making one unable to see him clearly.

“Has he already refined the blood?”

Diwuhen muttered.

“He should have. It’s really enough for anyone to feel envy…”

A complex look flashed in To Bagui’s eyes. While he didn’t know which ancient peerless character had left behind this drop of blood, in terms of quality it had already completely surpassed the limits of his understanding. Such a lucky chance, how could he not envy it?

At this time, the light of the Great Dao condensed, forming into new clothes that draped over Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s cultivation had unexpectedly risen to the peak Holy Lord realm!

The blood of two existences that were Beyond Divinity had violently clashed within his body, the fallout causing Lin Ming’s cultivation to rise to the late Holy Lord realm and break past it into the peak Holy Lord realm!

Such a rapid pace of cultivation had never been experienced even by Lin Ming.

Diwuhen, Smokeless, To Bagui, and the others were all left incomparably shocked. “Peak Holy Lord?”

“This is too fast! Even a genius often needs several hundred years to rise from the middle Holy Lord to peak Holy Lord realm…”

“But to surpass two small boundaries all of a sudden, would that make his foundation unstable?”

Everyone wondered, worried. No matter which race, their geniuses always suppressed their cultivations to temper their comprehension of Laws.

Otherwise, if one’s cultivation rose too quickly but their Laws couldn’t follow them, then the gains simply weren’t worth the losses.

For instance, take a martial artist that cultivated the Fire Laws. If they entered into the Holy Lord realm after comprehending the sixth level Concept of Fire as opposed to entering the Holy Lord realm after comprehending the seventh level Concept of Fire, the effects of entering the Holy Lord realm would naturally be completely different between the two.

This was especially true for Lin Ming. The Laws he cultivated were far too vast and his understandings into them weren’t profound enough. If he couldn’t gain a deep comprehension of these Laws and made cultivation breakthroughs rapidly and randomly, that would inevitably affect his future achievements.

Towards all of this, Lin Ming remained silent.

Indeed, his cultivation boundary had risen far too fast. From the early Holy Lord realm to the peak Holy Lord realm, he had only used a mere several dozen years. Compared to other geniuses, he was at least ten times faster!

He would have to make up for the consequences of having his cultivation progress so rapidly. In other words, Lin Ming would have to spend a long, long time at the peak Holy Lord realm before he broke into the World King realm.

Breaking into the World King realm would be an important step in Lin Ming’s road of martial arts. He couldn’t be even the least bit careless about it.

Then, Lin Ming examined his body.

He discovered his inner world had expanded yet again. The size of his inner world was actually much broader than many World King level powerhouses’ inner worlds. Even so, Lin Ming could feel that within his body, the two strengths which belonged to the Asura Road Master and Holy Scripture creator still stood opposite to each other like water and oil, unable to fuse.

They each occupied a part of Lin Ming’s body, faintly opposing each other with equal force.

“Indeed… wanting to fuse these two strengths together is far, far too hard…”

Lin Ming sighed. The road he wanted to walk down was one that no one had ever walked down even in 10 billion years.

To many geniuses, if they could only cultivate their inner or outer universe and bring it to the limit, that was already an unimaginable achievement.

And wanting to fuse the two together, that was just the wishful thinking of a crazed idiot.

Lin Ming had a faint premonition that these two strengths were lying in ambush deep within his body. If he couldn’t fuse them together then they would slowly develop with time. For himself, this might be an extremely dangerous matter…

To fuse together two Laws that were Beyond Divinity, as well as to consolidate his foundation and break into the World King realm…

These two brutally difficult missions were like two large mountains that lay in front of Lin Ming’s road of martial arts. To cross over them one at a time, that was easier said than done.

“At the very least… it will take a hundred years to consolidate my foundation and break into the World King realm. But a hundred years from now, just what sort of situation will the Divine Realm be in?”

Lin Ming silently thought to himself, gripping his fists.

Chapter 1893 – Six Supreme Treasures

After Lin Ming absorbed the blood essence from the Holy Scripture creator, the earth began to shake. The massive Cold Ice Mirror that stood tall in the world started to descend, falling back into the earth.

And at the same time, in front of Lin Ming and the others’ eyes, a blue stone road appeared. This blue stone road rose into the skies, and at the end, a shrine emerged.

This shrine was old, emitting the aura of endless years. It had floated in the skies for an unimaginable span of time.

Around the shrine was a giant array formation. This array formation contained a terrifying energy. Thick chains wrapped around the shrine like black dragons, fixing the shrine in the skies.

The shrine should have already existed here, but it was covered by the Cold Ice Mirror before.

Everyone glanced at each other. Just what was in this shrine?

“This is the final road. If I’m not wrong, then this is the Asura Shrine recorded in the ancient texts of my god race. If there is a path to salvation in the Asura forbidden land, then it should be sealed within that Asura Shrine!”

Diwuhen suddenly said, his voice quivering. With the end so close, he couldn’t contain his excitement!

He felt a deep anticipation but also a deep fear.

He anticipated that there was something within the Asura Shrine which could turn the tide of war. But, he also feared that this was nothing but a one-sided wish from their side; he was afraid that there was no way to save their primal god race.

“This blue stone road, can we go up?”

Smokeless frowned. She felt that only Lin Ming had managed to pass the test of the Cold Ice Mirror and she had barely been able to mix herself into the pool of victors. As for the others, they weren’t close at all.

In this situation, did they have the qualifications to step into the final shrine?

Smokeless’ words caused Diwuhen to hesitate for a moment. He paused at the blue stone road and then carefully said, “The ancestors are merciful. Even if I have lost honor for the god race, I am still their flesh and blood descendant. With the destruction of our race arriving, even if we are useless trash the ancestors still shouldn’t be indifferent towards us and let us perish…”

As he spoke, Diwuhen raised his robes and knelt on the floor, deeply bowing towards the shrine.

Behind Diwuhen, Shenku, Lanlu, and the others also knelt, all of them deeply bowing towards the shrine.

After kneeling for ten breaths of time they stood up. Then, Diwuhen took a slow and careful step forwards and stepped onto the blue stone road. Finally, he discovered that he wasn’t forced back by the array formation.

Diwuhen was overjoyed. He stepped forwards, allowing the others to step onto the blue stone road.

“We can go.”

On this road, Diwuhen was covered with a strange feeling. It was like his entire being had become ethereal, as if he were withstanding a baptism of the endless Laws of the universe.

Shenku, Lanlu, and the others also followed up on the blue stone road.

Then there was Lin Ming. He looked at the blue stone road, finding it similar to the blue stone road he had encountered in the Asura Road’s final trial, within the planet-sized heavenly palace. The blue stone there had also contained the aura of Laws.

Everyone carefully moved towards the Asura Shrine.

The road didn’t seem too long, but everyone walked for an entire day.

They walked extremely slowly, allowing themselves to become aware of the Laws here as much as possible.

Finally, the six people neared the shrine.

Lifting their eyes, they saw the entire temple shrouded in blue light. There was a formidable energy contained within that grew endlessly, not seeming like it had experienced 10 billion years at all.

The great doors of the shrine were shut tight. But as the group neared, the doors swung open.

Diwuhen and To Bagui walked at the front, cautiously leading the way into the Asura Shrine.

There were no dangers within the shrine. Lin Ming could feel that the Laws here were peaceful; most of them were defensive array formations. As long as no one tried to destroy the shrine then there wouldn’t be any killing intent.

The passage leading into the shrine wasn’t too long. The six stepped in, their feet walking on tiles that had been untouched for countless hundreds of millions of years. Light pattering sounds echoed within.

At the end of the passage was a vast grand hall. This grand hall was over a thousand feet long and wide, similar to a city square.

The light of the Laws illuminated this hall, making the entire hall shine as if it were daytime within.

As the six people entered the grand hall, they could see an altar at the center.

This altar was only several dozen feet high, but had a stairway of nine steps. Each step was carved with beautiful images with faint, multi-hued lights sparkling from them, bursting with auspicious sights.

But at this time, no one bothered with the stairs. Instead, all of their eyes were focused on the skies above the altar.

There, floating in the air, were six items, each one of them completely different from the others.

Standing outside the altar, because of the light of the Laws and their shadows, it was hard for people to immediately discern what these six items were.

“What a powerful aura. These were left behind by the Asura Road Master!”

Lin Ming could confirm that these six items were not ordinary treasures at all!

Beside Lin Ming, Shenku, To Bagui, and the others were all panting loudly. Because of these precious treasures it was hard for them to suppress their mood.

These were supreme treasures from 10 billion years ago. Any one of them was countless times more precious than a True Divinity spirit treasure.

“Mm? There are words here…”

Smokeless suddenly said. Everyone followed her gaze to see that somewhere on the altar, there were words of the primal god race carved onto it.

No one present had a problem understanding the primal god race language; they soon understood what it meant.

It was the division of treasure.

Of the six treasures, only three could be chosen.

Of these three, one belonged to them all.

But as for two others, they belonged solely to the person who had passed the Cold Ice Mirror. In other words, they belonged to Lin Ming!

Seeing the rules of assignment, everyone glanced at Lin Ming with envy. To choose three treasures and for two of them to go to Lin Ming, this was truly enough to arouse one’s envy.

Of course, because of the protection of Laws in the Asura forbidden land, as well as the old God Sovereign’s support of Lin Ming, and also the immeasurable function that Lin Ming had in helping the ancient races survive this great calamity, no matter how much anyone envied Lin Ming, none of them would think about plotting against him.

“Choosing treasures!”

Diwuhen sucked in a deep breath, his voice shaking. The reason they came to the Asura forbidden land was for this moment.

Whether or not they could see a ray of hope in the dark, all of that would depend on what these treasures were.

The group slowly flew towards the altar. They could feel the vast power of Laws swell towards them like a wave.

The first treasure was facing the group; it was a large furnace.

This furnace was 30 feet high and had a simple and plain design. There were runes carved onto it, with a taotie diagram and all sorts of other flowers and birds.

These carvings didn’t seem exquisite at all. In fact, they appeared rather rough. Looking at the furnace there didn’t seem to be anything special about it, as if it were some common bronze antique found within the mortal world.

However, for this furnace to be placed here, everyone knew that it had to be some uncommon treasure. Without a doubt, it was likely some supreme magic tool that the Asura Road Master carried with him in the past.

“There are markings within the furnace!”

Smokeless suddenly said. Everyone looked in to see that within the furnace, there were dense small writings. These writings were in the language of the primal god race, each word flooded with the power of mystical Law runes. They were faint, seemingly covered with fog, making one unable to see them clearly.

“This furnace is a Beyond Divinity level supreme treasure.”

A brilliant light flashed in Lin Ming’s eyes. This furnace – he wanted it!

Not to mention the terrifying strength of the furnace itself, just the runes and writings within the furnace left him blinded with desire. If he could perceive them then the advantages would be unimaginable.

“What an excellent furnace…”

Diwuhen sighed in praise. But, he only looked. This furnace was precious, but it wasn’t enough to save their god race. Not to mention anything else, just its terrifying grade of Beyond Divinity meant that it wasn’t something the average person could operate.

Perhaps even an extreme Empyrean might only be able to display a few percent of the furnace’s power. How could anyone think of killing the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign with this alone?

The group continued to look.

On the side of the furnace was a pill box.

The pill box was completely sealed, as if there was a separate universe within.

Lin Ming didn’t know what pill it was nor could he smell the medicinal fragrance. Everything had been blocked out.

But, Lin Ming could faintly feel that there seemed to be the rhythm of a heartbeat echoing from the pill box, exuding an incredible life force as if there was some spiritual existence being bred within.

“The pill has manifested spirituality?”

The Asura Road Master has left behind a pill that had been enshrined on this altar for 10 billion years. Just what would it be like now?

This pill had likely become an existence similar to the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone. Upon opening this pill box, the pill might fly out into the skies, developing its own mind and intelligence, even being able to cultivate on its own!

Such a pill left everyone shocked. Shenku and Lanlu even wondered whether they would be able to keep the pill from running with their current level of strength after opening the box.

Wanting to prevent it from escaping wouldn’t be easy, and as for swallowing it, the difficulty of that task could be imagined.

“A pill on this level, would swallowing it cause the body to explode with energy?”

As To Bagui spoke, he looked at Diwuhen. Diwuhen shook his head, indicating that he wouldn’t choose this pill, because the pill wasn’t enough to save their people.

Diwuhen looked at Lin Ming. Lin Ming was silent. He alone could choose two items, so he wasn’t in a hurry.

The third item was a black symbol paper. This symbol paper had dense and complex runes drawn across it.

This was a divine runic symbol as well as a so-called god decree.

This was different from the god decrees Lin Ming had seen before that had already turned yellow. This god decree contained an incomparably horrifying strength. The power of Laws within hadn’t faded in the slightest even after 10 billion years, and instead faintly enhanced.

“This god decree…”

Lin Ming’s eyes brightened. He looked at the lines atop the god decree, slowly analyzing its function…

The fourth supreme treasure was a small green bottle. This bottle exuded a halo of light. As Lin Ming probed it with his sense, he felt a familiar aura.

He had felt an aura like this before, in the planet-sized heavenly palace at the Asura Road’s final trial. He would absolutely not mistake what this was – it was the aura of Asura blood.

This green bottle contained a drop of Asura blood. And from the aura it exuded, it was even beyond that of the drop of blood within the planet-sized heavenly palace!

“This doesn’t seem like an object of salvation either…”

As Diwuhen spoke, he felt his heart tighten. In this Asura forbidden land, would there not be anything that could save their people?

Chapter 1894 – Lin Ming’s Choice

Out of these four items Lin Ming had seen so far, he had difficulty deciding which to choose. Each one would be useful to him, so which should he select in the end?

At this time, Lin Ming’s gaze swept towards the fifth supreme treasure.

This treasure was the most unusual. It was a jade ship the size of a palm. The jade ship was covered with array formations and emitted a deep blue divine light all over it. Although this divine light was bright, it was gentle, without glaring in the least.

This palm-sized jade ship was undoubtedly a Beyond Divinity level supreme treasure.

But after clearly seeing this jade ship, it wasn’t just Diwuhen, but To Bagui also began to sweat.

Of these five treasures, none of them seemed able to force back the saints!

“Jade ship… should we have all the people of our races take refuge in this jade ship?”

Smokeless muttered. Diwuhen shook his head.

“It’s useless. Even if this is a Beyond Divinity level treasure ship, it will be difficult for us to display its strength. Once we are surrounded by a True Divinity, that means we will be intercepted. At that time we would be nothing but a turtle in a jar. Even if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign could not break apart this treasure ship quickly, he could easily kill us once this treasure ship exhausts itself of energy…”

What Diwuhen had described was something Lin Ming had personally experienced for himself.

Before, he had used Primordius Heavenly Palace to flee from Tian Mingzi and had ended up in such a situation.

Although Tian Mingzi wasn’t able to break apart Primordius Heavenly Palace, he was actually able to slowly exhaust the energy within it.

Once that time came, he would have died.

Then, there was the last treasure.

This last treasure was the smallest. It was shrouded in divine light, making it difficult to see what it was.

Everyone focused their senses into threads and slowly probed this light before verifying what the supreme treasure appeared to be.

It was a piece of jade the size of a baby’s palm. The jade was carved with numerous mystical runes. Besides that, it didn’t seem particularly special at all.

“This…”

Diwuhen’s voice shivered. He looked at this jade piece and was unable to discover anything strange about it, nor did he understand its function.

By relying on this, could they defeat the saints?

Diwuhen, To Bagui, and the others felt as if they were drowning in despair. Of these six treasures, could any of them be the salvation their people needed?

However, at this time, as Lin Ming looked at the sixth and final supreme treasure his heart began to race with excitement.

The emperor jade of fate!

It was impossible for him to be mistaken. This sixth supreme treasure was the emperor jade of fate he had been searching for all this time!

Those with fate would encounter it eventually, those without fate would never meet it. This was the final mysterious key needed to open the last level of the Asura Road’s final trial!

Unfortunately, it wasn’t time for the final trial to open, otherwise Lin Ming would have wanted to re-enter the Asura Road and use the two other emperor jades he had with this one to open the final divine treasure trove!

Lin Ming’s change in state of mind was undetected by anyone else.

They were all stuck making a difficult choice. This choice was just far too important.

Diwuhen said, “Choose, but be careful. These six treasures concern the future of not only the ancient remnant races, but even the future of the entire 33 Heavens. They are something that will change the result of the great calamity. In choosing the treasure, we must consider the choice carefully and make sure we unravel and understand the functions of each supreme treasure!”

As Diwuhen spoke, the truth was that he was speaking to Lin Ming. He knew Lin Ming was proficient in the Asura Laws, and only he could easily see through the functions of these supreme treasures.

Of these six supreme treasures, they were – the jade ship, emperor jade, god decree, furnace, pill, and Asura blood.

For To Bagui and Diwuhen, it was far too difficult to differentiate just which supreme treasure would be the most valuable.

“Or maybe…”

Diwuhen looked at the god decree. If he had to choose from the six items, he would think that the god decree of which they currently hadn’t discovered the function would most likely be the treasure of salvation.

If they could rely on it to kill the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign…

“Little Brother Lin, look at the god decree. Its function is…”

To Bagui asked Lin Ming, hope thick in his voice.

Lin Ming’s eyes moved to the god decree. In truth, he had been paying attention to the god decree for a long time already.

It was impossible for him to repair or to duplicate a divine runic symbol personally drawn up by the Asura Road Master. But to simply discover its function, that was within the realm of possibility.

Slowly, he began to discern the lines atop the divine runic symbol, gradually extrapolating just what its use was.

Everyone impatiently huddled around Lin Ming, waiting for him to finish.

“Choose this!”

After an hour of silence, Lin Ming slowly and clearly said.

“Oh? This is…”

To Bagui and Diwuhen’s eyes shined. These past days they had gotten to understand Lin Ming’s character. They knew that if he said such things, he naturally had a reasonable explanation.

Perhaps they might be able to find a favorable turn in this great calamity!

“This god decree, can it kill the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign?”

Diwuhen couldn’t help but ask. Yet Lin Ming shook his head, “No… it has no striking power, and it is not an offensive god decree.”

“What?” Diwuhen staggered backwards. “That is…”

Lin Ming thought for a moment and then said, “If I’m not wrong, then this god decree can be used multiple times. And its function is to… shuttle through the 33 Heavens. In other words… to pierce through the God Lamenting Wall!”

Lin Ming’s words were shocking. Everyone was stunned.

Pierce through the God Lamenting Wall?

The path to salvation, then wasn’t it… to flee?

Diwuhen and To Bagui looked to each other. They knew that in the universes of the 33 Heavens, there were some Heavens that were complete wildernesses. These universes had no smoke of the mortal world, and there were few intelligent life forms. But, this didn’t mean that they were completely unsuited for survival, it was just that the God Lamenting Wall separating these wild universes was too strong, and they were isolated far away from other universes.

If they could flee to these universes then it was possible for them to contend with the saints.

This was because even for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, if he wished to pierce through the God Lamenting Wall he would have to pay a deep price.

“To run away…”

Diwuhen didn’t know what taste was on his tongue. He muttered these words again and again.

“This is the only choice…”

To Bagui bitterly sighed and patted Diwuhen’s shoulder.

To have them leave the Primeval Universe like this, to leave the homeland that their races had lived in for 10 billion years, it was inevitable that they would be moved by this.

However, for them, this universe had become a dead end…

“The heavens bless my god race…”

Diwuhen meditated in his heart. In the air, he bowed deeply once more, and then reached out with his hands to take the god decree.

Under the protective rules, the array formation around the god decree didn’t stop Diwuhen.

Like this, he smoothly took the god decree into his hands.

The soft silky feeling caused Diwuhen’s hands to quiver. What he held in his hands was the future of the ancient remnant races!

“Little Brother Lin, we have already made our choice. What about yours?”

To Bagui asked.

Lin Ming hesitated for a moment. From the five remaining items, choosing two of them wasn’t easy at all.

After pondering over the choices for ten breaths of time, Lin Ming bowed and then reached out his hands.

First, he took the emperor jade of fate.

No matter what, he had to obtain this item.

He believed that deep in the Asura Road’s final trial, that was where the Asura Road Master had left behind his most core inheritance.

“This…”

Seeing Lin Ming receive the emperor jade, they were all surprised.

Smokeless frowned. She looked at Lin Ming, confused.

The first item that Lin Ming chose should be the one that he thought was the most precious.

However in Smokeless’ opinion, of the five remaining treasures, the most valuable one was the mysterious pill.

The other items were all external items, but a pill could directly enhance a martial artist’s strength; its value was naturally the greatest.

She couldn’t understand Lin Ming’s choice. Could this emperor jade be some extraordinary thing? Did Lin Ming see just how precious it was?

“There’s still one more.”

Lin Ming’s eyes swept over the four remaining items, one at a time.

The Asura blood?

The Asura blood was definitely good, but Lin Ming had already absorbed it once. If he absorbed this Asura blood a second time, the effects would be greatly diminished.

Moreover, Lin Ming had already obtained the blood of the Holy Scripture creator.

Lin Ming’s plan was to fuse the two different strengths within him through cultivating. Considering this, it would be far easier fusing together the two different powers if they were balanced.

Thus, Lin Ming first gave up on the Asura blood.

Then there was the furnace, mysterious pill, and jade ship!

Lin Ming considered his choices again and again. Finally, he grit his teeth and reached out for the jade ship!

This jade ship was the size of his palm. As it fell into Lin Ming’s hand, it spun around, its entire body white and emitting a soft atmosphere.

Thus, Lin Ming finished making his choices. He had chosen the emperor jade as well as the… jade ship!

Chapter 1895 – The God Sovereign’s Decision

Lin Ming’s second choice was the jade ship.

Seeing this, To Bagui, Smokeless, Diwuhen, and the others were all left stunned.

This jade ship should have once been the personal transportation of the Asura Road Master, a Beyond Divinity level spirit treasure spirit ship.

Creating a spirit ship was far more difficult than forging a weapon or refining a pill, moreover, the materials required for the construction were also far higher. But to Lin Ming, the furnace with the Law runes engraved within or the pill would have been much more useful for his cultivation.

To him, this spirit ship wasn’t too meaningful.

“Lin Ming… you chose this spirit ship, for…?”

Diwuhen had already guessed why Lin Ming made this choice, but he didn’t dare to randomly assume. Thus, he asked Lin Ming this question.

“To escape… otherwise, even with the god decree, none of you will be able to escape the Chaos Star Ocean. Without reaching the edge of the Primeval Universe, there will be no way to break through the God Lamenting Wall…”

Currently, the primal god race and the celestials were under a deep siege by the saints. They had only managed to delay for time by relying on the endless black holes and space-time vortexes within the Chaos Star Ocean.

In this situation, wanting to break through the ranks of the saints was unlikely.

“This…”

Diwuhen and To Bagui were at a loss for how to respond to Lin Ming’s words.

Lin Ming had used one of his chances to choose a supreme treasure to pick the spirit ship, all in order to allow the ancient remnant races a slim ray of hope. This benevolence was far too heavy!

Lin Ming shook his head. “You do not need to thank me. First, the old God Sovereign has treated me well, and second, I am also doing this for my own people. I think that the ancient remnant races can break through the space barrier to fly to the Divine Realm, and then use this spirit ship to carry away a part of the Divine Realm’s people to break through the God Lamenting Wall once more and fly to a wild universe together.”

The great calamity lay before them. Lin Ming was well aware that just by relying on himself as well as the Empyreans of humanity, it would be impossible to resist the saints.

It was inevitable that the Divine Realm would be captured by their enemies.

The Divine Realm had quadrillions of trillions of people as well as millions of worlds. The total number of humans was incalculable. Moreover, they were widely dispersed throughout the vast Divine Realm, so wanting to exterminate them all was a nigh impossible task.

Even if the saints used crowds of Empyreans and World Kings to search through each world and kill all humans they could find, they might not be able to finish the job even with 100 million years.

But, the truth was that the saints didn’t need to totally annihilate humanity. Rather, they simply needed to destroy the inheritances of humanity.

As long as they destroyed all the human Holy Lands and large influences, humanity would lose their foundation. They would devolve into the humans that lived in the Soul World, becoming nothing but a race of slaves that were ruled by others. After that they would slowly decline until they were finally destroyed.

Thus… the elites of humanity could not be allowed to die.

Divine Dream, Emperor Shakya, Dragon Fang, Jun Bluemoon, Hang Chi… as well as the many Empyreans, World Kings, Empyrean descendants, the peerless proud children of heaven… these people were all the future of humanity. They represented the greatest achievements in martial arts that humanity had developed. In order for the inheritances of humanity’s martial arts to continue onwards, these people were all needed.

With a short hundred years, this was all Lin Ming could do. In fact, this could be said to be the only choice possible in a situation where they were cornered and without a path out…

“Pass into the Divine Realm and join together with the human race?”

Diwuhen was thoughtful. The ancient remnant races allying with humanity was perhaps a good decision. Since they both had the goal of destroying the saints, this was a union of interests.

Of course, such a significant prospect had to be reported to the old God Sovereign so that he could make the final decision…

…….

Like this, the venture into the Asura forbidden land ended.

Lin Ming had obtained what he wanted the most – the emperor jade of fate. What followed next was waiting for the Asura Road’s final trial to open.

But before then, he had to assist humanity and the ancient remnant races in evacuating their universes.

All of this was a perfectly ideal situation. But… would the future really develop in the road he wished…?

Lin Ming couldn’t judge that.

As they said, man proposes, but heaven disposes!

Even if he failed, even if humanity was destroyed, even if he died, he would not regret the choices he made for himself, he wouldn’t regret refusing Sheng Mei.

Everything he did was to follow his heart.

This was especially true after he saw Empyrean Primordius in that dark chamber, and those alarming words he had etched into the ground.

Seeing them had strengthened Lin Ming’s belief.

Even if he suffered a cruel death, he wanted to follow his heart and walk forwards, one step at a time!

……

Lin Ming returned to the primal god race. The old God Sovereign had already been waiting for him for a long time.

After seeing everyone return safely as well as after hearing Diwuhen’s recounting of what happened, the old God Sovereign was extremely startled. Although he knew that Lin Ming was extraordinary, he didn’t think that his performance in the Asura forbidden land would have been so amazing. He had jumped ranks to strike down one of the strongest geniuses from the ancient era.

As for allying the god race with the human race, the old God Sovereign readily agreed to this.

Although taking a detour to the Divine Realm would make their escape far more dangerous, this would be greatly beneficial to the reformation of their race in the future.

Moreover, if it weren’t for Lin Ming, they would have had no chance of fleeing; they would have only been able to sit here and wait for death.

“This is a spirit ship left behind by the Asura Road Master?”

Next to a black stone table, the numerous powerhouses of the god race and celestial races had gathered together. An emergency summons had been sent out, calling them all here.

“Yes, we’ve studied this spirit ship. It can change size at will and there is a separate dimensional space within it, one that is extremely vast. It can completely fit all the ancient remnant races that are currently residing in the Chaos Star Ocean.”

Wanting to fit several billion martial artists in the spirit ship wasn’t difficult at all. A 30 by 30 mile square plane could fit a billion people, and if divided into levels, it could fit dozens of billions or even hundreds of billions of people. And, this spirit ship was far, far larger than that.

Moreover, those within the spirit ship also carried their own spatial magic tools. These magic tools could also hold people, increasing the holding capacity at exponential rates.

Currently, the god race’s population only consisted of a pitiful several dozen millions of people. And these people weren’t all located within the Chaos Star Ocean.

Even with the celestials and all the other races added together, the spirit ship could still fit many times more their number.

“The plan will commence one month from now. At the appointed time, we will begin a covert operation and convene all our people here. We will have them all shifted into the spirit ship within 20 days, and afterwards, the spirit ship will set off! The fate of our people will depend on whether or not we can break through the siege!”

The old God Sovereign waved his hand, loudly declaring.

The truth was that this was not a meeting, but simply a notice. An escape plan had been formulated long before this. No matter who or where they were, all had to obey.

Break through…

Hearing these words, the numerous powerhouses present fell silent. They knew that breaking out of the siege wouldn’t be easy. Making sacrifices was an unavoidable matter, and if they were unlucky, it was possible they would all be annihilated.

The great war that would happen 50 days from now, that would concern the life or death of all the ancient remnant races!

After everyone was silent for a long time the old God Sovereign quietly spoke up. “Lin Ming…”

“Junior is present.”

Lin Ming stood up.

The old God Sovereign lovingly looked at Lin Ming. He slowly said, “This is a spirit ship that you brought back. Its name has long been lost to time. Why don’t you give it a new name?”

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred.

His eyes moved away from the old God Sovereign.

At that moment, his eyes seemed to pierce through the space barrier of the grand hall and gaze into the boundless starry skies.

“Let’s call it Hope. The Ark of Hope…”

Lin Ming whispered.

……….

News of Lin Ming, Diwuhen, and the others bringing back the method to salvation from the Asura forbidden land was completely blocked off. Only the high level figures of the god race and celestial race were aware of it. This was in order to avoid anything being revealed to the saints, so that they wouldn’t launch a desperate invasion into the Chaos Star Ocean.

Currently, the god race needed time!

The old God Sovereign had chosen to leave a month before the summoning of the people and the start of the plan. The truth was that this was all in order for Lin Ming to repair god decrees.

As soon as Lin Ming returned to the god race, he threw himself into a chamber.

There wasn’t much time until they fled. With the god race’s current strength, even with the support of the Asura Road Master’s spirit ship, wanting to break out of the saint race’s encirclement would be mind-bogglingly difficult.

And if they had a batch of high quality god decrees assisting them, this mission would be much easier!

For a time, the entire god race was shrouded in a tense and oppressive atmosphere.

Lin Ming repaired the god decrees without a sense of day or night. His cultivation wasn’t high to begin with and these god decrees were top divine runic symbols left behind by True Divinity level supreme elders. Wanting to repair them wasn’t easy at all.

Thus, the old God Sovereign had sent out several peak Empyreans to be on standby and assist Lin Ming wherever possible.

These peak Empyreans also considered following Lin Ming to learn some techniques.

At this time, they wanted to learn divine runic arts not to steal anything, but only to help Lin Ming. They wanted to assist him so that there would be more god decrees and stronger god decrees to deal with the saints.

But they slowly discovered that no matter how diligent they were in their studies, they weren’t able to learn anything at all.

This divine runic arts technique seemed exclusive to Lin Ming. Besides him, no one else was able to understand anything about it.

Another god decree was repaired by Lin Ming. His soul force frequently ran dry.

Then, he would sit in meditation, slowly restoring himself.

“Lin Ming, his Majesty the Battle Sovereign has bid me to send these soul recovery pills…”

After Lin Ming completed a repair job and was beginning to rest, Smokeless entered his chamber.

In order to break out of the besiegement, the celestials gave every effort they could.

These soul recovery pills that Smokeless brought were top quality pills amongst top quality pills. Several soul forging specialized celestial Empyreans had collaborated in order to refine these, using all sorts of precious soul nourishing materials without hesitating to pay any price.

At this time, no one felt there wasn’t anything they weren’t willing to give up. They would spend anything as long as it helped that much more.

“Thank you…”

Lin Ming’s voice had a hint of exhaustion that was hard to conceal. At this time, his face was white and his eyes were bloodshot. Piles of materials were haphazardly thrown about all over his chamber.

This was because some god decrees were incredibly damaged. Lin Ming even needed to redraw some tiny runes on these god decrees.

Adding runes was even more taxing on Lin Ming. Even if it was just a little, this exhausted his soul force.

Smokeless looked at such a Lin Ming, a complex light in her eyes. Because she had taunted Lin Ming and had even been hostile to him in the past, she felt nothing but a crushing guilt.

“Make sure you rest well…”

Smokeless bit her lips, speaking in a soft voice.

If an ordinary person were to say such words, it would only be considered polite. But to Smokeless who was born arrogant and coldly indifferent, these were rare words.

“I understand. Thank you for the soul recovery pills.”

Lin Ming had incredible attainments in the soul; he was naturally able to see how uncommon these soul recovery pills were.

To him, repairing these god decrees under a high period of stress was a good chance to temper himself. And with these precious soul recovery pills, he could wantonly overdraw his soul force without consideration of whether there would be any lasting damages left over.

“Mm…”

Smokeless nodded. She looked deeply at Lin Ming and then left the chamber…

The repair process of the god decrees continued on as intensely as it did before.

At this time, Lin Ming who had overdrawn his soul force numerous times already, didn’t know that in a place countless miles away, something terrifying was brewing.

Chapter 1896 – The Giant Beast in the Blood Pool

In the deep vastness of space, there was a metal planet.

On the surface of this planet there was a cave entrance that was over a thousand miles wide. The edges of this massive hole were smooth and uniform, clearly not formed by natural forces but forcefully carved out by a powerhouse using their great supernatural might.

This cave was fathomless. If one entered, they would find something even more astonishing. After entering a thousand miles deep, there was a titanic space over ten thousand miles wide in radius. This was the same as the entire planet being carved out from within.

And in this massive space was a crimson blood pond that stretched out for thousands of miles. Blood surged and rippled. Killing intent soared to the heavens, alarming to the senses.

In the skies above the blood pond, a middle-aged man in a rainbow-hued robe quietly floated.

This middle-aged man had deep red hair and his looks were ancient and profound, as if his appearance were carved by a saber.

At this time, his eyes were shut tight and his hands were grasping across his chest, his ten fingers splayed outwards, tightly grabbing onto his shoulders. His lips murmured as if he were reciting some ancient text.

Beneath him, the blood pond seethed and roiled. The scent of blood filled the world. Slowly, countless bubbles slowly emerged from the blood pond, as if it were boiling over with excitement.

More and more bubbles emerged, becoming increasingly dense. The splashing of the blood pond grew larger and larger until finally… with a loud explosion, a massive head thrust out from the blood pond, bringing with it a wave of blood over a hundred miles high that crashed into the horizon!

An endless rain of blood fell down like a torrential waterfall. But, the middle-aged man still remained motionless, his eyes shut tight.

He floated within this torrent of blood, but not a single drop touched his body.

What had just come out of the blood pond was a fierce demonic head. This head was a hundred miles long with a pair of curved horns and a great maw, just like a malevolent red dragon!

This malevolent red dragon wildly roared, its massive head swinging from side to side.

At this time, massive bubbles emerged from the blood pond once more. With a great rumble, another ferocious dragon head hurtled out, tumbling about in the skies.

And following that, fierce dragon after fierce dragon drilled out from the blood pond; it was unknown just how many there were.

If a martial artist were to enter this planet at this time, they would definitely be bewildered. They would think that this blood pond was a giant dragon nest and there were many wicked dragons slumbering within.

However, what followed next was shocking.

After over 30 fierce dragons rushed out from the blood pond, the entire pond of blood began to rapidly lower, drying up…

The surface of the blood pond dropped again and again. Eventually, a titanic 10,000 mile long spherical object was exposed. This ball-like object was the same color as the blood pond, and if one didn’t look carefully they might even think it was the same.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Viscous blood poured down from the surface of the sphere like a waterfall, eventually revealing thick black chains.

These black chains overlapped each other, firmly locking down that sphere and completely binding it.

As the blood pond lowered more and more, the sphere began to slowly wriggle. There were even beating sounds from within, like the beating of a heart!

Faintly, one could feel a vast aura of life emitting from this sphere; it seemed to be a mass of flesh and blood.

As for the 30 plus fierce red dragons, at the end of their necks that were hundreds of miles long, they were connected to this massive ball of flesh and blood!

In other words, the 30 plus cruel red dragons were not individuals, but part of a whole!

They were branches of this humongous sphere!

It was hard to imagine what sort of terrifying life form this sphere was. In size alone it was 10,000 miles wide and had more than 30 fierce red dragon heads extending from it, each one emitting a terrifying aura no less than that of a True Dragon!

As this horrifying monster appeared, the rainbow-robed man floating in the skies frowned. Beads of sweat had developed at his temples; he had clearly consumed a great deal of energy.

His lips changed as fast as a bolt of lightning. He continued to chant, his words becoming faster and faster!

The words he spoke formed visible runes in the air that flew towards the bizarre giant monster. Then, like water into an ocean, they submerged into the monster’s body.

The middle-aged man consumed more and more energy. His blood vitality tumbled in his body and astral essence gushed out from him. He became increasingly bright, sparkling like a bright afternoon sun.

“Mark of the Saint Ancestors – Seal!”

The middle-aged man’s eyes suddenly popped open. At that moment, all of the texts he chanted gathered together, forming a massive curse seal that flew towards the monster.

Then, this curse seal reflected atop the middle-aged man’s head. It slowly sank into the monster and disappeared from sight.

Wu wu wu –

Wu wu wu –

The monster emitted a deep and bass cry like an earthquake. The entire planet shook, as if it were affected, thundering together with the monster!

This process continued for half an incense stick of time. Then, with a crashing sound, something strange occurred.

Of the monster’s 30 some dragon heads, one of them suddenly melted away, turning into bright red blood that rained down to the ground.

And after several more breaths of time, another dragon head exploded, turning into blood rain once more.

Like this, the 30 some dragon heads each exploded one after another, all of them turning to blood.

Blood gushed down, soaking the monster. After the monster was soaked in this blood, its main body also began to slowly melt away, like a piece of thick lard being heated into liquid.

Finally, the main body completely disappeared, turned into a blood pond.

To begin with, there was no blood pond in this planet, but instead a transformed giant monster!

When the blood pond completely calmed down, the rainbow-robed man closed his eyes, meditating in the void. Chanting all those texts and using the technique he just did had consumed a great deal of his strength.

As the man was meditating, a flame lit up in front of him. The man frowned and opened his eyes.

“Soul Emperor… that old monster, just why is he looking for me…”

The man’s eyes flashed with a strange brilliance. In the next moment he casually tore open the void and stepped forwards. His surroundings changed as he suddenly arrived in a grand hall built of crystal.

Floating in the center of this grand hall was a person’s shadow.

This shadow was fuzzy and undefined; it was clearly just an illusion.

This illusion was that of a youth with smooth, fair skin, and black hair that fell like a waterfall. But, what was bizarre was that this illusion’s eyes were filthy and spiritless, as if on the verge of death.

Such an appearance made one’s scalp creep.

The old youth looked at the middle-aged man. His lips slightly parted, “You seemed to have exhausted yourself considerably? I wonder what it is that can cause the Sovereign of the Saints to work so hard.”

The rainbow-robed man was the saint race’s Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!

“You worry about too many things.” The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign indifferently said, with no intentions of mentioning the spell he just cast. “Just what are you doing here?”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s eyes glared at the Soul Emperor. Although they had come to a temporary truce, they were absolutely not friends.

“I have come here especially to… tell you some news!”

The Soul Emperor’s voice was old and empty, without the least bit of feeling, as if he were speaking words of ice.

“Then speak!”

“There is a person. He has gone to the Primeval Universe. He, is something you might be interested in… his name is… Lin Ming!” The Soul Emperor quietly said. As the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign heard this, his eyebrows leapt up.

“Lin Ming! He has arrived at the Primeval Universe!?”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was certainly not unfamiliar with the name Lin Ming.

Lin Ming was a terrifying youth. At a mere hundred years of age, he could suppress seniors several times his age. He was even able to defeat the Good Fortune Saint Son, someone that was an entire large boundary higher!

If such a person were allowed time, then their future would be unimaginable!

But now, Lin Ming was weak.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign certainly wouldn’t allow Lin Ming to freely grow. He had already planned to kill Lin Ming in the next few hundred years and eliminate all potential problems, cutting the weeds at the roots!

However, before this the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign always had matters he needed to attend to. For instance, dealing with the spiritas or dealing with the saints, or even refining that mysterious blood pond in the planet just now.

But now, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign actually learned from the Soul Emperor that Lin Ming had arrived at the Primeval Universe. This was also the universe that the saints were invading!

If so, then he could completely annihilate the ancient remnant races and conveniently kill off Lin Ming while he was at it.

“Really, you choose not to walk the road to heaven but would rather burst through the gates of hell!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign sneered, a bloodthirsty light shining in his eyes.

Killing Lin Ming was the same as wiping out the hope of humanity!

Chapter 1897 – Raise the Sails!

Soul World, Soul Rapture Holy Lands –

In a grand hall crafted from soul crystals, an old youth stood beside an altar.

His hands were crossed in front of his chest. His eyes were closed and his divine sense stretched out like the tentacles of a monster, piercing through the God Lamenting Wall…

This youth was the Soul Emperor.

In a normal situation, even the Soul Emperor who ruled the entire Soul World would find it impossible to penetrate the God Lamenting Wall with his sense.

But, if he was able to leave a mark on someone ahead of time, then even if that person wasn’t in the same universe he would still be able to pass through the 33 Heavens to sense them.

The Soul Emperor and the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had both left marks on each other’s bodies. As long as they wished for it, they could cross the layers of universes to communicate.

Currently, the Soul Emperor had contacted the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign in order to tell him about news related to Lin Ming.

Ssaaa –

The Soul Emperor’s eyes opened. At the same time, the connection between him and the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was interrupted. In front of the Soul Emperor, the blurry shade of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign slowly disappeared without a trace.

The Soul Emperor was silent. He descended from the altar, one step at a time. With his long black hair and his snow-white robe, from the back he appeared like an extraordinarily beautiful youth at the peak of his prime.

And standing in front of the Soul Emperor was a woman wrapped in a black cloak.

This woman was Sheng Mei.

At this time, Sheng Mei had lowered her eyes. Her expression was faint and indifferent; it was impossible to tell what she was thinking.

“Has your heart gone soft?”

The Soul Emperor suddenly asked. Sheng Mei pressed her eyebrows together, not responding.

The Soul Emperor smiled. “There is no need for you to put on a play before me. I already have a general feeling of the thoughts within your heart. You personally spoke with Lin Ming and blocked out my sense. Afterwards, Lin Ming went to the Primeval Universe. You spoke with him in private for almost a quarter hour – just what did you talk about?”

A light smile hung on the Soul Emperor’s face. But, this smile was terrifying.

Sheng Mei still remained silent. She only stood in the dark hall, looking like a sculpture of white jade that was enveloped in a black cloak.

The Soul Emperor stared at Sheng Mei for ten breaths of time and then chuckled as he shook his head. “Your heartbeat remains the same and there isn’t the slightest disturbance to your aura. Even the energy circulating within you is perfectly uniform! You really do not shame the reputation of being called my soul race’s Soul Empress. However…”

The Soul Emperor’s voice suddenly changed. The atmosphere around him turned icy cold, his entire body surging with killing intent!

His filthy dark eyes turned murderous. “I will not allow you to disobey me again! You should know just how valuable Lin Ming is to me. He is the key to opening my future! After so many years, I have discovered the turning point for all my ambitions. I will not allow anyone to ruin my plans!”

The Soul Emperor overflowed with killing intent, like cold winds that howled from the nine nether abyss. As Sheng Mei faced this violent killing intent, her protective spirit essence trembled.

She took a deep breath and looked at the Soul Emperor. Her voice was equally cold as she said, “You don’t need to threaten me. I already have no other path to take. Your choice is also my choice!”

Although Sheng Mei said this, she still didn’t know what taste was in her heart. In truth, this so-called choice was not hers alone, but one that Lin Ming helped her make…

Rather, it could be said that Sheng Mei had already expected Lin Ming’s choice, and she was simply using their conversation to once again steady her resolve.

“Good! Good! Very good!” The Soul Emperor said, shouted out good three times. “A worm that lives in the dead leaves and fallen branches will never understand the beauty and greatness of the world, because their field of vision is far too narrow and their life is far too short. They will never be able to live past the winter snows…

“I think you don’t want to become such a worm…”

As the Soul Emperor spoke, he stepped forwards until he was a mere foot away from Sheng Mei.

He wasn’t tall and only had the appearance of a newly minted youth. As for Sheng Mei, she was tall. With that, their eyes were completely even with each other.

As their eyes met, countless complex emotions were contained within Sheng Mei’s gaze.

The Soul Emperor’s last words were also the words that Sheng Mei had spoken to Lin Ming. But compared to when she had said them, the feelings behind them were completely different…

Time slowly passed.

With the descent of the great calamity, waves would rise and winds would surge!

These were troubled times. Overlords of the various universes were hatching their own plans, taking this one in several billion year chance to realize their ambitions!

Mortal desires were without end. In particular, the True Divinities that stood at the peak of their universes. They had accumulated countless lucky chances and had passed through countless massacres, withstanding innumerable tribulations to arrive where they were. They weren’t willing to meekly follow the road that fate had assigned them, they weren’t willing to obey the samsara of the Heavenly Dao. They wanted to control their own destinies, rising above the world and grasping the Heavenly Dao in their hands!

As for the Soul Emperor and Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, they were both among them…

…..

“It’s time…”

Chaos Star Ocean, primal god race headquarters –

The old God Sovereign stood on the edge of a stargazing platform, looked at the endless galaxies circulating around him.

His old eyes seemed to see through the fog of the universe, peeking into the future fate of the god race.

“Reporting to Your Majesty God Sovereign, all people of the ancient remnant races have already boarded the Ark of Hope. This includes the god race’s 22 million citizens, the celestial race’s 350 million citizens, the roaring bone race’s 810 million citizens, the titan race’s 80 million citizens, the ancient spirit race’s…”

An Empyrean respectfully stood behind the old God Sovereign. Diwuhen had stepped forwards, reporting everything to the old God Sovereign.

The old God Sovereign slowly nodded. “Do they all understand how dangerous this battle will be, and what it means to our ancient races?”

“They understand!” Diwuhen responded with absolute surety. “Everything is ready. We can break out at any time!”

“Good.”

The old God Sovereign finally turned around. He slowly tidied his sleeves. On his sleeves, three pure black symbol papers were attached.

These three symbol papers were god decrees personally drawn by the Asura Road Master!

Seeing these three god decrees, all of the Empyreans present had changed complexions. These god decrees were their greatest trump cards in breaking through!

Otherwise, they would have no way to overcome the hurdle that was the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!

“Your Majesty.” Three peak Empyreans stepped forwards together and knelt on the ground, their hands raised over their heads in reverence. “Please bestow us the god decrees!”

“You all… are you ready?”

The old God Sovereign looked at these three people, his tone ancient and powerful.

As god decrees left behind by the Asura Road Master, wanting to activate them wasn’t simple at all!

If a True Divinity galvanized them, they would be drained of strength. And if an Empyrean were to do so, they would affect their own life source and burn the fires of their lives, greatly diminishing their lifespan!

“Honorable Master, please bestow me a god decree!”

Diwuhen stubbornly lifted his hands.

“It is not your turn.”

Two elderly peak Empyreans stood in front of Diwuhen. “Please grant them to us…”

“Mm…”

The old God Sovereign looked at these two old god race Empyreans. They were already over 80 million years old.

With a wave of his hand, two god decrees flew into the hands of the two Empyreans.

“The word of Sealing as well as the word of Striking, the two of you can take one. As for the last one, I will hold it myself…” The old God Sovereign’s voice echoed out. As Diwuhen heard this, his heart shook and he quietly drew back.

He knew that he could not change the decision of the old God Sovereign. Out of all the primal god race’s peak Empyreans, he was the youngest…

The young and those in their prime, they were the future of the god race after this great war…

“Let us go.” The old God Sovereign took a deep breath. “We… will fight!”

…….

In the starry black skies, the void was quiet and endless.

Within the Chaos Star Ocean that was filled with space-time storms and black holes, a pure white spirit ship cut straight through space, flying out without slowing!

At the center of this pure white spirit ship, there was a massive array disc. 12 Empyreans sat in a circle around this array disc, providing energy to the spirit ship.

Countless energy stones burned within the array formation.

Lin Ming stood outside the array formation, quietly watching all of this.

Nearby, he could see the vast endlessness of space rapidly passing him by.

“It’s begun…”

Lin Ming had a faint premonition that this battle to break through would be the spark that lit the explosive flames of war…

The future of humanity, the future of the ancient races, as well as his own future, everything would depend on this battle.

“Reporting to Your Majesty, in front of us lies the saints’ space blockade…” At the bow of the spirit ship, a messenger soldier from the titan race reported the information.

“Run it over!”

The old God Sovereign simply and mercilessly replied. His voice carried a deep killing intent.

“As you will!”

The messenger soldier passed on the command. The entire spirit ship suddenly accelerated.

Bang!

With a loud explosion, the void shook!

The saints’ space blockade had been directly ripped open. The Ark of Hope didn’t slow in the least, piercing through the spatial barrier like an arrow through thin paper.

This was the spirit ship left behind by the Asura Road Master and driven by numerous Empyreans. How could such a massive blockade possibly hope to stop it?

Chapter 1898 – Killing an Empyrean

“Enemy attack!”

Amongst the fleet of the saints, someone cried out loud.

Hundreds of sound transmitting talismans lit up together, rapidly passing down information through various channels.

“Who dares!? They are courting death!”

Over a hundred saint martial artists rushed out.

These people were mostly small battalion leaders and team commanders. They were originally enjoying themselves and playing around, and now that they suddenly heard the enemy was attacking, their festivities were interrupted and they naturally didn’t feel well.

These small group leaders were mostly all Holy Lords. As they saw a massive pure white spirit ship hurtling towards them, they all stared in a stunned daze.

“High grade spirit ship!”

The saint martial artist in the lead was a tall and fat man with a Great World King cultivation. All things considered, he had good eyesight and was able to immediately recognize that this white spirit ship was extraordinary. It was as large as a small planet and even though it was still hundreds of thousands of miles away, it was clearly visible!

“Do they want to break through the defensive line of our Godstep Heavenly Palace!?

“Activate the defensive array formations and prepare to meet the enemy! Report to Empyrean Godstep what is happening, I think those god race bastards have finally become too bored!”

The fat Great World King immediately ordered. These saint martial artists had gone through numerous battles. Although they were all boisterous and rowdy, when they truly met the enemy they wouldn’t be lazy. They immediately opened the array formation to meet the incoming enemy.

However, the white spirit ship didn’t fire towards their battle array but hurtled in another direction!

“What?”

The fat Great World King was stunned. That direction was where Godstep Heavenly Palace was!

That Godstep Heavenly Palace was personally guarded by Empyrean Godstep!

It had to be known that many Empyrean Heavenly Palaces were themselves top grade magic tools. Their combat strength was amazing.

“Are they insane? Do they want to commit suicide?”

The fat Great World King was dumbfounded.

The other group leaders laughed. “Nothing but trying to break a rock with an egg. They’re just looking to die!”

“With Empyrean Godstep’s status, he shouldn’t be willing to meddle in such a battle. But if they are going to run up to his doorstep to die, no one’s going to stop them.”

People chuckled as they spoke. However, the fat Great World King’s complexion was somewhat odd. The situation was too suspicious. That white spirit ship…

As the fat Great World King was thinking, something amazing occurred. The spirit ship shot towards Empyrean Godstep’s Heavenly Palace and didn’t seem to be slowing at all. From the current trajectory and speed, they were going to collide!

“Insane!”

The fat Great World King was panic-stricken. Such a terrifying strike would absolutely cause a riotous detonation. After the array formation of a high grade spirit ship exploded along with the massive amount of energy stones within, the energy shockwaves produced would suck up every nearby Holy Lord and tear them all to shreds.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Floating in space, Godstep Heavenly Palace began to shine with the luminescence of an array formation. Divine light shot out from within the Heavenly Palace; this was the Heavenly Palace’s defensive array formation!

With such a large-scale array formation in addition to the personal management of Empyrean Godstep, even the all-out strike of a peak Empyrean wouldn’t be able to shake the barrier.

But the fragile-seeming spirit ship continued rushing forwards. It was the suicidal appearance of someone trying to crack open a stone with an egg!

“This is suicide!”

Many people waited to see that white spirit ship crash and blow up into countless fireworks in the starry void.

However, when the white spirit ship struck the array formation at high speed, the front of the spirit ship also shined with the light of an array formation. Infinite divine light gathered there, forming a massive blade!

The blade recklessly tore through all. With a loud explosion, the Heavenly Palace’s array formations were torn asunder!

This was like a knife tearing through ordinary paper, without the least bit of resistance!

Then, the white spirit ship fired forwards with unbelievable speed, straight into Godstep Heavenly Palace.

Bang!

The Heavenly Palace violently shook. The walls were ruthlessly torn through by the white spirit ship. The white spirit ship broke through, crashing into the Heavenly Palace!

A monumental tide of energy swept out. In that single collision, countless saint martial artists within Godstep Heavenly Palace had perished!

Even the World Kings within were sucked in and injured.

However, the white spirit ship continued forth with unstoppable momentum. With nearly constant speed, it pierced through the massive Godstep Heavenly Palace, penetrating all the way from one side to the other, bringing with it a brilliant detonation of fireworks as it passed through!

This sort of feeling was like a javelin piercing right through a target!

At that moment, the entire Godstep Heavenly Palace collapsed. Endless fragments were sent flying away as countless martial artists that were within Godstep Heavenly Palace were thrown into the cold vacuum of space.

As for the white spirit ship, it was like a phoenix flying out from an inferno, continuing to race deep into the universe!

Several hundred thousands of miles away, the fat Great World King and the others looked on with horrified expressions, all of them scared witless.

They thought that this was a futile battle and the white spirit ship would blow apart. But, the white spirit ship had actually come out unscathed while the entire Godstep Heavenly Palace had been destroyed.

The result was the complete opposite to what they had thought!

Heavens, what is that!?

“Who is it!?”

From within the ruins of the destroyed Heavenly Palace, an angry and thunderous voice echoed outwards. A skinny man with a mane of white hair stepped out, chasing right after the white spirit ship.

This skinny man’s hawk-like eyes blazed with a severe light!

He was Empyrean Godstep! His own Heavenly Palace had been ruined; how could he silently endure such an insult?

“Break for me!”

The skinny man shouted and slapped out his palm. His palm transformed into a thousand mile palm that shined with a golden divine light, grasping towards the white spirit ship’s driving array formation. He wanted to destroy the spirit ship’s power source!

Bang!

The golden hand smashed against the white spirit ship. The spirit ship suddenly shook and slowed down.

However, the tremendous impact carried Empyrean Godstep forwards.

“Your Majesty God Sovereign!”

Within the spirit ship, the Empyreans managing the driving array formation suddenly felt the spirit ship slow down, receiving a great resistance. “An upper saint Empyrean is hindering our spirit ship from several tens of thousands of miles away.”

“Erase him, quickly and decisively!” The old God Sovereign’s voice was as cold as ice.

“Yes.”

Three peak Empyreans received the order and flew out from the white spirit ship. Even for a peak Empyrean, wanting to instantly kill an upper Empyrean from tens of thousands of miles away was difficult. After all, even if the opponent couldn’t fight they could still run.

But this time, one of the three peak Empyreans held a yellow symbol paper in his hand. This was a god decree left behind by an ordinary True Divinity, but after being repaired by Lin Ming, its might could no longer be compared to how it was in the past!

Divine light sparkled and the god decree lit up. At the same time, the two other peak Empyreans also assisted in the attack.

Three beams of divine light cut through the void, hurtling straight towards Empyrean Godstep with inconceivable speed.

In particular, the central beam of light was overwhelming, tearing through the cosmos!

“Mm!?”

Empyrean Godstep was alarmed. He could feel a terrifying strength within that middle divine light. Moreover, the strength of the three people attacking him had far surpassed his imagination.

“This is bad!”

Empyrean Godstep cried out in shock. He rapidly drew backwards, but… it was too late!

The light that blossomed from the god decree was too dreadful. After it locked onto Empyrean Godstep, there was no way for him to avoid it!

The brilliant divine light swallowed up Empyrean Godstep.

Meanwhile, the attacks of the other two Empyreans also collided. The three attacks joined together, completely piercing through Empyrean Godstep’s body.

“Ahhh!”

Empyrean Godstep howled pitifully. His mortal body was torn apart by the divine lights and his soul was annihilated.

Like this, an Empyrean, and even an outstanding person amongst Empyreans, had been erased from existence, instantly killed in a horrifying manner.

“What?!”

Hundreds of thousands of miles away, the fat Great World King’s heart shriveled as he saw this.

In his lifetime, this was the first time he had ever seen an Empyrean die, and an upper Empyrean at that!

In ordinary times, an Empyrean was no different from a god in their eyes, an unreachable existence!

But in that brief moment just then, an upper Empyrean had been instantly killed, turned to nothing but ashes and smoke!

This frightening scene caused the fat Great World King to freeze where he was, looking like a statue.

And beside the fat Great World King, the other martial artists weren’t able to withstand such a sight. They shivered and a cold sweat dripped down their bodies.

Just what kind of spirit ship was that!? With a single move it was able to erase an upper Empyrean!

“The ancient races… have they all emerged from their nest?”

The fat World King suddenly realized this possibility. The ancient races finally weren’t willing to resign themselves to being encircled and were planning to break free!

“Quickly report the news!”

The fat Great World King’s mind was in utter chaos. He began to realize that this opening salvo would be the fire that lit the fuse for the final decisive battle between the saints and the ancient races!

In fact, it wasn’t just the fat Great World King who realized this. From the destroyed Godstep Heavenly Palace, many World Kings had rapidly sent out news of what happened. This sudden change of events would soon reach the ears of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

Chapter 1899 – Famine

Deep within the Primeval Universe, within the center of an icy metal planet –

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign sat atop a massive blood red sphere that was 10,000 miles wide. This crimson sphere constantly wriggled. Fierce dragon heads jutted out from the bloody sphere before melting back into it with a rain of blood, repeating this process again and again…

At the same time, loud sounds rang out from within the center of the crimson sphere.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

With the thunderous roaring of the earth, the entire planet vibrated with this sound.

The terrifying sound echoed through the semi-sealed interior of the planet. If a martial artist with an insufficient cultivation were to stand in this space, they would be affected by the horrifying high energy sound waves. Their body and organs would resonate with the sound waves until they turned to mush.

In this environment, a young man knelt before the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, his hands splayed on the ground in reverence.

“Your Majesty Sovereign Ancestor, your child requests to go to battle!”

This young man had already been kneeling here for a long time. He was tall, with broad shoulders. His facial features were sharp and fierce, a faint hostility creeping in his eyes.

This youth was the person who had been defeated by Lin Ming in the past – the Good Fortune Saint Son.

In that 100 year duel, when only 60 years had passed, the Good Fortune Saint Son had been defeated by Lin Ming. Not only had he been defeated, he had lost in a miserable fashion.

In the face of numerous people with the Empyreans of the saint race, human race, monster race, and demon race present, the Good Fortune Saint Son had been publicly cuckolded by Lin Ming. His fiancé was stolen and he was beaten to a pulp. This event would forever be the greatest shame in his life!

Now, 20-30 years had passed. The Good Fortune Saint Son had endured this humiliation, torturing himself, diligently training, all for the fervent wish he had of wiping away that shame!

But Lin Ming seemed to have disappeared without a trace; no one was able to find him.

It was only a few days ago that the Good Fortune Saint Son learned Lin Ming had entered the Primeval Universe. With this he could no longer sit still, thus he requested to be sent to the battlefront by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

However, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign didn’t respond.

And just now, he also learned that the ancient races were riding a top grade spirit ship to break through their encirclement. Because of this, the Good Fortune Saint Son volunteered himself for battle once more.

“Your Majesty Sovereign Ancestor, your child can confirm that Lin Ming is riding aboard that white spirit ship. The reason Lin Ming came to the Primeval Universe should have been in order to form an alliance with the ancient remnant races. It even seems that Lin Ming has convinced the leaders of the ancient races. They should be trying to escape the Primeval Universe and flee to the Divine Realm to meet up with the humans!”

As Lin Ming’s rival, the Good Fortune Saint Son had somewhat of an understanding of Lin Ming. He was already able to guess part of the truth.

However, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign shook his head. “You are not Lin Ming’s match. You have diligently cultivated for 20 some years, but even now… the disparity between you and him has only grown larger.”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s words were like a bucket of cold water tossed atop the Good Fortune Saint Son’s head.

“I…” The Good Fortune Saint Son gripped his fists. Although he didn’t want to acknowledge it, he was well aware of just how terrifying Lin Ming was.

In the past, Lin Ming was able to jump ranks to defeat him and he was younger, in the prime of his youth. Now, over the past 20 some years, the disparity would only have grown larger and larger.

The Good Fortune Saint Son grit his teeth, saying, “I might not be his match, but I do not need to defeat him head on. As long as I can lead the army to rout him on the battlefield and kill him there, that will equally restore my heart of martial arts! I beg Your Majesty Sovereign Ancestor to allow your child to command the troops into battle!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son deeply bowed. But, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign continued shaking his head. “You don’t need to be so stubborn. Many times, when a peerless genius reaches the final stage of their growth and must comprehend the Laws of the heavens and earth and step onto the road of divinity, leading a smooth life without problems and bumps isn’t necessarily good…”

“Martial artists are creatures that need setbacks at times, just like a phoenix needs to undergo nirvana… your road has been far too smooth. Experiencing such a strike might not be bad for you. As for Lin Ming, he is the same. Although he had experienced some hurdles as he grew, compared to chasing after the Heavenly Dao, all his problems have been insignificant so far…

“You and Lin Ming both need to fail. However, you have me standing behind you, so even if you are defeated you can start over from nothing. As for Lin Ming, he has no one behind him. Once he is defeated, there is nothing but… death!”

As the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign spoke to here, the massive blood red monster beneath his body seemed to have become infected by his aura. The monster wriggled more and more, causing the entire planet to shake.

“Go, it’s time to end this charade. I will not allow a mere human boy to destroy my plans. Before he has grown, I will kill him!”

Killing intent erupted from the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, recklessly gushing out like a tide.

The Good Fortune Saint Son who was less than 10 feet from the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign felt his heart chill, as if he had fallen into the nine nether abyss!

Even he had never earnestly felt the horrifying might of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign like today.

Wu – wu – wu – !

The crimson monster wriggled more and more. The tiny remaining amount of the blood pond rapidly dried up.

The blood pond had been absorbed by the crimson monster, completely swallowed up!

On the surface of the monster’s body, massive runes began to appear. And, the divine light that these runes shot out all gathered between the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s eyebrows.

In that moment, a rune also appeared between the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s eyebrows. This rune was gold, similar to the runes that covered the monster’s body.

“Could it be…” The Good Fortune Saint Son was shocked upon seeing this. He could clearly feel that at this time, the spiritual sea of the crimson monster had become one with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s!

Bang!

Bang!

Bang!

With a terrifying explosive sound, from the crimson ball beneath the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s feet, dozens of fierce red dragon heads rushed out. These fierce dragons roared with overweening power, breaking into the walls of the metal planet!

The entire planet violently shook. The wicked red dragons tore apart the earth. Endless energy shot out, firing into the vast nothingness of space.

If one watched this planet from millions of miles away, they would see something horrifying occur.

The planet began quietly collapsing from within!

And in the cracks of the disintegrating planet, boundless blood red light filled the air, becoming thicker and thicker until the entire planet was swallowed!

This sort of feeling was like a monster being born from a mother, but because the monster was too powerful, it even swallowed the mother!

“This… this…”

Seeing such a vast and horrifying sight, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s mind shook.

The crimson monster was devouring a planet!

“The holy beast of my race… ‘Famine’…” The Good Fortune Saint Son gulped. “Your Majesty Saint Ancestor! Have you already established a spiritual connection with the holy beast? You can control it!?”

The Good Fortune Saint Son was panic-stricken. He had long known of the existence of their saint race’s holy beast.

Rumors said that this holy beast was originally an extremely terrifying existence even amongst abyssals. Its full name was – ‘The Abyssal Demon – Famine’!

And its special attribute was – to devour all!

The abyss of the ancient ruins was a dreadful place, so frightening that no one could understand it.

The entrance was blocked off by a terrifying enchantment. This enchantment was called the ‘Heaven Sealing Enchantment’.

The Heaven Sealing Enchantment was said to contain the phantoms of the Asura Road Master and the Holy Scripture creator.

Through any reasoning, even an abyssal that surpassed the realm of a peak Empyrean would be unable to break past the Heaven Sealing Enchantment.

But, ‘Famine’ had emerged. As for how it did so, no one knew.

There was only one truth – that after ‘Famine’ left the abyss, its strength had precipitously fallen. Even so, it still possessed a dreadful strength capable of swallowing most True Divinities!

The appearance of ‘Famine’ set off an unprecedented disaster for the saints!

It swallowed a massive number of saint powerhouses and countless saint martial artists, eating them up to make itself more powerful.

But finally, the saint race’s ancient Saint Sovereign had led many True Divinities to join forces and besiege ‘Famine’ with overwhelming strength.

Finally, ‘Famine’ was grievously wounded. Even 90% of its recovered origin energy had disappeared.

Even so, the saints weren’t able to destroy Famine.

In this situation, Famine then signed a contract with the ancient Saint Sovereign.

This was an equal contract. The saints would look for blood and food for Famine to devour, and Famine would fight on behalf of the saints!

Like this, Famine became the holy beast of the saints.

The saints were always ambitious. They wanted to rule the 33 Heavens. However, in the great war 3.6 billion years ago when the saints fought the humans, the saints had paid a dire price!

“Your Majesty Saint Ancestor, wasn’t Famine heavily wounded in the battle 3.6 billion years ago by Empyrean Divine Seal burning away his life as the price? Ever since, Famine has fallen into a deep slumber. How did you manage to awaken it?”

The Good Fortune Saint Son couldn’t believe his own eyes. More than one saint Empyrean had wanted to awaken Famine, but they had all failed.

But now, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had not only awakened Famine, but even seemed to have gained control of it. This left the Good Fortune Saint Son gasping in disbelief.

Rumble rumble rumble!

A series of terrifying explosions continued. From that giant spherical body of blood, more and more blood dragon tentacles stretched out, digging into the earth of the metal planet and recklessly swallowing its energy!

Strength streamed into Famine’s body. But, the entire planet withered away. Its origin energy dried up, the seas evaporated, and massive fissures raced through the world.

Even the dried-up land that had lost all spiritual energy was completely swallowed by Famine. Like this, a giant planet that was tens of thousands of miles in radius was eaten by Famine!

This process lasted less than a quarter hour of time. Such a drastic change in the world left the Good Fortune Saint Son struggling to compose himself.

Although he had heard that Famine possessed the ability to swallow worlds, stories were only stories. Now that he saw these stories come to life with his own eyes, he was utterly shocked.

To pierce through a planet wasn’t difficult, but crushing apart a planet was hard. As for completely swallowing up a planet, what sort of mighty power was that?

As a martial artist who wholeheartedly chased after the peak of martial arts, the Good Fortune Saint Son had a zealous obsession with strength.

If… only this strength was his own, how wonderful would that be!

At this time, the Good Fortune Saint Son discovered that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s feet had submerged into the blood of Famine at some unknown time.

Rather, it was more accurate to say that he didn’t submerge, but the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s mortal body had already fused together with the blood plasma of Famine, sharing blood vessels.

“Hah!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign coldly sneered. On his neck, blood vessels rose up like red worms, making him look fearsome to the extreme.

“Swallowing a planet is nothing. 3.6 billion years ago when Famine was in its peak state, it even swallowed up the destiny of the human bloodline – in other words, one of humanity’s Heavenly Daos, the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s words were stunning. The Good Fortune Saint Son was also shocked; he had never heard about this chapter of history before.

Chapter 1901 – Blast Through the Void

“Damn it!”

In these past years, numerous saint Empyreans had fought through the Primeval Universe while suffering little damage.

But in this battle, three of them had already died before much fighting had even occurred. Moreover… they were all upper Empyreans!

Upon reaching the level of an Empyrean, wanting to defeat a similar opponent wasn’t difficult. However, wanting to kill one was a completely different matter.

After all, every person that managed to reach the heights of an Empyrean was an extreme talent that was blessed with a great destiny. They had experienced innumerable lucky chances as they grew and had countless life-saving cards hidden up their sleeves.

And their own defensive capabilities were particularly powerful, their life force almost unparalleled in tenacity.

But such characters had been instantly annihilated to dust upon facing the white spirit ship, killed without a chance to react. This left the rest of them frightened.

It had to be known that in the all-out war between the humans and saints 3.6 billion years ago, the saints only had several hundred Empyreans die, and most of them were lower Empyreans and middle Empyreans. Now, to lose three upper Empyreans like this, the losses were mind-boggling.

Several other Empyreans were also severely injured. Their combat strength had weakened. However, their mortal bodies were formidable and their regenerative abilities were outstanding. These wounds slowly healed.

“That spirit ship, how can it be so strong!?”

“Just what sort of ancient treasure is that terrifying!?”

Several Empyreans felt fear rise in their hearts. Before this, they were already accustomed to the ancient remnant races scattering to flee upon the beginning of a fight as they were all immediately routed. To the saints, invading the Primeval Universe was the same as beating up a crippled man; it was a completely overwhelming and one-sided battle. They had never experienced such frustration before.

“Slow them down but do not face them head-on, be careful of that god cannon! The ancient races have countless treasures, once they die they are all ours!”

A peak Empyrean sent out a sound transmission.

At this time, more and more saint Empyreans were catching up!

The saints possessed seven universes, each universe having Empyreans that numbered in the triple digits. With all the universes added together they had over a thousand Empyreans; this was an incomparably terrifying strength.

Compared to this, the ancient races were far too weak. Even with all of them combined together, they only had several dozen Empyreans, even less than humanity.

“In the cannon blast just now, how much energy was used up?”

The old God Sovereign calmly asked as he stood before the Asura Primal God Cannon’s array formation.

“Approximately 2%. At most we can send out 20 cannon blasts; we have to retain at least 60% energy for our protective barriers and the flight array formation. Moreover… if we fire the cannon too many times, we will also consume a considerable amount of strength…”

The Asura Primal God Cannon could burn energy stones to attack, but it needed an Empyrean to manage the array formation.

In order operate a Beyond Divinity level magic weapon, the pressure it placed on the Empyreans could be imagined!

“20 strikes…”

The old God Sovereign placed his palms together, rapping his fingers as he was lost in thought.

Without a doubt, there was a massive disparity in strength between the ancient races and the saints. It was impossible to make up for this difference by depending on the Ark of Hope alone.

Even if they sent out another 20 cannon blasts they wouldn’t be able to kill many more Empyreans. This was because the saint Empyreans were now wary and would avoid the direction of the Asura Primal God Cannon. This made killing these saint Empyreans far more difficult.

“Rush out. Don’t try to fight them.”

The old God Sovereign was incredibly calm. The Ark of Hope was the only thing they could rely on to escape, so they had to avoid the saints as much as they could. As long as they could break out of the encirclement and penetrate past the spatial barrier that surrounded the Chaos Star Ocean, they could use the Ark of Hope to warp forwards with a greater void shift. With that, they would be provided temporary safety.

But the saint Empyreans wouldn’t let the ancient races do as they wished.

In the void of the Primeval Universe, everyone was far away from each other. The low level martial artists had long since fled, leaving behind only the Empyreans.

Only an Empyrean level martial artist could play a role in fighting the Ark of Hope.

A blinding divine light wove through the starry void. Astral essence swelled forth, gushing out like a growing galaxy!

Many Empyreans attacked together. The scene was dazzling to the eyes.

“Slow them down, delay for time!”

Two peak saint Empyreans thrust out their hands. Golden astral essence transformed into giant palms that grabbed onto the Ark of Hope’s hull.

These two Empyreans attacked from a tricky angle. They avoided the Asura Primal God Cannon and chose a relatively safe area.

Soon after, another peak Empyrean summoned a magic tool. This magic tool was a large bronze bell. The bell rolled like an oncoming thunderstorm, smashing into the Ark of Hope!

Bam!

With a loud explosion, the giant bell smashed into the Ark of Hope’s defensive barrier!

The bell collapsed and was sent tumbling away. Although the Ark of Hope wasn’t damaged, the ship had used up a great deal of energy.

“Everyone strike! Move as far back as you can to attack and use up the ship’s energy! This ship should be a peak True Divinity spirit treasure. Although breaking it is impossible, as long as we can exhaust its energy supplies then that ridiculous pack of dead ancient races will be nothing but a turtle in a jar! We will be able to kill them as we please!”

The peak Empyrean who threw the bell shined with a golden light, his voice indifferent as he spoke.

“Haha, that’s right, we don’t need to frontally face them at all!”

The saint Empyreans all drew back, cold sneers on their face. They pulled out all sorts of magic tools and soon endless divine light enveloped the entire void for millions of miles!

The Ark of Hope’s energy was slowly consumed. The Empyreans managing the array formation also consumed their soul force.

The ancient race Empyreans were fighting an enemy with ten times their numbers!

Bang!

The Asura Primal God Cannon blasted out once more!

The thick beam of light pierced through the void, causing a horrifying energy storm to roll up.

However, the saint Empyreans were already prepared. They could keenly feel the Asura Primal God Cannon gathering energy and were able to move away a step ahead. Only a lower Empyrean, because he was too slow and his sense wasn’t too sharp, was sucked up into that energy storm.

After being pulled into the horrifying energy storm, that lower Empyreans was immediately reduced to ashes.

“Damn!”

One of the god race Empyreans managing the Asura Primal God Cannon pounded his fist onto the array formation’s altar. “The magic tool left behind by my ancestors has been shamed beneath my hands. Although the energy is powerful, my abilities are lacking and I cannot kill this damned pack of dogs!”

The Asura Primal God Cannon was too high grade a weapon. If the martial artists of the ancient remnant races wanted to operate it, they simply lacked the ability to freely use it. They were no different from little children picking up heavy axes and trying to wield them. It required far too much energy to lift the axe and their dexterity was lacking. As long as someone was fast enough and moved just a little, they could easily avoid the strike.

In front of the array formation’s altar, Lin Ming silently looked upon all of this. He was rapidly replaying the two blasts of the Asura Primal God Cannon.

The shimmering lights of the array formation’s runes reappeared in his mind as he constantly analyzed them…

Then, with another explosion, the hull trembled.

The saint Empyreans were barraging the protective barrier of the Ark of Hope.

Once the protective barrier was destroyed, the saint Empyreans could even invade the Ark of Hope and fight directly with those onboard. Once that happened, the 10 billion plus members of the ancient remnant races onboard would be slaughtered like lambs at the butcher, recklessly killed!

“The hull’s energy had been reduced to 95%...”

Someone reported. A gloomy cloud covered the old God Sovereign’s face. The leaders of the other ancient races also appeared ill. This was because the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had yet to appear…

The truth was that all the powerhouses present had already decided to bet their lives on this battle and were willing to give up their lives if needed. But if they used up all of their strength before the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign appeared, then their sacrifice would be meaningless.

The ancient races had already come to this point. All the Empyreans present, especially the elderly ones, no longer feared death. Death was not frightening, what was frightening was dying without meaning.

“Let me try…”

At this time, a hesitant and slightly unsure voice sounded out. Everyone turned. The one speaking was the only person in the central control room of the Ark of Hope that didn’t even have a World King cultivation – Lin Ming.

“You want to… control the Asura Primal God Cannon?”

The eyes of some of the elderly leaders lit up. Lin Ming had conjured numerous miracles already. If he were to propose something like this, everyone’s first reaction was hoping that he could create a miracle once more.

Lin Ming slowly nodded, his eyes still unsure. While he had studied the Asura Primal God Cannon’s array formation before this, he hadn’t obtained any substantial results.

The array formation was too unwieldy and the Laws involved were far too profound. Moreover, the requirement of absolute strength was extremely high.

After all, Lin Ming had yet to study the complete Asura Sutra; he wasn’t omnipotent.

“I can only say I can try, and I will also need your assistance. My strength is far too lacking to activate the Asura Primal God Cannon. I can only try to steer the direction so it is more accurate.”

Lin Ming discreetly said after deeply thinking over it.

“Great!”

Hearing Lin Ming’s words, many ancient race martial artists immediately perked up, their lowered morale somewhat restored.

In a corner of the room, Smokeless watched all of this occur, a strange light flashing in her eyes. She discovered that unknowingly, Lin Ming’s status within the ancient remnant races had become invaluable. Every word and action he took could inspire morale within the Empyreans; this was almost unthinkable.

“Open the array!” The old God Sovereign looked at Lin Ming, a wizened and affectionate smile on his face. Like the name of this spirit ship, what the ancient remnant races needed was hope.

And the peerless elites of the younger generation were the source of this hope. With Lin Ming here, the old God Sovereign felt much more at ease. His life was already winding down to its end. Even if he didn’t live to see the day that the ancient races overcame the great calamity, he could still die in peace.

Weng weng weng – !

Beneath the constant barrage of the saints, the Asura Primal God Cannon’s array formation activated once more!

For a time, the scattered energy within the universe began to crazily stir. The energy in the Primeval Universe was thin, but these energies were varied and profound, with all sorts of origin energies contained within it. Like a whale drinking water, all of these energies rolled up towards the Ark of Hope!

To absorb as much energy from the universe as possible while keeping the energy use of the Ark of Hope to the barest minimum, this was one of the changes Lin Ming made to the Asura Primal God Cannon’s array formation while operating it.

Of course, this change was all based upon Lin Ming’s profound understanding into the Asura Laws.

Chapter 1903 – The Power of the God Decrees

The saint Empyreans were naturally able to see how strange the spirit ship was. If they freely allowed it to escape and use great void shifts then it would be even more difficult to chase after them, and because of this they would all be guilty of failing in their duties.

On the other hand, if they could keep the ancient remnant races from escaping, they would be able to obtain generous rewards from the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. These past years, they had been busy guarding the Primeval Realm Ruins. And the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, as the most powerful True Divinity amongst the saints, his resources, whether in quality or quantity, were enough to make others drool with envy!

“The 12 of us can join together. We just have to be a bit more careful!”

A peak Empyrean sent out a sound transmission. The other peak Empyreans nodded.

“That blast just now must have consumed a considerable amount of their strength. If that cannon light divided into nine, there must have been an extreme degree of control behind it. With the soul force needed for such control, they shouldn’t be able to send out such a blast every time.”

A peak Empyrean analyzed the situation. He wore red robes and his figure was tall and wide. Amongst the 12 peak Empyreans, he held the greatest authority.

Magic tools were taken out one after another, forming a wall of light blocking out space.

They moved back, preparing to engage in a battle of attrition once more. They only wanted to delay the Ark of Hope and wait for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign to catch up to the battlefield.

As the supreme commander of the saints’ war, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign didn’t stay near the Chaos Star Ocean. The peak Empyreans only needed to hold the battlefield until his arrival.

“These fellows!”

A titan Empyrean gripped his fists; it was easy to see what the saint Empyreans’ plans were.

They needed to flee from the Chaos Star Ocean that was blocked in by a spatial barrier and then cross through space using great void shifts. Then, they needed to fly to the nearest edge of the God Lamenting Wall that bordered the Divine Realm, and break through that God Lamenting Wall to enter.

Woosh!

The red-robed peak Empyrean took out a gourd. As he opened this gourd, billowing black smoke gushed out, covering the surrounding space.

“It’s Allheaven Demon Smoke!”

Some god race martial artists recognized this demonic item. This was a rarely seen type of spirit treasure. The spirit treasure was in the form of smoke, and once it touched a magic tool it could corrode it.

Chi chi chi!

The Allheaven Demon Smoke sunk through the protective shields of the Ark of Hope, slowly draining away its energy.

“This person is troublesome!”

The celestial Patriarch thoughtfully said. This red-robed Empyrean faced the head of the ship and also faced the Asura Primal God Cannon. To do this meant that he had sufficient confidence in himself, otherwise he wouldn’t dare to stand in such a position. The other 11 peak Empyreans all spread out in other directions, encircling the Ark of Hope.

“Break out from the right side, that is where the protections are the weakest!”

Diwuhen suddenly said. The right side was where the old man with the divine bell was standing and he had already been injured by Lin Ming using the Asura Primal God Cannon. His divine bell had lost most of its spiritual power and it had also become deformed; it was clearly weakened tremendously.

If they broke through on that side, the resistance they faced would be much less.

But now, they couldn’t yet use the Asura Primal God Cannon. Without Lin Ming using the Asura Laws to guide the cannon, it would be almost impossible to aim the Asura Primal God Cannon in the right direction and hit a target.

“Let me!”

Looking at the saint Empyrean holding the divine bell, a cold light appeared on To Bagui’s face. He slowly traced his spatial ring and took out a plain wooden box.

Opening the wooden box, there was a yellow symbol paper inside. This was a god decree left behind by an ancient upper True Divinity and was one of the treasures that the celestials were willing to take out to repair the Chain of Calamity in order to receive three spots to enter the Asura forbidden zone.

But because of Lin Ming, this precious god decree didn’t need to be used so it was saved.

Not just that, but in the past month, this upper True Divinity god decree had also been repaired by Lin Ming. It had recovered the damaged energies it had lost over 10 billion years, and now its power was incomparable to how it was just a month ago.

“Wuhen, Whitemark, go with the Battle Sovereign and assist him!”

The old God Sovereign issued an order. Whitemark was one of the peak Empyreans of the god race; it was only that he was considerably old and didn’t have much time left remaining.

In Diwuhen and Whitemark’s hands, they each grasped an upper True Divinity god decree!

These three upper True Divinity god decrees were the trump cards of the ancient remnant races. Once they used them in battle they would display a terrifying effect, enough to reverse the tide of a battle.

“Look for a chance and rush out of this encirclement!”

The old God Sovereign felt that they couldn’t be delayed for much longer. He was well aware in his heart that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would soon catch up to them and that when he arrived, that would be the true final battle!

“You wretches, come and get it!”

To Bagui stepped onto the bow of the Ark of Hope, facing the saint Empyreans in the vast starry space.

Behind him stood Whitemark and Diwuhen.

As the saint Empyreans saw these people suddenly appear, they felt dread coil within them. But, they didn’t stop their barrage, instead only saving more strength to deal with any dangerous situations.

“Be careful!”

A saint Empyrean reminded. But at this time, with a loud humming sound, a horrifying divine light began to bloom from around To Bagui, making him blaze like a sun!

The common-looking ancient god decree in To Bagui’s hand melted away into light. For a time, countless Law runes spun around. These Law runes fluctuated and changed, finally turning into the phantom of a primal god ancestor.

This primal god ancestor held a long scythe in his hands as it rushed forwards like a god of death!

“Mm!?”

The saint Empyreans were horrified. As people with extraordinary vision, they could naturally see how terrifying this strike was!

As the divine bell peak Empyrean saw this attack his face drained of blood. This attack was specifically aimed at him!

The two peak Empyreans standing on either side of the divine bell old man wanted to help him, but they were locked down by Diwuhen and Whitemark’s killing intent.

The two peak Empyreans could see that Diwuhen and Whitemark were also holding onto yellow symbol papers.

Moreover, Diwuhen and Whitemark were both individually strong to begin with. With their killing intent locked onto the two peak Empyreans, the two peak Empyreans were too busy thinking of protecting themselves; neither of them was willing to risk their life to help rescue someone else.

Now, the divine bell old man had to face this god decree that was activated with all of To Bagui’s strength!

This was an upper True Divinity god decree. Even though a glorious period of 10 billion years had passed, it still possessed an incredibly destructive power!

“Humph! Do you think I’m easy to bully just because I’m injured!?”

As a peak Empyrean the divine bell old man was arrogant to his bones. Even though he was injured and realized how frightening this strike was, he didn’t think he would die like this.

He formed seals with his hands even as he drew backwards. At the same time, he stimulated his protective astral essence to its limits. The divine bell in his hands also spun outwards, emitting a clear ringing sound!

“Nine Suns Illuminate the Void!”

He roared. From the divine bell, nine spheres of light formed by astral essence shot out, linking together in a line in the void. They were like nine suns that came crashing down at the phantom of the death god.

But at this time, the death god also slashed down its scythe!

Hu - !

With a nearly indiscernible sound, like a gust of wind blowing open doors, the death god phantom vanished. It had only appeared for an instant and made this single strike.

This strike didn’t seem grandiose at all. The death god had only slashed down his scythe, with barely the whisper of a sound following it.

But this faint trace left behind by the strike remained in the skies. Silence spread, and the void seemed to be cut apart like thin paper, leaving behind a clear rift. As for that divine bell, it struck the tear in space with a ring and was immediately sliced in half.

Seeing this, the divine bell old man was left dazed. From his left shoulder to his right rib, a straight line of blood appeared.

And then, blood sprayed out.

The old man’s body shook and almost slipped apart!

“Guru Gold Bell!”

The saint Empyreans were dumbfounded!

From behind the divine bell old man, several peak Empyreans flash stepped towards him like bolts of lightning. As they reached him, they discovered that the divine bell old man’s situation was extremely bad; he was dead soon!

Empyreans of the saint race all had extremely formidable mortal bodies; even after suffering a serious physical wound they wouldn’t die. But in that strike just now, the death god’s energy had pierced through the old man’s flesh and blood, directly extinguishing his life force!

This was an irreversible loss that could not be recovered from. In other words, this divine bell old man was done for!

A peak Empyrean had been heavily wounded with one strike and would die in the next moment!

And in frontal combat and in a situation where the divine bell old man wasn’t injured, his combat strength wouldn’t be much worse than To Bagui’s!

“What terrifying power!”

To Bagui gasped, amazed. As one of the leaders of the celestials, he definitely knew how powerful the god decree in his hand had been. He also knew that after being repaired by Lin Ming, its strength should have risen even more.

But he didn’t think it would rise to such a degree!

Ever since the war began, this was the first time a peak Empyrean had died!

Generally speaking, when one reached the level of a peak Empyrean they could freely wander through the universe with a wide smile, with almost nothing being capable of threatening them. But in this battle, a peak Empyrean had died!

“Break through!”

The old God Sovereign firmly acted and sent out an order. The Ark of Hope changed directions, hurtling towards the nearly dead divine bell old man!

And on the bow of the Ark of Hope, Diwuhen and Whitemark tightly grasped the two other upper True Divinity god decrees, glaring at the other saint Empyreans!

With the threat of the god decrees present, the two peak Empyreans near the divine bell old man felt their breath catch in their throats. Neither of them dared to stop the spirit ship.

The miserable fate of the divine bell old man was openly displayed in front of them and they didn’t think they were much stronger than he was. Once they were targeted by those terrifying god decrees, even if they didn’t die they would suffer heavy wounds and either directly drop in cultivation boundaries or lose a tremendous portion of their lifespan.

As for the other nine peak Empyreans, they were hundreds of thousands of miles away; they couldn’t immediately help.

Bang!

With a thunderous rumble, the Ark of Hope used its dreadful speed and strength to break past the spatial barrier set down by the saint Empyreans and then rushed deep into the starry cosmos!

The Ark of Hope’s speed was astonishingly fast. With dozens of ancient race Empyreans joining forces to drive it, once the spirit ship broke past the blockade it would be difficult for Empyrean powerhouses to overtake them.

“Have we made it?”

An ancient race Empyrean held his breath. Did they really escape successfully?

Just as this thought passed through the minds of everyone, at this time, the old God Sovereign shook.

The old God Sovereign looked deep into the void of space. Within his old eyes, fear began to rise.

“…Heavens, what is that?”

Chapter 1904 – Good Fortune Saint Sovereign

At the words of the old God Sovereign, the ancient race martial artists all began looking out the porthole.

Through the deep porthole, amongst the endless ocean of stars that was the universe, they could see a dim blood red light.

Then, they could clearly see a massive crimson sphere, one that was 70,000-80,000 miles in diameter.

On the upper part of the crimson sphere, dozens of blood dragons recklessly roared out. Only half the bodies of these blood dragons appeared; they seemed to have been bred from within the crimson sphere, making them look like tentacles.

The blood dragons roared, revealing red fangs.

As the ancient race martial artists saw this titanic and horrifying beast appear, they were all struck dumb.

It didn’t seem like any vicious beast or God Beast they knew of, and the aura it emitted was over a hundred times more terrifying than a God Beast!

Facing this horrifying monster, the ancient race Empyreans felt their hearts quiver!

The crimson monster was incredibly fast. It was originally far off in the distant space, but in just several breaths of time it flew close, like a blood red ghost.

Deep red filled the universe. This feeling was like a drop of blood falling into clear water, slowly spreading out until it covered everyone’s eyes.

“This is…”

Even To Bagui, the war-hardened Battle Sovereign that never chose to give up, began to feel fear.

On the side of the primal god race, the old God Sovereign sucked in a breath of cold air. His wizened features had turned completely pale. As he looked out the porthole, he was unable to say anything. His heart began to slowly sink.

He was able to guess just what the origin of this monster was.

Billions of years ago, the ancient races had also fought with the saints. In the texts of the ancient races there were records about this dreadful monster.

But according to the information written down in these ancient texts, this monster should have had its soul erased billions of years ago and plunged into a state of eternal slumber.

Why… why would it reappear here?

Recalling the terrifying description of this monster from the ancient primal god race texts, the old God Sovereign felt as if he were drowning in despair!

“Could this really be… our destiny… do the heavens really wish to annihilate my god race?”

The old God Sovereign whispered. His words were heard by many ancient race Empyreans. They all looked at him with shock, “Your Majesty, what is that?”

At this time, not too far from the old God Sovereign, the celestial Patriarch spoke up. His voice trembled, making him seem far, far older in this moment.

“That is likely… ‘Famine’, the totem holy beast of the saint race… billions of years ago, Famine rampaged through the universes, devouring countless lives, including even many True Divinities.”

“What? Devouring True Divinities?”

The ancient race martial artists all shook.

In the current 33 Heavens, only two races possessed True Divinities – the saints and the spiritas. Even so, the number of True Divinities they had was extremely small! Among them were those who deliberately retired to their homelands and didn’t wish to participate in the disputes of the world, as well as those mysterious True Divinities who people weren’t even sure were still alive.

“I never would have imagined that Famine would still exist…” An old man from the roaring bone race deeply sighed as he shook his head. Many of the Empyreans present hadn’t read the ancient texts, and there weren’t many records of Famine to begin with.

“With our current strength, if we wish to overcome this great calamity we must slay the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign… that was already a nigh impossible mission to begin with, but now even Famine has appeared…”

The roaring bone old man looked away from the porthole. He shakily slumped into a chair, listless.

He was the Patriarch of the roaring bone race and one of the leaders of the ancient remnant races. According to custom, he shouldn’t have said anything that would lower the morale of the troops. But, the gloom in his heart was simply too great.

The appearance of Famine caused him to feel as if the world was collapsing.

“Famine… is it even stronger than the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign?”

Someone asked. The one who spoke up was Lin Ming. He had taken the soul recovery pill and was sitting in meditation. He had also seen the terrifying monster outside the porthole.

“Yes… according to the ancient texts, it is likely stronger than the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, and… it is absolutely more horrifying than the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. It can swallow, swallowing a trillion lives, swallowing even a world. The more it swallows, the more powerful it becomes. The speed at which it can destroy a world is a hundred times faster than the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!”

“I understand…” Lin Ming’s eyes darkened. Facing this new catastrophe, even he began to feel lost.

Humanity had to face the saints which were far, far stronger than them, and they also had to face the mysterious spiritas, whose goals were yet unknown…

The situation of humanity was becoming increasingly complex!

He recalled the strange conversation he had with Soul Empress Sheng Mei and he also recalled his meeting with the old youth, someone who he didn’t even know was a friend or foe.

With the arrival of the great calamity, all forces were surging upwards, everything becoming confusing.

As nothing but a little peak Holy Lord martial artist, no matter how many more lucky chances he had or how powerful his Laws were, in the end, without a formidable cultivation base he would be nothing but a tiny gust of wind in this great calamity. Just what could he do?

Lin Ming felt a sense of morbid exhaustion creep over his heart. In his ears, Sheng Mei’s words unconsciously echoed, “Give up and leave this storm, because all of your efforts will be for nothing… Don’t you know the story of Empyrean Divine Seal from 3.6 billion years ago? He was a truly peerless character, a True Dragon of the world, but he also chose to shoulder the destiny of humanity and in the end he died in battle. What a pity, what a loss!”

Lin Ming closed his eyes. He clenched his fists so hard that his knuckles emitted loud cracking noises!

“Look at that monster’s back!”

An ancient race Empyrean said.

Everyone looked over; they could see that the crimson monster was carrying two people on its back.

One was a tall and middle-aged man wearing a gold cloak. The other was a handsome young man with sharp eyebrows and gloomy eyes.

Seeing these two people, the old God Sovereign’s complexion changed. “That man… is the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign! His body, how could it… has he become one with Famine?”

The old God Sovereign muttered with disbelief thick in his voice. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s legs had sunk into Famine’s body. Moreover, he could see that the flesh and blood of Famine was spreading into the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, their blood vessels linked together.

As if Famine was swallowing the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

However, logic told him this was impossible. Perhaps it was the opposite… the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had swallowed Famine, or perhaps Famine had even become the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s avatar!

“So he… is the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign…”

Lin Ming looked at the man wearing the golden cloak. This was the first time he had laid eyes upon the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. He could feel this other person’s eyes pierce through the vastness of space and gaze upon him.

This was a bizarre feeling. They were separated by a great distance of space as well as the Ark of Hope’s protective shields, so it should have been impossible for him to be seen. But for some reason, Lin Ming felt as if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was looking at him, as if there were no barriers between the two.

And standing beside the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was someone Lin Ming was long since acquainted with – the Good Fortune Saint Son.

At this time, the Good Fortune Saint Son had a wild grin on his face. This was the smile of a victor, carrying with it a hint of pity, a hint of ridicule!

And then, beyond Lin Ming’s imagination, the Good Fortune Saint Son began to speak.

His voice spread through millions of miles of space using energy as a medium.

“Lin Ming! I know you are onboard that spirit ship! Today is the day you die, hahahaha!

“The day of our hundred year duel has yet to truly arrive, right? Unfortunately, you won’t have such a chance. Today you will be killed!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son raved. Lin Ming’s heart skipped a beat; the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign knew he was with the primal god race!

But why would the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign know his whereabouts?

Lin Ming had carefully disguised and hidden himself away and was positive he hadn’t been discovered by the saints.

If his whereabouts were revealed in this sort of situation, then it was either because there was a spy amongst the god race, or Sheng Mei had informed the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign of his location.

The chances of it being a spy weren’t too great. This was because the ancient races didn’t know of Lin Ming’s past history with the saints. Moreover, after the escape plan was finalized, all information was limited to the high level figures of the ancient races in order to prevent anything from being leaked out.

Then… could it be Sheng Mei?

Lin Ming faintly frowned. Although he and Sheng Mei were no longer friends, and might even be enemies, he still didn’t believe that Sheng Mei would betray him like this.

Perhaps, when he left the Soul World and entered the Primeval Universe, his location might have been locked down by the Soul Emperor. For the Soul Emperor, this wouldn’t be difficult.

“The Soul Emperor… does he want to sentence me to death?”

 But as these thoughts flashed through Lin Ming’s mind, in the starry skies, that massive crimson sphere suddenly distorted!

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Atop the blood sphere, dozens of fierce red dragons roared and came rushing forwards!

These blood dragons possessed an overwhelming killing intent. They tore through the void, manically racing forwards!

And their target was the Ark of Hope!

“This is bad!”

The Empyreans managing the Ark of Hope’s array formation began to panic. They did everything they could to control the array formation and change the direction of the Ark of Hope.

But with their abilities, how could they compare with Famine?

Bang!

A loud explosion rang out. Dozens of fierce dragon tentacles smashed into the Ark of Hope’s protective shield!

The Ark of Hope violently shook, nearly spinning around. The Empyreans within were able to use energy to stabilize their bodies, but the common ancient race citizens were far worse off. They cried out in alarm, some of them even injured in the fierce impact.

“Damn it!”

To Bagui was incensed. They were originally about to escape into the heavens and break through the God Lamenting Wall, but at this critical moment they had encountered such a disaster! All of their plans were toppling over!

“That strike just now consumed 2% of the hull’s energy!”

A roaring bone race Empyrean reported. Famine’s attack had used up 2% of the ship’s energy; this was the same as a single blast from the Asura Primal God Cannon. If this continued, they wouldn’t be able to last too many strikes before the Ark of Hope’s energy was used up!

“Haha! Lin Ming, aren’t you strong? What? You don’t have the strength to fight back?”

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s voice reverberated in space, insolent beyond compare.

Chapter 1905 – Asura Decree

Bang! Bang! Bang!

The dreadful crimson monster far off in the vast starry space formed numerous blood red dragons that smashed into the Ark of Hope’s protective shield.

The Empyreans directing the spirit ship were completely unable to control the its movements. For a time, the entire spirit ship began to violently rock like a small leaf caught in a storm.

“Energy reserves have been reduced to below 90%!”

An Empyrean shouted. If this continued it wouldn’t be long before the Ark of Hope’s energy reserves were completely depleted. At that time, they would all die!

“The time has come. We can only use our final trump cards.”

The celestial Patriarch said. He looked towards the old God Sovereign and sighed.

The so-called final cards were in truth the god decrees left behind by the Asura Road Master.

These were god decrees personally drawn by the Asura Road Master; there was a total of three.

One offensive, one sealing, one support!

As Beyond Divinity level treasures, if a peak Empyrean were to activate these god decrees they would have to burn away most of their life as the cost in order to potentially kill a True Divinity.

Of course, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was not an ordinary True Divinity. To kill the Good Sovereign Saint Sovereign might be impossible, but they should still be able to at least heavily wound him. And if they combined the other two Asura Decrees and the rest of their god decrees, they might really be able to exterminate the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!

However, currently, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had somehow fused together with the body of Famine.

The abyssal demon – Famine.

An inconceivable existence with an incomparably terrifying life force. If they only burned part of their lives to activate the god decrees left behind by the Asura Road Master, would they even be able to severely wound it?

Everyone’s hearts grew heavy with doubt. If they couldn’t severely wound Famine, how could they hope to escape?

The old God Sovereign silently traced his spatial ring. He slowly said, “I never imagined that as we stood on the precipice of life or death, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would show up even more formidable than before. I originally thought that with our god decrees and the peak Empyreans of my race burning their life to activate them, they could at least pose a threat to the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. But now it seems that merely burning a part of their life won’t be enough… in fact, even a peak Empyrean alone will be insufficient…”

“Everyone… who is willing to step up?”

The old God Sovereign never thought that things would turn out like this.

Only peak Empyreans could activate the Asura Decrees. And in this situation, in order to display the greatest might of the Asura Decrees and damage Famine as much as they could, those activating the god decrees would have to completely burn away every last vestige of their life. In order words… that was to sacrifice themselves!

Moreover, a single person wasn’t enough!

With all the Empyreans of the ancient races added together, there were a total of seven peak Empyreans; this was a relatively high number.

Seven peak Empyreans. Three god decrees.

The old God Sovereign planned to have two peak Empyreans activate the first god decree together!

Two was the best number. The second Empyrean would only be able to increase the might of the Asura Decree by less than half, and a third Empyrean would add even less than that.

Originally, activating the Asura Decrees didn’t mean death, thus the old God Sovereign was willing to appoint others to use them.

But now, using them meant certain death. So the old God Sovereign didn’t force anyone, but instead asked those present.

The old God Sovereign’s elderly eyes swept over the peak Empyreans present. Guilt showed heavily on his face. He also desired to go to battle, but… he couldn’t die now. During this escape, they needed a leader to command the troops, and he was the backbone of the ancient races.

“I am willing to go to battle…”

An old primal god Empyrean said. He was a peak Empyrean and had already lived for 80-90 million years. He was reaching the twilight of his years and didn’t have much time left remaining.

“I also want to go…”

“Allow me!”

“I volunteer!”

…….

Peak Empyreans stood up one after another. This great calamity involved the life or death of their people. These ancient race Empyreans had long since hardened their resolves and were willing to die.

Seeing so many Empyreans stand up, the old God Sovereign’s wizened eyes filled with tears. Now, he had to choose.

Those he chose would be those that died!

Lin Ming stood not too far away, silently watching all of this occur. Besides the old God Sovereign, the other six peak Empyreans didn’t avoid their duties at all. And Lin Ming knew that if the old God Sovereign needed to sacrifice his life, he wouldn’t have even blinked in doing so.

This scene left Lin Ming shocked.

A feeling that had long been absent from his heart began to quietly linger within him. He clenched his fists.

Some people fought in order to kill others and steal their possessions.

Some people fought to take revenge and cut down their enemies.

Some people fought to obtain lucky chances and treasures.

But, there were also those who fought and were even willing to sacrifice themselves all for the sake of others, for the sake of the greater good and the continuation of their people…

“Wuhen, Battle Sovereign, the two of you draw back!” The old God Sovereign waved his hand. The Battle Sovereign and Diwuhen were both Empyreans in the peak of their prime. They were the hopes and future leaders of the ancient races in this great calamity, and it was impossible for the old God Sovereign to sacrifice them.

“But…”

“Your Majesty…”

Diwuhen and To Bagui’s eyes turned red and misty, but the old God Sovereign had directly dismissed them.

“Whitemark, Dugu, I am sorry…”

The old God Sovereign chose two people, both of them peak Empyreans of the primal god race. The old God Sovereign silently closed his eyes, two lines of tears running down his wrinkled face…

“Understood!”

“Great!”

The two old Empyreans stepped forwards. As Lin Ming saw their white hair and bent backs, he didn’t know what to feel.

The other ancient race martial artists looked at them and were unable to restrain the sorrow in their hearts.

“If you have any words you wish to say…”

The old God Sovereign asked.

Whitemark was silent. He took out a scroll painting from his spatial ring and a jade pendant. He silently unrolled the scroll. The paper of this drawing was extremely ancient, as if it had been stored away for an illustrious span of time.

The painting on the scroll was of a childish and innocent youth. The youth had a jade pendant hanging from his waist, the exact same as the one Whitemark was holding.

“This is my grandchild. His natural talent couldn’t be considered too great, but he was diligent in his youth and always gave his best efforts. During his youth, he stubbornly left to go adventuring, and he entered the Primeval Realm Ruins to temper himself in the dangers of the mystic realms there. But after that, he didn’t return…”

The old man’s voice was aged and hoarse. This was his only grandchild. The primal god race was a race that wasn’t accepted by the Heavenly Dao. They could not compare to the three peak races because their reproductive capabilities were extremely poor.

They had few descendants, and even then the descendants of Empyreans weren’t necessarily peerless geniuses. The reasons that the humans and saints were able to find talents amongst their ranks was because of their thriving populations. Their innumerable descendants were screened through layer upon layer of tests until the best were remaining.

“If you can find him, please take care of him for me. In my life, he is my only remaining worry…”

The old man passed the two items to Diwuhen.

Diwuhen didn’t know what to feel. He parted his lips as if he wanted to say something, but no words came out. He eventually sighed.

He knew that the chances of finding this young man were nearly nonexistent.

In all likelihood… he had already perished. However, in the primal god race that had low numbers to begin with, they valued their descendants above all and couldn’t bear the thought of losing them or even giving up on them.

In particular, now that Whitemark was soon about to die, in his heart he hoped that this own bloodline could continue onwards…

“Dugu, and you…?”

The old God Sovereign looked at the other Empyrean, his eyes wet.

Dugu looked back indifferently, slowly shaking his head.

Compared to Whitemark, Dugu had grown up in the wilderness since his youth, living by drinking the blood of birds and beasts. His disposition was more detached.

Once, he had ventured into the Primeval Realm Ruins as an assassin. His hands were stained with the blood of saint martial artists.

“I have nothing much to say. I have no descendants, only myself…”

Dugu’s eyes were neither sad nor happy. Instead, they contained a calm tranquility and an iron-hard resoluteness.

He had once been young, and he had also deeply loved someone.

However… in his long life, the woman he loved was not able to give birth to a child.

The reproductive capabilities of the primal god race were far too low. It was as if the Heavenly Dao had placed a curse upon them…

He had arrived alone in this world and now he would die alone. Perhaps this was his fate for being an assassin, but presently, he was no longer an assassin…

The spirit ship’s atmosphere was tense and heavy.

Worry, fear, anger, and even sorrow towards the future.

Every person’s eyes flashed with light, their minds filled with thoughts.

Everyone watched as Dugu and Whitemark left.

The two of them stepped onto the bow of the ship.

The Good Fortune Saint Son looked at these two old men on the bow of the ship and diabolically grinned. “Two fools seeking death!”

Beside the Good Fortune Saint Son, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s attention was raptly focused on the two old men.

The two of them were peak Empyreans in the waning years of their lives. This was not enough for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign to feel fear for, but the black symbol paper in their hands was actually startling.

“That is… a god decree? Good! Then let me see just what this ultimate power is like!

The pure black god decree carried with it an endless slaughter aura. Beneath Whitemark’s control, it slowly floated upwards.

Whitemark calmly looked at the god decree floating before him. Then, with a resonant shout, a brilliant blood red light lit up his eyes. Winds rose up around his body. His hair fluttered upwards and his robes flapped about.

In this moment, he emitted a blinding light. Vast waves of life force gushed out of him like raging rivers, endlessly surging into the middle of the god decree.

And in the next moment, all of his blood boiled over to the surface, rushing towards the god decree. The old Empyrean’s body was soaked in a dazzling divine light.

Then, divine light also lit up around Dugu.

His face was still cold and indifferent, but now it contained a deep unyielding and unwilling gaze!

His life had reached its terminus and this would not change. But, he didn’t want the future generations of the primal god race to share his fate!

“If the heavens must destroy my god race, then with my god blood, let me turn into demonic flames that burn down the skies!”

Dugu’s blood began to burn.

This was the final brilliance released from combusting his very life!

In that instant, the god decree seemed to come alive. Fluctuations emanated from within it.

Although this was only simple fluctuations, it was like a divine weapon that had lain dormant for a trillion years was stirring, releasing a terrifying aura.

A massive black Asura phantom began to slowly appear…

Chapter 1906 – Blood Dyes the Starry Skies

With the appearance of the pitch black Asura warrior standing atop the spirit ship, Lin Ming could feel his heart begin to race. The Asura blood within his body trembled and the Black Dragon Spear fused into his body also began to emit a keening cry.

These forces that were incorporated into Lin Ming’s body began to resonate with the god decree’s Asura phantom.

“Asura Road Master…” Light passed over Lin Ming’s eyes.

Compared to the previous True Divinity level god decrees that had burned away, this aura was abnormally sharp.

As the Asura warrior phantom’s image became increasingly clear, the smell of blood and iron also spread outwards, as if the entire surrounding space had turned into a merciless killing field.

A boundless vorpal light shot out from his pupils, casting out through the universe.

The god decree rose up in strength once more. Like a sun, it emitted endless rays of light.

The Asura warrior was covered by this light. A black long spear formed in his hands and he rushed out from the spirit ship, hurtling into the distance.

Rumble rumble rumble.

Outside the snow-white spirit ship, waves of attacks struck like a tide, emitting horrifying sounds like the beating of a great drum that caused the heart to race.

“The Asura Road Master’s god decree? You want to use this to resist me? Lin Ming, as well as those old bags of bones from the ancient races, today you will all become food for Famine!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign ruthlessly sneered, his complexion cold. In his eyes, the primal god race were nothing but a sun finally setting beneath the mountains. Although they still had some qualifications left, against the rising saints and their irresistible momentum, they were nothing but dogs and chickens.

Now, on this day, he wanted this once incomparably glorious race to vanish in the endless flow of time.

Thinking this, a blood red light lit up his eyes.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

The dozens of fierce blood dragons were like infinitely long whips. They all completely halted their attacks and immediately retracted, surrounding the vast crimson sphere.

At the same time, a dragon tentacle fell down onto a giant saint race warship, allowing the Good Fortune Saint Son to drop down.

In a moment, those fierce dragons turned into layers of flesh and blood shields, forming countless walls, surrounding the massive planet-sized ball of flesh.

After being locked onto by the Asura Decree, dodging was unrealistic. Moreover, with Famine’s body being so large, dodging would be impossible to begin with.

The Asura warrior trod through space, a massive black dragon spear grasped in his hand. Endless rays of black light radiated from him.

Each ray of light covered tens of thousands of miles of space.

Some saint race spirit ships that were too close were swept up in the light. Then, like kites caught in an explosion, all of them burst apart into black fireballs. From within the spirit ships, countless pained howls echoed out.

The Asura warrior became one with his spear. Boundless potent might gushed out from him, rippling out in all directions.

The surrounding void began to shake like a tossing sea. Space cracked without end and even nearby celestial bodies began collapsing.

Many saint race spirit ships rapidly retreated. Some of those that were fast enough were able to escape the blinding light, but those that didn’t withdraw in time were disintegrated.

The Asura warrior and the long spear in his hands seemed to transform into an endless column of black light that hurtled into the center of that giant blood red ball.

Pitch black light and blood red light covered the endless starry space, making it impossible to clearly see what was happening.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Waves of heaven-shaking detonations occurred. Many pieces of meat scattered outwards and burned away. The void was pierced through all around, causing massive space storms to sweep out.

In the shockwaves of that terrifying attack, even the universe seemed to crack open.

Seeing this occur, the eyes of the primal god race powerhouses in the white spirit ship began to light up with hope.

As for those in the saint race spirit ships, all of them fell quiet, the atmosphere solemn and earnest.

The battle outside had only lasted for a single strike.

But the vast momentum and heaven-collapsing energy made it impossible for anyone to approach. In fact, they likely couldn’t even withstand the fallout.

“This is a god decree left behind by God Sovereign Asura? Our Sovereign… there shouldn’t be a problem, right?” Someone murmured.

In that dreadful impact, the Asura warrior and his black spear began to slowly fade away.

All that was left over was limitless black lights that continued to burn and emit thunderous rumbling sounds.

And at this time, in the center of the explosions at a place surrounded by endless black light, a fierce blood dragon suddenly shot out.

Then –

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Fierce dragon after fierce dragon drilled out, tearing open the void that was distorted by the black light. Famine’s giant bloated body forcefully ripped open the void and pushed out from the horrifying space storms.

“It’s alive…”

Seeing Famine appear, the old God Sovereign blanched. Although he had planned for the worst situation to occur, as he really saw this happen he almost suffocated.

Woosh!

A mountain-thick whip of meat penetrated the void and smashed against the Ark of Hope.

This powerful blow was enough to crush a planet. The spirit ship hummed as trillions of runes flashed and dissipated.

“Damn it all!”

The Ark of Hope shakily flew away.

At this time, more and more blood red dragons thrust out, thoroughly scattering the black light that covered Famine.

With this, everyone saw Famine, which had been injured by the Asura Decree.

Within that titanic ball of blood meat, there was a massive fissure that was thousands of miles deep!

A great deal of Famine’s flesh had turned into bloody water that spread out. A number of fierce dragons had been cut off and they wriggled on the surface of Famine like worms.

Then, these cut off worms melted away, fusing back into Famine.

Famine could swallow all, and it could even swallow its severed limbs to reabsorb them.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign stoop atop this massive ball of meat, his expression murderous. Blood vessels had torn open and exploded all over his body, causing him to be drenched in blood and seem like a demon.

The Asura Decree’s strongest blow had been aimed towards him. If it weren’t for Famine blocking the strike for him then he would have been grievously wounded, and there was even a chance he might have died.

“Asura Road Master, you are really fierce… just a wisp of your remnant aura is able to injure me like this! But so what! You are already dead, and now I will make sure all your descendants become extinct!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had not tasted such pain in a hundred million years. With overweening arrogance, raging anger kindled within him.

Seeing this, those within the Ark of Hope were frightened.

Inside the spirit ship, there was nothing but silence.

“Not even that could kill him!” Someone cried out in fear, their eyes clouding over with despair.

To Bagui’s complexion was somber; he was already at a loss for words. Two peak god race Empyreans had been sacrificed and an Asura Decree had been used, and the only result they managed to get in return was a wound on the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. This caused a heavy pall to fall on everyone’s mind.

Without a doubt, this showed that after the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign fused with that abyssal, his strength had increased astronomically. His vitality now far exceeded that of an ordinary True Divinity and not even an Asura Decree could kill him.

“For you lot to accomplish this… is indeed surprising. But, don’t think you will have a second chance to injure me.” As the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign towered above the massive ball of flesh, his eyes glowed with a cold light.

Space rumbled like an endlessly rolling thundercloud. The sound seemed to link straight into the hearts of everyone, daunting them with a horrifying pressure.

On Famine’s body where the fierce dragons had been cut off, the flesh began to wriggle about. With a gurgling sound, a new fierce dragon thrust out.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign thrust out a hand and pointed towards the white spirit ship.

Rays of blood red light shot out like bolts of crimson lightning. They formed layers of red enchantments that surrounded the white spirit ship.

Each red enchantment was like an invisible great hand, squeezing down with incredible power.

The white spirit ship’s defensive shield emitted cracking sounds. More and more energy rapidly dissipated.

“The ship has less than 85% energy remaining! We won’t be able to hold much longer!” A primal god race Empyrean managing the spirit ship loudly shouted with a shaky voice towards the old God Sovereign.

An anxious and strained atmosphere covered the entire ship along with the increasingly loud squeezing sounds from outside.

Each cracking sound seemed to be squeezing down on the hearts of the ancient race martial artists.

Outside, the saint race spirit ships gathered together. Their war cries blasted out like thunder, reverberating through the cosmos.

What could they do?

Some people clenched their fists. Anger lit up in their eyes along with unwillingness.

Some people closed their eyes in pain. They were once the strongest race with a legacy that continued through the endless years. But now, they had been reduced to this.

More people looked outside, their eyes boiling over with radiance. At this time, Battle Sovereign To Bagui stepped forwards. He shouted out, “Even if we must die, we will die with glory and honor! Your Majesty God Sovereign, please give the order to send out my celestial race! I am willing to lead the numerous martial artists of my people to serve as the vanguard!”

The ancient races were all proud and arrogant people. Their races had once experienced infinite grandeur. In the midst of blood and iron, that was where their lives should bloom with the greatest light. How could they submit themselves to dying cowardly deaths?

The voices of those desiring to fight suddenly rose up like a rising tide.

Empyreans began stepping forwards one after another. In particular, those Empyreans in the prime of their lives were extremely excited, all of them wishing to go out and slaughter as much as they could.

When those two elderly Empyreans had sacrificed themselves, they had done so in order to preserve these robust young Empyreans and have them revive the ancient races in the future.

“Everyone calm down!”

The old God Sovereign angrily scolded. For a time, everyone fell quiet.

“We… have not yet reached a dead end. We still have two Asura Decrees!”

The old God Sovereign lifted his hand. Above his hand, two black god decrees still floated, bathed in a divine light.

As the god race Empyreans saw these two god decrees, their eyes filled with a complex color.

In order to activate an Asura Decree, it required peak Empyreans to combust their life – this was a tremendous price. And even then, they had only been able to wound the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and weren’t able to kill him.

Although they had two remaining, was there still a use for them…?

Seeing the skepticism of the Empyreans, the old God Sovereign said, “We won’t sit idly by, but we won’t die in vain either. These two Asura Decrees are different!”

Chapter 1907 – The Changes of Time

“There are two god decrees, one with the word Seal and the other with the word Faith. The word of Seal is a great sealing technique, capable of binding the soul and destroying a spirit mark.

“But the word of Faith is a supportive technique. It can have a martial artist dig out the greatest potential of their life for a short period of time, obtaining a strength ten times greater than what they have!

“However, the target of the word of Faith should be a True Divinity. Only a True Divinity can withstand such a potent power.

“For a peak Empyrean, their body and foundation is more vulnerable and if they were forced to withstand the power of the word of Faith then their body might collapse from the influx of strength. Even if they could withstand it, they wouldn’t be able to fight for long. It would be the same as burning away their life for battle…”

As the old God Sovereign spoke, Diwuhen stepped forth.

“Honorable Master, allow me to withstand it!”

“I will do it! The losses to the god race are not small and when it comes to the mortal body, my celestial race is slightly more formidable than the god race.” To Bagui said. If an old Empyrean were to have an Asura Decree used on them, then their body would simply disintegrate on the spot. Only a peak Empyrean in the prime of their life would be able to show the potential of the word of Faith.

However, the old God Sovereign shook his head. “You two… cannot withstand it…”

“What… this…”

Diwuhen was worried. He and To Bagui were the two individuals that had the greatest vitality within the ancient remnant races. The ancient races were races that were able to triple cultivate essence, energy, and divine. To Bagui and Diwuhen had both cultivated body transformation before. If they couldn’t withstand it, then who could?

The old God Sovereign took a deep breath as if he were coming to a decision.

“Lin Ming, come with me…”

The old God Sovereign’s words were lonely and desolate. Lin Ming was startled. Faintly, he seemed to realize something.

The surrounding Empyreans were confused about what was occurring. They didn’t know what the old God Sovereign was calling Lin Ming for. Although Lin Ming had amazing attainments in the Laws, in terms of overall combat strength he was beneath the Empyreans present.

“Senior God Sovereign, you…”

Lin Ming hesitated. But, the old God Sovereign only continued forwards, not turning around. The old God Sovereign whispered, “I never thought… I never thought that his words would finally come true…

“In the end, that there would be such a day.

“In the end, he cannot escape the past…”

As the old God Sovereign spoke, they finally arrived in front of a plain and heavy stone door. This stone door was pure black and was carved with mysterious patterns.

Lin Ming had seen this stone door once before. He always felt that it was similar to a tombstone.

When the god race headquarters was evacuated into the Ark of Hope, this secret chamber was also moved in. This stone door was the entrance to the chamber.

Lin Ming was silent. He watched on as the old God Sovereign pushed open the stone door. Behind it he could feel a fierce and brutal… demonic aura!

This demonic aura surged into the vast space, incomparably suppressing. A deep and bass roar howled out like the screams of a wild animal, filled with endless fury and murderous intent, flooding the chamber and echoing without end!

Empyrean Primordius…

Lin Ming listened to the roars in this chamber and his mind filled with inexplicable memories. In the deep dark he saw the two blood red pupils. They were familiar, enough to make his heart quicken.

This ferocious great beast seemed to crawl up from an abyss. Horns jutted out from its head and its grand body was tied down with layers and layers of chains. Its blood red pupils were full of madness and slaughter.

It heavily panted, its horrifying eyes tightly fixated on Lin Ming. Inside these eyes were nothing but bloodthirsty desires!

Empyrean Primordius had once possessed the Grandmist Spirit Bead. Using it, he opened the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace and reached large success in body transformation.

He was an extreme talent. If it weren’t for the saints trying to kill him off ahead of time then Empyrean Primordius might have been able to complete his Grandmist Samsara Dao and become another Asura Road Master!

Afterwards, although Empyrean Primordius had been grievously wounded and he lost the Grandmist Spirit Bead, he still managed to seize the body of an abyssal.

This abyssal demon’s body was even stronger than a God Beast!

The current Empyrean Primordius was a peak Empyrean who had opened the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace and had fused with an abyssal.

Because he had lost his rationality, his combat strength was greatly diminished. Even so, in terms of just the mortal body, he had reached the peak!

If… he were supported with the Asura Decree and all the potential of his life were dug out, then he would become unbelievably powerful.

Just how much potential did the current Empyrean Primordius possess? Lin Ming found this hard to imagine!

“God Sovereign, do you plan… to have Senior Primordius go to battle?”

Lin Ming sighed inwardly, not knowing what he felt. A hero who had reached his end, who had lost his road, even so he still desired to rush onto the battlefield, even if this meant dying in foreign lands!

The old God Sovereign silently nodded.

Lin Ming remembered the words Empyrean Primordius had carved into the stone of the chamber –

‘I have become a demon, and I fear death no more. But once I die in this strange land, will my ashes return to my homeland?’

‘Time to time clarity returns to me, time to time I am lost in chaos. I know that one day I will devolve into a base beast. On that day, do not kill me, and do not seal me away forever. Wait until the great army of the saints arrives and let my demon body enter the camp of the saints, drinking thirstily of their blood, devouring my fill of their flesh! Let me die heroically in battle!’

Recalling Empyrean Primordius’ words and the current Empyrean who howled and who had lost all the brightness in his eyes, Lin Ming felt a deep and abiding sadness.

The old God Sovereign gently patted Lin Ming’s shoulder. “Do not feel guilty. To die on the battlefield is the greatest desire that Empyrean Primordius repeated to me before he devolved into a mindless demon…”

Even with these words, Lin Ming found this hard to accept. Although this was Primordius’ wish, to have him rush out and sacrifice himself in a state where he had no rational thoughts, Lin Ming found this difficult to understand.

Lin Ming hoped that at least in the end, when Primordius’ life was at its twilight, he could decide for himself and see why he was fighting.

“Senior God Sovereign, can this junior try to awaken just a tiny sliver of Empyrean Primordius’ awareness?”

If Lin Ming could try awakening Primordius’ consciousness, even just a little, then he would be able to realize the Laws. And with being able to understand combat tactics, his battle efficiency would rise dramatically!

“Can you?”

The old God Sovereign was shocked. Lin Ming even had such an ability?

This involved the most mysterious soul domain of the body. Moreover, this was a most troublesome case of soul fusion and disassociation of personality. Even a spiritas supreme elder that was skilled in the soul arts would be left powerless and frustrated.

“If I can ignore all potential damages to his spiritual sea, then perhaps I can try… Senior God Sovereign, could you calm down Senior Primordius as much as you can?”

Lin Ming had once wanted to probe Empyrean Primordius’ spiritual sea, but he was almost killed by the berserk Empyrean Primordius.

The old God Sovereign nodded. An energy that seemed to accept all formed a sea of energy that slowly soaked Empyrean Primordius’ body.

Lin Ming’s complexion was earnest. He took a step towards this horrifying abyssal.

Roar - !

Just as Lin Ming approached a little, Empyrean Primordius howled and slashed out his claws. The great shaking strength passed through the air, aimed at Lin Ming!

But in that moment, a warm and vast energy surged out from behind Lin Ming, counterbalancing the killing power of Empyrean Primordius.

The old God Sovereign was completely focused. He didn’t dare to use too much strength for fear of enraging Primordius. Once Primordius went crazy, even the old God Sovereign wouldn’t be able to stop him. Primordius was a terrifying killing machine!

Seeing this, Lin Ming’s heart settled a little. He floated up and forwards until he was just three feet away from Empyrean Primordius’ giant black head.

Then, using the power of divinity and power of grandmist, Lin Ming slowly stimulated the Magic Cube’s energy, trying to fuse it with Empyrean Primordius’ spiritual sea.

At this time, Lin Ming could no longer care about hiding the Magic Cube.

And the old God Sovereign clearly realized Lin Ming had a soul-related treasure within his body.

“There exists a treasure that can separate a spiritual sea?”

The old God Sovereign was dumbstruck, but, he didn’t ask any questions. He naturally realized just how dreadfully valuable such a treasure must be.

Lin Ming had far too many secrets on him, enough to leave one numb.

The energy gradually penetrated into Empyrean Primordius’ giant head. Lin Ming was attempting to use the Magic Cube to peel away the abyssal demon’s soul. As long as he could destroy a part of the abyssal’s soul mark then he would be able to slowly awaken Empyrean Primordius’ memories.

The Magic Cube excelled in erasing spirit marks. But because too much time had passed, the abyssal demon’s spirit mark had fused together with Empyrean Primordius. If he wanted to erase the abyssal demon’s spirit mark without injuring Empyrean Primordius’ soul, that was nearly impossible.

Thus, Lin Ming could only disregard any damages that might occur to Empyrean Primordius’ soul. He didn’t think he could fully awaken Empyrean Primordius; all he needed to do was awaken him a little.

Empyrean Primordius’ eyes blurred and his vision turned blank. Lin Ming carefully continued, beads of sweat dripping down his forehead.

He had to be utterly careful; there could not be a single accident.

He knew there wasn’t much time left remaining. Facing the wild attacks of Famine, the Ark of Hope’s energy reserves reduced again and again. As for the violent vibrations of the Ark of Hope, all of that was weakened by the old God Sovereign’s energy in order to reduce the impact of the vibrations on Lin Ming as much as possible.

Chapter 1908 – Love and Pain

“A little more… just… a little bit more…”

Lin Ming clenched his teeth, unable to spare any effort to wipe the beads of sweat dripping down his face. In a situation where he was completely disregarding any possible damage he might do to Empyrean Primordius’ spiritual sea, he was attempting to awaken those long slumbering memories.

Beneath the shrouding of the Magic Cube’s divine light, a rare brightness appeared in Empyrean Primordius’ eyes.

However, this clarity appeared for just the briefest moment before they were once again submerged by blood red light.

Two different minds alternated back and forth. Primordius’ body violently trembled as a pain swelled up from his soul.

Primordius began to struggle. That tough and iron-like body contained an incomprehensible level of strength!

For a time, crackling sounds filled the air as the energy shackles that the old God Sovereign placed on Empyrean Primordius to calm him down began to emit breaking sounds, unable to endure the pressure.

The old God Sovereign’s complexion changed.

“Lin Ming! Be careful!”

Once Primordius went out of control, the damage would be incalculable. With Lin Ming’s current degree of cultivation and bodily defense, Primordius would only need a single strike to disintegrate his body!

“Lin Ming, draw back, I cannot hold him for much longer!”

The old God Sovereign’s forehead was wet with sweat. However, at this time, Lin Ming’s soul force was completely poured into the Magic Cube as he tried to connect with Empyrean Primordius’ spiritual sea.

Roar!

Primordius howled, the raging sound as turbulent as tsunamis and collapsing mountains. If an ordinary Holy Lord were to face such a roar then their head would blow up and they would die where they stood.

Peng!

Empyrean Primordius’ upper arm shook. The energy shackles binding him there were torn apart!

This process wasn’t difficult at all. It was just as if Primordius had broken a little branch in half.

The old God Sovereign paled. Without caring for anything else, he grabbed Lin Ming’s shoulder and released his protective power of divinity to the limit. He was ready to pull Lin Ming back at full speed the moment Primordius went berserk.

It was not easy for Lin Ming to awaken Primordius’ consciousness. This was because stripping away parts of an individual’s psyche would inevitably cause agonizing pain to the soul, enough to make Primordius lose all control.

Roar!

Empyrean Primordius wildly howled. A terrifying energy storm struck the old God Sovereign’s protective true essence, causing his clothes to recklessly flutter in the air and his white hair to blow backwards.

At this moment, something appeared and began to emit a dim blue light in front of the old God Sovereign.

This blue light was soft and inconspicuous. In the wild energy storm it was nearly undetectable. However, the moment that this faint blue light reflected in Empyrean Primordius’ brutal eyes, his body suddenly shook and he instantly calmed down.

This blue light was misty, as if it were the only one of its kind in the world. It slowly floated out from the old God Sovereign’s chest, drifting towards Empyrean Primordius.

As Lin Ming and the old God Sovereign saw this they were both left bewildered. This blue light was the Chain of Calamity!

The Chain of Calamity was a True Divinity spirit treasure used in opening the Asura forbidden land. The body of it had once been worn by Heavenly Empress Xuanxing, and after she died, the Chain of Calamity was entombed with her. When Lin Ming stumbled his way into her tomb, that was when he had taken it.

Could it be…

Lin Ming held his breath. He looked helplessly on as more and more blue light appeared around the Chain of Calamity. This misty blue light eventually faintly gathered into the phantom of a woman.

This woman’s phantom became more and more clear, nearly seeming as if it would manifest into physical reality. Her appearance was as beautiful as the bright moon and her black hair hung down her back like a waterfall of ink.

Her feet were bare. Her skin was glittering and crystalline, as if she were formed from the essence of the stars and moon. Her eyebrows were like a painting and her eyes were as bright as the morning skies. She was a goddess from the highest heavens who had been exiled to the mortal world.

Heavenly Empress Xuanqing!

Lin Ming was panic-stricken. Apparently just before Heavenly Empress Xuanqing had died, she had sealed away a wisp of her soul in the True Divinity spirit treasure that she shared origins with, and had deeply slumbered within it ever since.

In truth, let alone a martial artist that was powerful in the aspect of the soul, even for a mortal, after they died, their personal effects might develop a sense of spirituality. At certain times these items might manifest the appearance of their master from before their death.

And Heavenly Empress Xuanqing was originally at an extremely high boundary. In addition to this True Divinity spirit treasure that surpassed the level of an Empyrean, no one realized that a fraction of her soul was sleeping within the Chain of Calamity.

It was not until a moment ago when Lin Ming attempted to awaken Empyrean Primordius’ consciousness that the aura released by Empyrean Primordius finally rekindled Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s soul.

She already didn’t have much life left. To awaken also meant her near demise…

Beside Lin Ming, the old God Sovereign trembled. From his wizened and disbelieving eyes, tears began to fall.

As for Empyrean Primordius, as he saw Heavenly Empress Xuanqing, his body violently shook. Within his eyes, confusion and madness struggled against each other. It was as if he were experiencing an enormous pain, one that was unbearable.

Roar –

Empyrean Primordius cried out in pain. An energy storm viciously lashed out like a hail of blades. Lin Ming and the old God Sovereign paled. This sort of energy storm could instantly kill a Holy Lord. As for the wisp of Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s soul, she would absolutely not be able to withstand it!

However, just as they were about to move, they discovered that the entire storm had completely avoided Heavenly Empress Xuanxing with nothing striking near her.

“Primordius…”

Heavenly Empress Xuanqing’s eyes revealed a deep sorrow. Her voice was dim, as if her words were an illusion…

Gently, she flew toward Empyrean Primordius’ side. She slowly reached out a hand and lightly caressed his chest…

She was only a soul form and couldn’t physically touch anything. But, Empyrean Primordius immediately calmed down even more.

Within his soul, even if two different consciousnesses were attacking each other as before, causing endless pain to surge within him, Empyrean Primordius still suppressed all of this. His body didn’t move even a single inch as he allowed Heavenly Empress Xuanqing to lightly touch him.

This was because…

No matter what he had experienced, no matter what he had become, whether it was in the past or in the future, he could never harm this woman…

“If you can’t remember, then don’t think about it…”

Heavenly Empress Xuanqing whispered, unable to bear the sight before her. To part for 100,000 years and meet once again, things had actually ended up like this.

He had turned into a demon, losing his sanity. She had died somewhere else, leaving behind only a wisp of her soul. Even though her pain had reached the pinnacle, she was unable to cry…

A soul would not shed tears, but they would feel the limits of pain.

They gently supported each other. Even though there was no real physical touch, in this moment their hearts were still connected. This was because… within each other’s hearts and minds they had forever marked each other, a brand that would never be forgotten.

Empyrean Primordius had already completely settled down. The two different personalities within him were no longer in conflict.

Within his eyes, pure brightness showed.

He looked at Heavenly Empress Xuanxing, seeming to remember everything.

He didn’t speak, because after fully becoming an abyssal, it seemed he was unable to say words…

Then, he looked at the old God Sovereign.

The old God Sovereign had rivers of tears falling down his face and his lips were quivering.

Although Primordius didn’t receive an explanation, it was like he already understood everything that had occurred.

It had arrived at last – the final moment.

The obsessions of his heart would soon be resolved. And, he also saw his most beloved once more.

A short happiness. The final brilliance of life. Everything would burn like a meteor through the skies, becoming an instant of magnificent glory.

“Father…”

Heavenly Empress Xuanqing turned towards the old God Sovereign whose back was hunched over with age. She wanted to cry, but no tears flowed out.

The old God Sovereign’s lips shivered. He wanted to reach out his hand to stroke his daughter’s cheek, but he couldn’t feel her at all.

The old God Sovereign deeply sighed. The one in front of him was his daughter that had died 100,000 years ago, as well as his only direct descendant.

To the primal god race who rarely had offspring, their children were their everything.

His daughter was proud and arrogant and beautiful, and had the life of someone who would step into divinity. But in his old age when his time was coming to an end, she had already taken a step ahead and silently left him. To the old God Sovereign, the magnitude of this attack on his heart could be imagined.

“There is no time…”

Heavenly Empress Xuanqing shook her head. She seemed to understand just what was happening.

She flew away from before the old God Sovereign and landed on Empyrean Primordius’ solid shoulder.

The towering Empyrean Primordius was like a tower of iron, the incarnation of a demon. And above this demon’s shoulder was the perfectly beautiful and elegant Heavenly Empress Xuanqing. Her grace and presence was like that of an ephemeral fairy.

As this image fell into Lin Ming’s eyes, it became eternal…

The old God Sovereign silently took out a god decree. At this time, this black god decree seemed cold and merciless.

The old God Sovereign’s heart bled.

If Empyrean Primordius and Heavenly Empress Xuanqing had to burn away their lives in battle, then let it be him who personally lit the flame…

Facing the old God Sovereign, Empyrean Primordius had already composed himself and was calmly waiting for this final battle. At this time, there was a sense of satisfaction in his eyes.

In the final moment he was able to reunite with his love. His life would be able to brilliantly burn in the dark before fading. With this, the obsessions and unwillingness he had held onto for 100,000 years had already faded a great deal.

Then, he looked at Lin Ming. Empyrean Primordius didn’t know just who Lin Ming was, but he could feel his own aura on Lin Ming’s body.

Without a doubt, Lin Ming was his descendant.

He could feel Lin Ming’s great strength. Within the body of this youth there seemed to be a True Dragon deeply slumbering! This youth’s potential was inexhaustible!

With such an outstanding person inheriting his final wishes and legacy, even if he were to die in battle he would have no regrets…

Empyrean Primordius didn’t say anything, but the old God Sovereign seemed to understand his thoughts.

The old God Sovereign began to quietly chant. The Asura Heavenly Dao Laws started to gather. Beams of divine light shined from the old God Sovereign’s body. Drops of blood essence seeped out from between the old God Sovereign’s eyebrows and continuously sank into the god decree.

The old God Sovereign was burning his own life.

The word of Faith. He had to pour his life into it to ignite it, and only he was most suited to do so!

From his withered body, an incomparable and potent life force began to rise. Vast waves of energy rushed out like a raging river, merging into the god decree.

The god decree became increasingly bright until it completely burned away, transforming into countless runes that converged into Empyrean Primordius’ body.

In this moment, Empyrean Primordius felt an infinite strength stir in his body. His massive mortal body grew once more. A terrifying strength percolated within him like a volcano that would erupt at any moment, a strength that could not be suppressed, only released!

His eyes blazed with fighting spirit. His senses were as sharp as a savage beast as he rushed out of the spirit ship and locked onto Famine and the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!

Empyrean Primordius had never come into contact with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign before. But at this time, Empyrean Primordius knew that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was his life’s greatest enemy.

Only one of them could live beneath the heavens!

Chapter 1909 – Severing the Dragon

The Asura Decree erupted with black flames that burnt through the underground chamber. This underground chamber of the god race could originally be considered an Empyrean spirit treasure, but even it began to melt away beneath these heated flames!

Empyrean Primordius’ body was soaked in these flames. His aura began to rapidly climb, soon surpassing the boundaries of an Empyrean!

The Asura Decree was a Beyond Divinity level treasure. Using it as a support, a peak Empyrean could easily rise to the level of a True Divinity!

However, what was difficult was that even a peak Empyrean would find it hard to withstand the strength contained within the word of Faith. It was even possible that their body might collapse and explode from the energy, immediately killing them.

But Empyrean Primordius was different. The intensity of his mortal body had already far surpassed that of most True Divinities.

In particular, the raging anger within his heart pushed him to the limits, allowing his strength to reach an inconceivable degree for a short period of time. All of his life potential was erupting!

On Empyrean Primordius’ shoulder, Heavenly Empress Xuanqing turned into a wisp of blue light that sank into his body.

In the final moments of their lives they would be together and die together, never to separate again.

An exit tunnel opened up within the spirit ship. Without turning, Empyrean Primordius flew out. From this point on, he was a demon bent on revenge!

……

Bang!!

Terrifying explosions rocked the vast space. The Ark of Hope was like a little toy that was sent tumbling around. Its protective shield rippled and surged, energy sparks flying.

Beneath the continued onslaught of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, the Ark of Hope’s energy reserves began to rapidly decline.

“Lord Patriarch, we only have 50% energy remaining!”

An Empyrean reported to the celestial Patriarch. After the old God Sovereign left, the only one who could manage the chaotic situation was the celestial Patriarch.

The celestial Patriarch’s palm was drenched in a cold sweat but he still calmly directed the room. He could not be flustered. Even if his heart was lost and he was panicking within, on the surface he could not show any hysteria.

He didn’t know where the old God Sovereign and Lin Ming had gone, nor did he know where they were going. They had already disappeared for a quarter hour; the spirit ship wouldn’t be able to last much longer!

But at this time, the celestial Patriarch froze. He looked outside the porthole with utter shock as he watched a towering demon hurtle out from the spirit ship and rush towards the saints.

This demon’s goal was Famine!

Although this black demon was massive, compared to the planet-sized Famine, it was far too tiny.

“That is… what is that?”

This demon was far too fast; many people found it hard to see its appearance.

Was this the old God Sovereign’s final trump card?

This thought immediately cut through the celestial Patriarch’s mind. But as soon as he thought this, he discovered that the black demon didn’t rush towards the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign but instead impacted towards… the saint race’s peak Empyreans!

“Mm? That is…”

On the side of the saints, the fused being of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and Famine was stunned. From this black demon, he could feel the aura of an abyssal!

“How is this possible…?”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign could hardly believe his own eyes. There had been an abyssal hiding within the god race all this time?

Within the 33 Heavens, the abyssal demons were a taboo existence. God Beasts could be tamed and forced into becoming a peak Empyrean’s contract beast, but an abyssal could never be brought to heel. Abyssals were incomparably evil beings. Their wisdom was relatively low and they often relied on their instincts to manage affairs. They were the mortal enemies of all intelligent life forms!

Of course, there was always the possibility of something like ‘Famine’ occurring. An abyssal with a high degree of wisdom could establish an equal contract with an intelligent race in order to mutually benefit each other. But, these intelligent abyssals were often peak True Divinity level existences. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign didn’t believe that such a powerful abyssal would ally with a declining race like the primal god race.

“Just what is going on…”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign hesitated. But at this time, Empyrean Primordius had already rushed towards him with unbelievable speed!

“You are seeking death! Since this is the case, I will devour you!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign coldly sneered. With a thought, a thick dragon tentacle lashed out from the giant body of Famine. This dragon whip instantly passed through ten thousand miles of space, striking towards the black demon!

The power behind this strike already surpassed the level of an Empyrean. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign wanted to cut down this unknown black demon and have it become a part of Famine’s flesh and blood.

Rah - !

The blood dragon opened its jaws, biting down on Empyrean Primordius!

In that instant, Empyrean Primordius’ eyes burst out with freezing killing intent! Although his mind was still clear and bright, his eyes had turned blood red!

Roar!

Empyrean Primordius roared. Without changing direction, he shot towards the maw of that giant blood dragon!

Like this, that massive maw would thoroughly swallow Empyrean Primordius!

For a time, all of the ancient race martial artists felt their hearts tighten. They didn’t know how strong Empyrean Primordius was.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign diabolically grinned. But at this time, Empyrean Primordius appeared cold and merciless to the extreme.

Ka ka ka!

With two cracking sounds, two long bone knives shot out from Empyrean Primordius’ elbows, stretching out until they became massive crescent moon blades. These blades were a thousand feet long and glowed with a black divine light. With an unparalleled momentum, he slashed out!

Shua!

The void shattered. Empyrean Primordius broke into the blood dragon’s jaw, his entire body vanishing!

However, the moment that the blood dragon closed its jaws, two fierce half-moon bone blades slashed out from the blood dragon’s cheeks. Blood sprinkled down as the blades continued downwards, unstoppable!

Blood gushed out, dying the void red. The red dragon tentacle futilely struggled wildly, but in front of Empyrean Primordius its flesh and blood was no different from tofu. It had no ability to resist Empyrean Primordius’ bone blades!

Like this, from beginning to end, the thousands of miles long red dragon was sliced open!

“What!?”

In that instant, whether it was martial artists from the saints or ancient races, they were all panic-stricken. This demon that had appeared from nowhere had severed one of Famine’s tentacles!

Before then, only the god decree left behind by the Asura Road Master had been able to injure Famine!

“Just what are you!?”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s pupils shrank. He could feel a dreadful killing intent from this black demon’s eyes, as if they shared some deep and unforgivable grudge.

When did he become enemies with an abyssal?

Empyrean Primordius didn’t speak. On his elbows, those crescent moon blades swung out, causing blood to fly. The entire red dragon tentacle was severed in half by Empyrean Primordius!

After being cut from its mother-body, the tentacle instantly turned into bloody water in the skies. Then, something shocking occurred. Empyrean Primordius opened his mouth and a terrifying traction vortex appeared, swallowing in all of that blood water!

Empyrean Primordius had swallowed Famine’s tentacle.

Famine was known as the existence that could swallow all, but now its own flesh and blood had been swallowed by Empyrean Primordius!

Chapter 1910 – Invincible

Crack crack ka!

Empyrean Primordius’ flesh and blood and meridians began to emit a thunderous clapping sound. After swallowing Famine’s flesh and blood, a greater strength was absorbed into his body. Within him, it was like a swelling volcano was rising, about to erupt at any moment.

“What is that demon? It can even swallow Famine’s flesh and blood?”

Within the Ark of Hope, as the ancient race Empyreans saw the black demon they were all confused; they didn’t know just what plans to make.

“This black demon has reached the True Divinity boundary and can even absorb Famine’s flesh and blood to eat as its own energy. This is terrifying, but… it is not Famine’s match.”

The celestial Patriarch shook his head. After the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign fused together with Famine, they became a nearly invincible existence. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign represented the highest Laws and the greatest strength, whereas Famine represented an incomprehensible life force and defensive capability.

With the two of them fused together, they had almost no weaknesses!

In this situation, the celestial Patriarch didn’t believe there was an existence capable of killing the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. This was what it meant to have an absolute disparity of strength!

“Hahahaha!”

In the void, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign howled with laughter, his cackles resounding through the endless space. “I never thought that there would be a monster like you in the primal god race! However… you seem to be relying on some outside power in order to forcefully raise your strength to the level of a True Divinity? How can someone like you possibly be my match? In the end, you will become nothing but feed for Famine.”

As the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign spoke, red dragon heads burst out from his body. These dragon heads wriggled in space, slowly twisting around. On the surface of these red dragons thick layers of bone armor appeared.

The dragons that were made of flesh and blood had now turned into bone dragons.

“This time, do you think your bone blades will still be useful?”

A contemptuous smile appeared on the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s face. With rolling dragon roars, the hundred plus bone dragons rushed towards Empyrean Primordius.

Compared to Empyrean Primordius, Famine’s body was far too large. Those terrifying bone dragon tentacles could easily pierce through a planet.

Bang!

Empyrean Primordius suddenly ignited with energy. He turned into a black beam of light that hurtled towards those bone dragons. The bone blades on his elbows slashed out, forming an arc of light that spread for hundreds of thousands of miles!

Blood sprayed out and a bone dragon’s armor shattered. But in the next moment, two bone dragons took its place, each one rushing towards Empyrean Primordius in a pincer attack.

Peng!

The void was smashed apart. Empyrean Primordius was sent flying backwards like a meteor, tumbling away for a thousand miles.

However, his mortal body was incredibly solid. Even after being struck backwards he instantly rose up in space and shot forwards once more!

Seeing this, the many ancient race Empyreans on the Ark of Hope felt their hearts skip a beat. At this time, the doors to the main control room opened up and an ashen man with a hunched back walked in, supported by Lin Ming.

This old man’s face was as wrinkled as a walnut and the sockets of his eyes were pulled in deep. His hair was sparse and his eyes were filthy. His entire body emitted a faint death energy.

This old man was the old God Sovereign, but currently, his fires of life were waning like a candle in a storm, ready to fade at any moment.

“Your Majesty!”

“Master!”

Diwuhen and the many god race martial artists were shocked and saddened as they saw the appearance of their old God Sovereign. Before this, when they saw the demon rush out, they had already guessed that it was related to the old God Sovereign. But now it seemed that the old God Sovereign really had paid a deep price in order to do this. His life was rapidly reaching its end!

“There is no need to panic, I’m not dead yet…”

The old God Sovereign calmly said, as if this was a simple and irrelevant matter. When the old God Sovereign burned the god decree he had preserved a tiny bit of his fires of life because he wasn’t able to die just yet. He still needed to guide the ancient remnant races to the Divine Realm.

“Honorable Master…”

Diwuhen fell to his knees. He felt as if a knife was stabbed into his heart and was being twisted around. As Lin Ming stood behind the old God Sovereign, he looked at Diwuhen who was crying tears and deeply empathized with his pain. This was because he understood what Diwuhen was feeling.

Hate. Hate towards himself. Hate towards his own weakness.

 “That black demon is…” An Empyrean couldn’t help but ask.

“He was once a proud son of heaven who belonged to the human race. He has already become an abyssal. 100,000 years ago, his name was… Empyrean Primordius.” The old God Sovereign slowly spoke, his voice aged and gravelly.

“Empyrean Primordius?”

Hearing this name, many ancient race martial artists were bewildered. They understood this part of history. Empyrean Primordius was a true elite, but what a pity, history never gave him the time to grow. Otherwise, perhaps he might have been the turn this great calamity needed. Of course, that was only a possibility; the fused Good Fortune Saint Son and Famine was simply far too powerful. Even if humanity and the god race possessed one or two True Divinities, it would still be impossible for them to contend with the saints.

“We cannot stay… Primordius is not a match for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign…”

The old God Sovereign’s voice was gloomy. Everyone was silent. They knew that Empyrean Primordius was sacrificing his life to buy time for them and they couldn’t allow him to die in vain.

“Open the energy matrix and pour all of your energy into it. Prepare to break through!”

The old God Sovereign ordered. The Empyreans present were solemn. They were well aware that even with Empyrean Primordius, wanting to break out of this encirclement would be filled with difficulties. This was destined to be a bitter struggle.

Ca!

A bone dragon tentacle was split in half. Empyrean Primordius was bathed in blood, looking like an ascendant demon!

He swallowed Famine’s flesh and drank Famine’s blood in order to restore his own energy. But compared to Famine with his vast, ocean-like life force, Empyrean Primordius’ combat strength was simply too low. Up until now, Famine hadn’t weakened at all.

As the celestial Patriarch had said, Famine was a nearly invincible opponent!

“So… you are not an abyssal, but that body is one that you’ve seized.”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign coldly sneered. From Empyrean Primordius’ spiritual sea, he could feel an aura different from that of a true abyssal. This was no abyssal, but someone from one of the intelligent races.

“To seize the body of an abyssal, you’ve actually caused me to recall someone… 100,000 years ago, there was a human who tried to bite off more than he could chew and attempted to imitate the Asura Road Master by establishing his own Samsara Heavenly Dao. In the end, his plans were toppled by me, and his Grandmist Spirit Bead was taken by me. He fell into the Dark Abyss, unable to escape. And if I remember correctly, at the time there had been a woman by his side, one that came from the primal god race…”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign slowly spoke, a taunting smile on his face. His words were like a knife that cut into Empyrean Primordius’ heart.

Empyrean Primordius’ blood red eyes burst out with a thick killing intent. However, he didn’t lose his reasoning. He hurtled through the starry sky battlefield, dodging the attacks of the red bone dragons. He could already feel that his attacks weren’t enough to threaten Famine. Thus, he needed to attack the core of Famine – the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. However… when comparing his strength against the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s, even if he reached him, how could he possibly defeat him?

“You’re done for!”

Standing atop Famine’s bloody red body, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign stretched out his hands. From between his hands, a black vortex appeared. A black sphere slowly manifested in it. This sphere was covered with ancient lines, shining blood red as if they had drunk their fill of blood.

Grandmist Spirit Bead!

On the Ark of Hope, Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. The item within the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was the Grandmist Spirit Bead. As a True Divinity who specialized in body transformation, if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign emitted an attack with the Grandmist Spirit Bead, its might would be unimaginable!

“Primordius, be careful!”

The old God Sovereign’s heart tightened. Originally, it was already difficult to deal with the fused Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and Famine, but now there was also the Grandmist Spirit Bead. Empyrean Primordius had suddenly fallen into a life or death predicament!

“Activate the Ark of Hope’s array formation with everything you have! We are breaking out of here!”

The old God Sovereign commanded. And at this time, black flames lit up all over Empyrean Primordius. In his blood red eyes, the shadow of the Grandmist Spirit Bead reflected in his pupils.

After 100,000 years, Empyrean Primordius once again saw this divine tool which had brought him to unimaginable heights but had also sent him crashing down. His heart wildly fluctuated!

“Primordius? I remember this was your name… 100,000 years ago, I wrested the Grandmist Spirit Bead from your hands. Now, I shall use the Grandmist Spirit Bead to kill you and bring our story to its end. You once used the Grandmist Spirit Bead to absorb flesh and blood essence to cultivate your martial artists, so now I shall use the Grandmist Spirit Bead to absorb your flesh and blood essence. I suppose you can consider this a kind of retributive karma, right? Hahaha! Mm… you want to run away? To think you can play tricks on me, you still aren’t good enough!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s complexion became cold and deadly, murderous intent bursting from his eyes! He discovered that the Ark of Hope was revolving energy within its array formation and was attempting to escape.

The truth was that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had already guessed Empyrean Primordius’ goal was to delay for time so that the ancient remnant races could flee.

How could he allow such a thing to happen? In particular, atop the Ark of Hope there was still Lin Ming, someone he had to kill above all!

“How naïve. My sense has been locked onto you all for this entire time. How could you possibly escape? You will all remain here and the ancient races will forever disappear into history!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s thoughts moved and dozens of transformed bone dragons rushed outwards!

These bone dragons roared, their bodies like beams of light as they instantly passed through tens of thousands of miles, smashing and grabbing towards the Ark of Hope!

Bang!

The Ark of Hope violently shook. The hull that was thousands of miles long was tangled by dozens of bone dragons!

And at this time, an enchantment appeared from millions of miles away, sealing Famine, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, and the Ark of Hope within!

This enchantment exuded a grand and violent aura; it was the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s good fortune force field. With the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign blocking out the surrounding space with his own force field and using dozens of bone dragon tentacles to tie down the Ark of Hope, the Ark of Hope was now like a bug caught in a spider web, unable to move.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign ruthlessly grinned. “Although you are only ants, I will not allow you the slightest chance to escape! I will give everything to strangle you all to death and bring this all to an end!”

Chapter 1911 – The Final Counterattack

“Damn it!”

On the Ark of Hope, the ancient race Empyreans felt their hearts surge with despair. The bone dragon tentacles shooting out from Famine were extremely powerful. Just a single bone dragon couldn’t be severed even with the all-out attack of a peak Empyrean. Not just that, but there were dozens of bone dragons tying down the Ark of Hope. It would be impossible to break free!

“What do we do?” The ancient race martial artists were worried. Many people looked towards the old God Sovereign. In this critical moment, this old man that was on the verge of death was still the spiritual leader of everyone present.

“Don’t panic!” The old God Sovereign took a deep breath. At the crux of life and death, the old God Sovereign’s voice seemed to possess a strange and mesmerizing charm that calmed everyone down. “We still have a chance, and it is also our final chance…”

The old God Sovereign took out the final Asura Decree – the word of Sealing!

Of the three Asura Decrees there was – the offensive ‘Word of Striking’, the supportive ‘Word of Faith’, and the final sealing ‘Word of Sealing’.

But sealing…

In the minds of those present, the word of Sealing was the weakest of the three Asura Decrees, because it had a weak striking power that could only be used to imprison.

By relying on the word of Sealing, could they reverse the course of fate?

At this time in the void, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had begun his final attack!

The Grandmist Spirit Bead was like a black hole. It floated above the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s head, seething with power!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign spread his arms, allowing energy to recklessly bathe his body. His long hair flew upwards!

On the surface of his body strange curse seals appeared, each curse seal matching those on the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

“Primordius, ancient remnant races, allow me to use this Grandmist Spirit Bead to deliver you all onto the road to hell!”

The Grandmist Spirit Bead emitted a misty red light. The void twisted apart as a horrifying suction force gushed outwards!

Empyrean Primordius howled. On the precipice of life and death, he began to recklessly burn his blood essence. As an abyssal demon and an Empyrean who had opened the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, he possessed an incredibly powerful mortal body. Now that he burnt all his blood essence, the strength that erupted from him could be imagined!

Bang!

Grandmist energy and the power of an abyssal erupted together. But, in the face of the terrifying aura released by the Grandmist Spirit Bead, the strength released by Empyrean Primordius was like a firefly to the bright night moon, simply insignificant.

In the void, the vortex of the Grandmist Spirit Bead became increasingly strong. All of the nearby martial artists in space felt this dreadful swallowing force that seemed to pull at their blood essence, wanting to pull out all the blood from their bodies!

The Grandmist Spirit Bead was the divine tool that represented ‘essence’. It could swallow flesh and blood, but it wasn’t limited to that alone.

This was because within the universe, essence, energy, and divine separately represented matter, energy, and the Heavenly Dao.

As for ‘essence’, that corresponded to all matter and physical things in the universe.

Now, with the Grandmist Spirit Bead being used by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, it could swallow all matter of creation!

Any strength, any light could not escape this swallowing force. It was like a limitless black hole, possessing a terrifying mystic strength.

Paka! Paka!

The surrounding space shattered in massive tracts. The greatest strength released by Empyrean Primordius was only able to faintly slow the Grandmist Spirit Bead for a moment before no longer having any effect.

“We must evacuate!”

The saint Empyreans that helped seal off the Ark of Hope were frightened upon seeing the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign use the power of the Grandmist Spirit Bead. They were scared they would be drawn into that black hole and perish without a trace!

……

“It’s time. This is our final chance…”

On the Ark of Hope, the old God Sovereign took out the word of Sealing god decree.

“I will join you…”

The old celestial Patriarch stood up. He could already see that the old God Sovereign planned to sacrifice himself and combust this god decree.

But the old God Sovereign himself was insufficient.

“It’s been almost 100 million years. I will accompany you… on this final journey!”

The celestial Patriarch smiled as he slowly walked up to the old God Sovereign’s side.

Seeing this, the ancient race powerhouses all looked dispirited.

Diwuhen and To Bagui shivered. Tears streamed down Smokeless’ face. Lin Ming closed his eyes. They all wanted to say something, but in the end they remained quiet.

Because at this time, there was no more meaning in saying anything at all.

The word of Sealing Asura Decree slowly flew up between the old God Sovereign and the celestial Patriarch.

The two old men flew up into the void.

The celestial Patriarch looked at the old God Sovereign and said, “When we were young we explored the Primeval Realm Ruins together. In our lives, I can’t remember the number of times we’ve battled side by side. Even when we had to fight each other, it was for our own people. However… I’ve always been slightly worse than you…”

The old God Sovereign shook his head. “It’s in the past. Today we shall fight together once more, and it will also be our last time…”

Speaking here, the two old men smiled, their smiles bright and confident. The god decree glowed brighter and brighter. The old God Sovereign closed his eyes, saying, “I’ll have to rely on you. I don’t have much strength left.”

“I know.”

After speaking these words, the two old men that stood at the pinnacle of the ancient races began to combust like two blazing suns. Their life’s essence energy continuously streamed out from every pore of their body, merging into the black Asura Decree.

With every wisp of life essence, the god decree lit up more and more. Slowly, it became blinding. But as for the bodies of the two leaders, they began to stiffen like stone and slowly disintegrate.

The black god decree began to expand at an incredible rate. Ancient and plain runes appeared, each one containing a vast and boundless power. A will from a far off time burst out from the rays of black light.

These rays of light brought with them the infinite aura of an Asura war god, possessing the power of a bottomless prison.

Hum –

Space shivered. As the black light spread out, even space seemed to be forcefully sealed away. Light, dust, all matter and energy and even the most root source Laws began to freeze solid, becoming like pitch black ice. This sight left the heart racing.

With a rustling sound, the bodies of the two old men collapsed and disintegrated into the air. The last wisps of their boundless life force and essence energy merged into the dazzling god decree.

Bang!

The god decree vanished from sight. Instead, what was left behind was a profound darkness, filled with black tentacles as dark as the void that roiled about, innumerable.

These tentacles had trillions of runes shining upon them. They pierced through the void, surging forwards…

All of the ancient remnant race martial artists felt their hearts weighed down by sorrow. This was a strike traded for with the lives of the leaders from two different races.

The two old leaders no longer needed to command this battle because their mission had been completed. If they could not win this battle then there was no meaning to exist. And if they could win, then the ancient remnant races would be able to escape even without their guidance, fleeing to open skies.

…….

“Just die!” A cold and cruel smile appeared on the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s lips. He pressed his hands forwards, pouring all of his strength into the Grandmist Spirit Bead.

Bang!

The power of the Grandmist Spirit Bead rose once more, completely crushing the defensive barriers that Primordius tried to put up. The black vortex grew larger and larger, eventually turning into a massive thousand miles black sphere that could consume all of creation!

Energy shock waves spread outwards like tens of thousands of stars exploding together. Like a boiling tide, all nearby planets started to blow apart one at a time. Even many nearby spirit ships began to flee, lest they be sucked into the vortex.

The black hole formed by the Grandmist Spirit Bead would expand without end until it swallowed all.

Even the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had to consume a tremendous amount of energy in order to use this power that could reverse the heavens and earth. He had to overdraw his strength and even then he found it difficult to control.

But just as Empyrean Primordius was covered by this black hole, a strange and formidable dark strength hurtled out from the Ark of Hope!

This dark strength blotted out the heavens, overwhelming the world. It was like a black sun with countless black tentacles spreading out from it.

As it appeared, vast tracts of surrounding space were instantly imprisoned. Even pure energy shock waves were frozen solid. Even Famine, even the Grandmist Spirit Bead, everything was tightly wrapped up in this sheer pitch black darkness.

“Mm? This is…!!” The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign detected that something was wrong. He discovered that this strange pitch black strength contained an inexplicable divine sealing ability. It was somewhat similar to the Grandmist Spirit Bead in that it shared characteristics with a black hole, but it was actually different from a black hole!

The Grandmist Spirit Bead was a swallowing power, but this dark strength was a seal!

It sealed everything away into a black space, and this space also began to rapidly shrink!

“Asura Decree!?!?”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s heart shook. Such a terrifying strength could only be achieved by an Asura Decree!

Although the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign knew that the primal god race had few god decrees personally drawn up by the Asura Road Master, he actually wasn’t sure what effects they had or what they were used for.

But now, it seemed that the function of this god decree was to create a divine natural space that surpassed the Laws of the 33 Heavens and sealed away all enemies within.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had already been imprisoned and was unable to dodge at all. And worst of all, even the completely berserk Grandmist Spirit Bead black hole would be sealed away with him!

“Damn it all!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign finally understood the plan of the ancient remnant races. He was so angry he wanted to smash his feet against a boulder!

“Break for me!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was incensed. He no longer cared for Empyrean Primordius but instead stimulated the Grandmist Spirit Bead black hole to its limits in order to break free from this divine natural space!

Ka ka ka!

The black hole and spatial barriers collided together. A terrifying and mind-boggling level of energy erupted. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign wanted to forcefully break free from this Asura Decree!

For a time, space seemed to be completely swallowed up.

Then, from the god decree left behind by the Asura Road Master, an unexpected shattering sound rang out, as if it would soon shatter!

After the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign fused together with Famine, and also with using the power of the Grandmist Spirit Bead, he could almost break open an Asura Decree!

“You want to seal me away? Keep on dreaming!”

A cruel and merciless light shined in the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s eyes. But in the next moment, his complexion changed. He watched helplessly on as a towering black demon hurtled towards him at full speed!

Empyrean Primordius was also covered by the word of Sealing. When the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign stimulated the Grandmist Spirit Bead black hole to its limits in order to break free from the imprisonment of the divine natural space, Empyrean Primordius had also been freed from the shackles of the black hole. Now, this was his chance to rush forwards.

Yet this time, his target was no longer Famine, but the main body of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!

Chapter 1912 – Black Hole Disintegration

“You are seeking death!”

Seeing Empyrean Primordius hurtle towards him, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign began to panic.

Even if he was stronger, having to control the incomparably powerful Grandmist Spirit Bead black hole to attack the divine natural sealing space had caused him to exhaust all of his energy.

This was an Asura Decree, a Beyond Divinity level treasure. How could it be easy to break through it?

Yet, in this crucial moment, Empyrean Primordius intended to strike him at his weakest. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign didn’t have any methods to deal with Empyrean Primordius’ attacks!

At this time, a savage killing intent burst out from Empyrean Primordius’ eyes. He brought his arms together, his two bone blades extended outwards. The dark and dense blades shined with a cold divine light, slashing straight towards the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s throat!

And the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign wasn’t able to block this attack!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was enraged to the peak. He was clearly far stronger than Empyrean Primordius, and the ancient remnant races were nothing but bugs he didn’t place in his eyes. And yet this crowd of bug-like existences had forced him to this step.

There was no road to heaven, no gates to the earth!

Die!

Empyrean Primordius had already recklessly burnt his blood essence. With his original mortal bodily strength, after burning the entirety of his blood essence he should have been able to rival a True Divinity, and now he was even supported with the Asura Decree – the word of Faith!

Empyrean Primordius’ body was covered in black flames. Wherever he went, the void was shattered, everything was crushed!

Empyrean Primordius’ strike could not be blocked by an ordinary True Divinity. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was naturally capable of blocking such a strike, but now he didn’t have the strength to do so!

Seeing the bone blade soon about to slice through his throat, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign fiercely grit his teeth and desperately attacked!

Crack! Crack! Crack!

He howled into the heavens. Scales formed all over his body. In this life or death moment, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had activated his body metamorphosis!

The saints were a body transformation focused race that was also divided by the quality of their bloodlines. Amongst the saints, martial artists with formidable bloodlines could metamorphosize their bodies, galvanizing their greatest strength.

The Good Fortune Saint Son and Imperial Prince Naqi were examples.

But the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign could not remember how many years it had been since he had used his bloodline power to activate body metamorphosis. This was because he simply never needed it.

In his ordinary state, he was almost the greatest powerhouse of the 33 Heavens.

After fusing together with Famine, he was nearly invincible!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign never would have dreamed there would be a day when he would be forced to use his body transformation by a bunch of ants!

“Get out of my way!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign exploded into a roar, his fist smashing outwards!

His fist was covered with scales and his muscles bulged out like the claws of a dragon.

This fist broke apart the void, colliding with Empyrean Primordius’ bone blades!

Kacha!

With a loud crack, the bone blades shattered!

Even if this was a hasty blow, the strike of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign possessed unimaginable power!

However, the moment the fractured bone blades shattered, they still tore through the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s protective astral essence and stabbed into his chest.

At the same time, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s fist smashed into Empyrean Primordius’ chest.

Bang!

Empyrean Primordius’ towering figure violently shook. His ribs caved in and he spat out blood as he was sent flying backwards!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s strike had heavily wounded Primordius, but his mortal body had been stabbed by Empyrean Primordius’ bone blade. Moreover, because the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had to stop what he was doing to attack Primordius, the Grandmist Spirit Bead black hole began to spin out of control!

Whorl whorl whorl!

The pitch black surface of the black hole violently clashed with the divine natural sealing space. A horrifying tide of energy burst outward!

Because the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign didn’t want to give Empyrean Primordius or the ancient remnant races any chance to escape, he had poured all his energy into the Grandmist Spirit Bead to send out an attack. This terrifying black hole could ruin a galaxy; its strength was beyond powerful.

The power that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign cast out was absorbed into the black hole, causing it to accumulate more and grow larger. Within, dangerous streams of power grinded against each other, squeezing each other…

Now that he had lost control of the black hole, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s complexion changed. He could feel the strength within the black hole begin to contract inwards, causing massive tracts of space to collapse and implode.

This entire process was like the explosion of a universe, the terrifying contraction that occurred after it had expanded to its limits.

It had to be known that every wisp of power within the black hole was highly tempered and incredibly pure. It was extremely terrifying.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s complexion became increasingly ugly. Once the strength sealed within the black hole was reduced to the peak, it would then explode. The following annihilating strength would create unimaginable destruction.

This was the same as dozens of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s attacks together. It simply could not be withstood.

“Grandmist Spirit Bead – reverse!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s complexion was fierce. He roused the power of the Grandmist Spirit Bead with all of his strength, trying to reverse the energies within and neutralize the black hole.

Excessive consumption of energy caused all of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s blood vessels to bulge upwards and burst open. At this time he was completely overdrawing on his strength!

He forcefully sucked all of this collapsing energy into the Grandmist Spirit Bead.

However, wasn’t wanting to neutralize all of the energy in a black hole on the verge of explosion easier said than done, especially in such a short period of time? The current Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was now a spent force.

Rumble rumble rumble!

After being neutralized by the Grandmist Spirit Bead, the black hole didn’t explode. But, it started to break apart. In this case, waves of energy still shot outwards!

They were like arrows, each wisp capable of crushing celestial bodies!

Woosh!

Black fluctuations of energy crashed into Famine.

The mountainous expanse of flesh and blood seemed to have been cut open by the blade of a divine god. In an instant, dreadful wounds as deep as canyons formed on Famine’s body.

Another energy fluctuation passed over Famine, severing seven or eight of its bone dragon tentacles.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Waves of black hole power slashed through the void. Famine had suffered heavy damage!

“Ahh!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign howled! His hair was disheveled and his body was dyed in blood. He simply couldn’t deal with the stormy power of this black hole.

If this continued, then Famine would suffer inconceivable damages.

This was because the black hole power possessed a swallowing attribute. It would drain a massive amount of Famine’s blood essence!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign bit down on the tip of his tongue and black light rose in his pupils. The pure source power of a True Divinity began to gush out from him.

As this source power appeared, even the universe started to shake. Countless lines of the Great Dao gathered and the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s aura changed. Even his astral essence turned pure gold in color.

In that moment, with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign as the center, a terrifying energy vortex arose within the universe. For billions and trillions of miles around, all of the power of good fortune began gathering towards the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!

This strength was not just heaven and earth origin energy, but all sorts of power from the world.

Heat, light, small ions, interstellar dust, everything began converging on the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!

This was the Good Fortune Divine Art, the technique to seize the power of good fortune! The so-called good fortune was the sum of all matter and life besides intelligent life forms. By drawing out the power of good fortune within the universe for an attack, the power behind this ability could be imagined!

This was an incomparably overbearing and tyrannical cultivation method. The Good Fortune Saint Son had once used it to contend with Lin Ming, but now that it was displayed in the hands of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, the might of the Good Fortune Divine Art was beyond terrifying!

With the support of the Good Fortune Divine Art, beams of golden astral essence gathered around Famine, forming a giant circular golden shield!

Within this shield, small figures floated up and down; these were the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s True Divinity incarnations.

Each small figure represented a wisp of the universe’s source strength, perfect and without flaw.

The moment that the Grandmist Spirit Bead began to veer out of control and the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign wasn’t able to divide his attention too much, he didn’t hesitate to use his source strength with the Good Fortune Divine Art. This round golden shield was a peerless martial skill from the Good Fortune Divine Art – Myriad Spirit Creation Shield.

The Myriad Spirit Creation Shield began to shine. An old and distant radiance emanated outwards as sounds of the Great Dao filled the air.

It was like a most precious treasure had appeared from the birthing of the cosmos, representing eternity and immortality.

Rumble rumble rumble!

The violent black hole strength smashed against the Myriad Spirit Creation Shield, colliding and erasing each other.

Massive amounts of source strength dissipated, however the impact wasn’t able to reach the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

But at this moment, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had also consumed a tremendous amount of his source strength and greatly overdrawn himself. His fused body of Famine was already cut and pitted, with massive and alarming fissures crossing it.

Even so, there were still those bone dragon tentacles that wrapped around the Ark of Hope!

Over half of them had been cut off, but there were still a dozen some of them that tenaciously clung to the spirit ship!

Although the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign could have withdrawn his bone dragon tentacles to help himself defend, he would rather suffer heavier injuries than allow the Ark of Hope to escape.

He didn’t want to let the ancient remnant races flee, especially Lin Ming!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had a dark uneasiness in his heart. He had to kill Lin Ming as soon as possible, but the speed he was growing at was far too fast!

This time, he had suffered a giant loss. Although it seemed that it was because the ancient remnant races had joined together with Empyrean Primordius, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had a strange premonition that in this battle, Lin Ming had played an irreplaceable role.

He needed to kill this human youth. He could not allow him to freely grow. He could not even give him the smallest chance!

“You… die for me!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s face distorted. His mouth was wet with blood!

He reached out his right hand and grasped towards the Ark of Hope!

With explosive cracking sounds, the 20 plus bone dragon tentacles around the Ark of Hope began to wildly contract, constantly crushing down on the Ark of Hope’s protective shield. Even though the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had been heavily wounded, he still had more than enough power to smash the Ark of Hope and the ancient remnant races to pieces!

The Ark of Hope’s energy reserves rapidly fell!

Through the successive attacks and counterattacks, the Ark of Hope had already used up over half its energy. In this situation, the Ark of Hope wasn’t able to last much longer. As for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, although he was exhausted, a starving camel was still larger than a horse. The vitality of Famine was strong to the point of disbelief!

“Die!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign roared out. But at this time, he saw a black shadow fly through a massive wound in his body and… drill into it.

Chapter 1913 – Point

“What?”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s complexion changed. All of his attention just now had been focused on the Ark of Hope. He wanted to obliterate the Ark of Hope’s protective shield and then swallow it, along with the primal god race and Lin Ming.

But during this time period he had suffered a sneak attack.

“It’s you again!!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign fiercely raged, furious. Famine’s body was far too large. After the black hole broke apart, Famine had been forced to withstand over 90% of the black hole’s turbulent energy shockwaves.

And Empyrean Primordius had hidden himself behind Famine. The moment the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign blocked the black hole’s energy shockwaves with the Myriad Spirit Creation Shield, Empyrean Primordius had taken this opportunity to strike!

And what was most ruthless was that Empyrean Primordius didn’t attack the exterior of Famine’s body, but instead chose to rush through the horrifying tearing wounds caused by the black hole energy and break into its body!

Such a sinister method caused the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign to fume with rage!

Puff!

Blood began to gush out of Famine like a river from the wound where Empyrean Primordius had rushed in!

In that moment, Empyrean Primordius had sliced open a giant blood vessel within Famine!

This blood vessel was over a thousand feet thick and it was cut in half by Empyrean Primordius’ bone saber. Underneath a terrifying blood pressure, blood as hot and thick as magma gushed out into space, soaring for thousands of miles!

“Just die!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s eyes gleamed with a vicious light. He changed his plans. He had to kill Empyrean Primordius first, otherwise with Empyrean Primordius freely rampaging through his body, his wounds would only become heavier.

Woosh!

A bone dragon tentacle drilled into Famine’s body like a leech, chasing straight after Empyrean Primordius.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was ruthless. He ignored any collateral damage to Famine’s body and vowed to catch and kill Empyrean Primordius!

As the bone dragon tentacle drilled in, it constantly transformed. It became sharper, more dense, similar to a blood red spear!

And at this time, Empyrean Primordius rushed forwards through the mass of flesh and blood. Before this, Empyrean Primordius’ left bone blade had been shattered by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s punch and his left hand had nearly broken apart at the same time. Now all he had left was the bone blade on his right elbow.

Using this bone blade, Empyrean Primordius hurtled forwards with irresistible momentum. He constantly tore through Famine’s body, drilling into it like a razor sharp cone!

“Since you’ve come, don’t think of leaving!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign surged with energy. Waves of the power of good fortune swelled towards him and Famine’s body violently wriggled. At the same time, the Grandmist Spirit Bead floated above the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s head. A stream of ancient runes rushed out, all of them entering into Famine’s body.

With the support of this powerful energy, Famine’s flesh and blood tightened, becoming more dense even as energy recklessly coursed through it.

These waves of energy smashed onto Empyrean Primordius like an endless tide. The blood became increasingly hot and also started to be filled with a horrifying corrosive power!

This corrosiveness wasn’t from physical poisons but from the Heavenly Dao Laws – in other words, the Poison Laws. Even if a True Divinity spirit treasure were bathed in Famine’s blood it would still slowly lose its spirituality.

Empyrean Primordius fought with everything he had. As he did, he felt the blood splashing on him become as dangerous as acid. As long as it touched him it would emit puffing sounds and vanish in a plume of white smoke.

The pitch black bone armor on his body began to melt away at a speed visible to the eyes. After a while, a plate of bone armor as thick as a large fist fell down.

The bone armor that was originally as smooth as a mirror begun to form holes due to the corrosive blood.

Some of that corrosive blood even splashed onto Primordius’ pupils.

On his deep pupils, runes began to collapse. The sight in front of Empyrean Primordius became hazy and dim, as if he would lose his vision at any moment…

Roar!

Through the layers of hurdles, Empyrean Primordius angrily howled out. A radiant light the color of fresh blood shot out from his pupils, as bright as a sun. The corrosive bodily fluids of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign were burned away by the source essence energy of Empyrean Primordius. A boundless shaking power rushed out, allowing Empyrean Primordius to continue hurtling into the deepest depths of Famine.

…….

“The situation is dire!”

Within the Ark of Hope an ancient race Empyrean felt his mind tighten.

Every single action and move that Empyrean Primordius took affected the hearts of the powerhouses within the Ark of Hope.

They could all feel that at this moment, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s body was surging with a potent power of good fortune. His fused body bloomed with a blinding light. Every pore shone, and the flesh and blood seemed to come to life making the heart race with fear.

That strength was so great that even the void would be swallowed up.

But after Empyrean Primordius had hurtled his way into Famine’s body, his aura became isolated from the outside without any way to sense his movements. Even the tear that Empyrean Primordius used to drill into Famine was slowly being covered over by wriggling flesh.

“Primordius is in danger!”

Diwuhen and To Bagui’s faces were dripping with sweat. Whether it was the celestials or god race, their old leaders had died in battle for their people. Now, the destiny of their races had been left in their hands and they had become the true commanders who had to lead the ancient remnant races to escape and survive.

The pressure on their shoulders could be imagined!

“The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign suffered a backlash from the Grandmist Spirit Bead and has taken heavy damage. He even overdrew his essence energy to activate the Good Fortune Divine Art – just how much strength could he possibly have left?!”

A god race Empyrean spat out with hate thick in his voice.

“Even a centipede that is chopped in half won’t die. Famine’s vital life force is too powerful. Even if it only has a tenth of its strength remaining, it isn’t something we can hope to contend with…”

Diwuhen took a deep breath. At this time, he was nearly out of his wits and out of his mind. Once Empyrean Primordius died, the rest of them would soon follow.

As everyone was anxious and worried, in a corner of the control room, Lin Ming had closed his eyes deep in concentration. Within his spiritual sea the Magic Cube slowly revolved, projecting out a phantom of Famine’s body.

His spiritual sea was nearly isolated from the world. All of his soul force was poured into the Magic Cube as he sensed the universe through it.

He was using the Magic Cube to search for that one ‘point’.

Beside Lin Ming, Smokeless was startled. She could faintly feel that at this moment, there was suddenly a strange change in Lin Ming’s soul force, one that was hard to fathom.

It was like waves of a vast and boundless strength, similar to a spiritual god, began to gush out from Lin Ming’s body, so profound that it caused the heart to race.

Other than Smokeless, many Empyreans also discovered that something unusual was occurring to Lin Ming’s aura. What they didn’t know was that this aura like a spiritual god that made their hearts race didn’t come from Lin Ming, but originated from the Magic Cube.

If there was a powerhouse that had a deep understanding of the Magic Cube, they could rely on this feeling alone to confirm that the Magic Cube was within Lin Ming’s body. This was because the momentum emitting from his body was too grand, too unique.

But now, no one could care to delve into this. Lin Ming had created far too many miracles. If they could feel a divine nature from his body, no one would think it was strange.

“Lin Ming…”

Diwuhen could see that between Lin Ming’s eyebrows, another eye had appeared. This eye shined out with a brilliant divine light, and within his eyes, the phantom of a gray cube seemed to spin around. This cube had mysterious markings that he had never seen before.

As this phantom cube appeared it also instantly hid itself. But as Diwuhen looked into Lin Ming’s eyes he had a feeling as if he were losing himself. This feeling left him stunned. As a peak Empyrean it was naturally impossible for him to be enchanted by the eyes of a peak Holy Lord martial artist.

Was it that phantom cube which had appeared for a brief moment just then?

Diwuhen had no time to think about it. At this time, Lin Ming stood up and asked, “Let me try once.”

“Mm?”

Everyone was shocked. What did Lin Ming want to try? Could it be that he wanted to deal with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign?

That was impossible!

They watched as Lin Ming slowly walked to the side of the Asura Primal God Cannon. Soul force wildly bubbled around his body. Rays of his soul force gathered around him, forming a beam of light in the void, as thick as a baby’s arm. This beam of soul force connected to the Asura Primal God Cannon. Beneath the revitalization of Lin Ming’s soul force, the Asura Primal God Cannon began to emit waves of faint spiritual light.

So he wanted to release the Asura Primal God Cannon once more!

“Lin Ming, you want to use the Asura Primal God Cannon? The Asura Primal God Cannon is strong, but… Famine is just too powerful. It is nearly invincible. Can you use the god cannon to threaten its life?”

The Asura Primal God Cannon was extremely powerful. With a direct strike it could even easily and instantly kill a peak Empyrean.

But to use it to blast Famine, it was actually far too weak!

After all, even in Lin Ming’s hands the Asura Primal God Cannon could only display a limited degree of strength. It was far inferior to an Asura Decree.

Even an Asura Decree could only heavily wound Famine but not kill it.

“Let’s give it a try. This time, my attack method will be different…”

Lin Ming touched the Asura Primal God Cannon. He had no idea just how many rare treasures of the universe were incorporated into this god cannon, just how many materials were needed to forge it. In the ancient era, this god cannon had once followed the Asura Road Master into battle and had obtained many magnificent war exploits.

Chapter 1916 – The Lurking Danger

A True Divinity tracking mark was extremely difficult to erase. At the Fallen God Mountain Range when Lin Ming was grasping the principles atop the shrine platforms there, he had been marked by the Great Brahmic God King. If it weren’t for Sheng Mei arriving right on time then Lin Ming’s situation would have been dire indeed.

The saint race Empyreans took these crimson jade slips and probed them with their divine sense. They could faintly feel the direction of the Ark of Hope in their minds. It was a small yet brilliant mote of light that was speeding away at an unbelievable speed, rapidly increasing the distance from them.

“There it is!”

The saint race Empyreans’ eyes lit up. From just this alone, they dreaded the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. When the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was severely wounded and his spirit mark was being attacked by the Asura Primal God Cannon and was nearly erased, he had still managed to return a strike and leave a tracking mark on the Ark of Hope. This level of ability was extraordinary.

90% of the Empyreans rushed away, chasing after the Ark of Hope!

As for the remaining saint race powerhouses that were dispersed all over, they completely sealed away this part of the universe.

Soon, in that battlefield that had been filled with intense and brutal fighting, there was only the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign left behind with the wounded body of Famine.

In the dark starry space, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s complexion was dim; no one could know what he was thinking.

He remained silent for a long time, quietly assessing all the wounded areas within Famine’s body. He frowned.

He had been injured far too heavily. He would need to return to recover from this and the healing period would be extremely long.

Slowly, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign stretched out his right hand. In his palm a black bead slowly revolved. Numerous mystical patterns ran across the surface of this bead, beating like blood vessels.

This was the Grandmist Spirit Bead. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign sucked in a deep breath of air. A thick smell of blood dissipated from the Grandmist Spirit Bead, entering the Saint Sovereign and Famine’s body slowly.

He was healing his wounds with the Grandmist Spirit Bead.

The Grandmist Spirit Bead was able to absorb blood vitality and essence. After the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign obtained the Grandmist Spirit Bead he had spent a long period of time venturing all over to find flesh and blood essence to nourish the Grandmist Spirit Bead. Now, he released part of this flesh and blood essence in order to enhance the recovery speed of himself and Famine.

Famine itself already possessed an incredible life force and a mind-boggling defensive power. Even though it had suffered strike after devastating strike, it was only injured, not yet dead.

But correspondingly, once Famine was wounded, recovering from these wounds was difficult. The loss in life force was far too great. No matter what sort of heavenly materials were tossed into Famine, it was like throwing a grain of rice into a field; there just wasn’t any noticeable effect.

So even with the Grandmist Spirit Bead it would be a monumental task for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign to completely restore Famine.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign constantly absorbed flesh and blood essence from the Grandmist Spirit Bead. This process continued for two hours.

After that, the light from the Grandmist Spirit Bead became increasingly dense and bright as it surrounded the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s main body. Then, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign separated himself from Famine and flew into the Grandmist Spirit Bead.

After that, the bead slowly sank into Famine’s body, burying itself deep within the monster’s flesh.

The Grandmist Spirit Bead sank deeper and deeper, falling inwards for over a thousand miles until it reached the center of Famine’s body where it soaked itself in a massive pond of blood.

This was the center of Famine. It was an area similar to a giant heart. Every time it beat, the sound was like colliding planets, bass enough to cause space to shake.

The Grandmist Spirit Bead was the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s secret escape route. Although he seemed like an unparalleled existence in the world, undefeatable by anyone, the truth was that there were existences within the 33 Heavens that could threaten his life.

For instance… the Soul Emperor!

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and the Soul Emperor had formed a devil’s contract with each other. For a long period of time, neither party would aggress against the other.

But the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would never believe any contract. He hid himself in the Grandmist Spirit Bead and used it to protect himself, only exposing Famine’s body on the outside.

During the healing period he would be extremely frail and weak. If a peak powerhouse of the 33 Heavens wanted to take this chance to strike out against him they would first need to break open Famine’s body and obtain the Grandmist Spirit Bead in order to find the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s true body.

If this were to occur then the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign could detonate all the life force energy within Famine’s body. The might from such an action could be imagined. If this were to happen, even a True Divinity would instantly perish.

Rumble rumble rumble!

After the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign sank into Famine’s body, a massive black vortex appeared beneath it. Then, Famine’s massive body slowly fell into this vortex, sinking into the dark chaos before it vanished from sight.

Following that, space restored itself and Famine completely disappeared. Spatial ripples spread out before calming down, as if nothing had happened here. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had taken Famine and vanished together.

……….

Meanwhile, deep in space, a white spirit ship was rapidly racing along!

The Ark of Hope had escaped into the vastness of space and had activated the great void shift. Every use of the great void shift crossed a billion trillion miles, spanning innumerable celestial bodies as it raced through the universe!

Within the Ark of Hope, Diwuhen and To Bagui had assumed command. They had taken over the position of the old God Sovereign and were managing the escape.

Now, the two of them had become the pillars of everyone’s minds and hearts.

In that previous great battle they had lost the leaders of their two greatest ancient races. Not just that, but numerous respected elders and legendary figures had sacrificed themselves for the common good.

Even so, none of them had time to mope over the past. They were still being hunted and the dangers had yet to end…

The spirit ship’s atmosphere was tense and solemn.

For all these years the martial artists of the ancient remnant races had gone on war campaigns without end and were used to their friends and companions dying. Martial artists may stand arrogantly above all of existence, wielding everything in the universe and defying the will of the heavens, but the truth was that once they died they often didn’t even have bones left over.  There would be nothing left of them but ash and smoke that faded away in the world.

“Everyone, take this chance to restore your wounds as much as possible!” Diwuhen loudly proclaimed.

Once the Ark of Hope was able to fly away at full speed, the amount of energy it used would be far less. Now, there was less than 10% remaining in the Ark of Hope’s energy reserves. While it wasn’t enough to operate the protective shield, it was sufficient to fly to the Divine Realm.

The Empyreans all swallowed down pills and sat in meditation.

But at this time, Lin Ming’s expression was still stern. He thought for a moment and then said, “Everyone… I have a foreboding feeling…”

“Mm?”

Many people looked towards in Ming. These casual words had no reasoning behind them, but was only a simple foreboding feeling that many people felt all the time. It normally shouldn’t have been enough to arouse anyone’s interest, but since the one speaking was Lin Ming, that was a completely different scenario.

“What is it?”

Smokeless stopped her meditation and looked to Lin Ming. She had consumed far too much strength and her face was paper white, making one feel pity for her.

“I can’t say for certain, but I feel that no matter how many times we activated great void shifts, we still never left the perception range of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign…”

Lin Ming’s words caused the martial artists present to be stunned. They all glanced at each, looks of fear and unease on their faces.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was far too terrifying an existence, one that they found hard to summon the courage to fight against. If it was true that they still hadn’t escaped the scope of his detection, how could they not be scared?

“Why do you have this feeling? A True Divinity’s divine sense can search a universe, but the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign has been severely injured so he shouldn’t have this ability…”

To Bagui’s complexion was ugly. Someone like the Great Brahmic God King could use his great supernatural power to search the world but doing so required an incredible amount of energy. For the current Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, doing this would be difficult to accomplish.

Lin Ming continued, “When I used the Asura Primal God Cannon to strike at the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s spirit mark, I became familiar with his soul force.”

What he said was a half-truth. When Lin Ming had opened the Daevic Eye Dao Palace to use the Magic Cube to capture the location of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s spirit mark in Famine, he had been able to feel the unique soul signature of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. So, even if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s divine sense was mixed into many others, Lin Ming could still pick it out.

Now, he felt a strange mental strength linger around them. It was extremely weak, but hadn’t left…

If it wasn’t for the Magic Cube and Daevic Eye Dao Palace, Lin Ming would never have sensed this.

“Is that so…”

Diwuhen took a deep breath. He could feel the situation devolving further and further. “If we must go to the Divine Realm then we must pass through one of the saints’ Heavens. If we really have been locked on by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, then our journey will be bitter indeed…”

If they followed the original plan, then the ancient remnant races would use the Asura Decree obtained from the Asura forbidden land to cross the God Lamenting Wall and directly enter the Divine Realm.

Such a journey was short, but unfortunately, although this special Asura Decree could pierce through the God Lamenting Wall, it still required a peak Empyrean to consume an enormous amount of energy to activate. The many peak Empyreans on the Ark of Hope had already pushed themselves to the point of exhaustion. If they didn’t rest to restore their strength it would be impossible for them to activate the Asura Decree.

So, they could only take the risks and pass through one of the saint’s Heavens!

Chapter 1917 – Return (A)

The Primeval Universe was one of the 33 Heavens. It was an incomparably vast space, but the Ark of Hope only used several days to quickly reach its end.

As long as they could pass through the God Lamenting Wall here, the other side would be one of the saints’ universes.

Currently, the ancient remnant races were racing against death. This was because even if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had managed to lock onto their position, it would still take time to pass on the information.

As long as the ancient remnant races could arrive at the Divine Realm before the armies of the saints intercepted them, then it would be their victory.

“Break through!”

Diwuhen ordered without hesitation. Within the void, the Ark of Hope accelerated without end, turning into a beam of divine light that crossed millions of miles instantly, directly impacting into the God Lamenting Wall.

Because of the great calamity from 3.6 billion years ago, the God Lamenting Wall separating the Primeval Universe and the saints’ universe had become extremely weak, nearly disappearing. If a peak empyrean were to strike it, piercing a hole through the God Lamenting Wall wouldn’t be difficult at all.

And the Ark of Hope’s full speed impact was even beyond the all-out strike of a peak Empyrean.

Woosh!

The Ark of Hope collided with the God of Lamenting. It was like an arrow shooting into an elastic curtain. The God Lamenting Wall stretched forwards, forming a massive cone on the other side.

The Ark of Hope quickly slowed down. The God Lamenting Wall violently shook. Finally, the wall tore open and the Ark of Hope succeeded in passing into the saints’ universe from the Primeval Universe.

The moment that they passed through the God Lamenting Wall, the ancient race powerhouses all felt their hearts gripped and went on full alert. They were afraid that behind the God Lamenting Wall, all that awaited them was the trap of the saint race.

But at this time, in this unknown saint race universe, all that existed was quiet space. Stars shined in the far off distance without the shadow of anyone present.

Everything was peaceful to the point of being eerie.

A restless feeling swelled within Diwuhen’s heart. But now was not the time to hesitate. He loudly proclaimed, “Full speed ahead!”

The primal god race was currently a worn out force filled with nothing but tired soldiers. But, the Ark of Hope didn’t slow down in the least. It passed through space, rapidly activating the great void shift.

Time and time again, the Ark of Hope crossed through this saint race universe.

The ancient races had a magnificent and gloriously long history. They possessed a star chart of the 33 Heavens, a grand map that broadly described the universes of the 33 Heavens.

It also marked where the universes of the 33 Heavens connected with each other and the main races that dwelled within them.

Although this star chart’s information was vague, it had an inestimable function for this moment. It could show them the general direction to take, otherwise the ancient races wouldn’t know just where to go to find the Divine Realm.

To Bagui looked at the star chart and said, “The universe we’re at is called Saint Strife Heaven. Its size is 70% that of the Primeval Universe and within the saints’ seven Heavens, it is one with a relatively low number of masters and is comparatively lacking in resources. According to what we know, this Saint Strife Heaven is one of the safer Heavens and there are no True Divinities here. There is a chance we can simply pass directly through and safely arrive at the Divine Realm!”

Even for a True Divinity, wanting to travel through the universe to catch up would require time. Even if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign wanted to send out news of their arrival it would still require time. Their successful escape wasn’t a hopeless prospect by any means.

Moreover, according to information obtained by the primal god race, the True Divinities of the saint race were in a heated struggle against each other. This was because the situation involved ownership of all the resources within the Primeval Realm Ruins.

Amongst the saint race True Divinities, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was the strongest. He had established the largest influence of the saint race and became the Saint Sovereign of the saint race, commanding all seven Heavens of the saints. He wrested away almost 80% of the saint race’s total resources, including the Primeval Realm Ruins and the Grandmist Spirit Bead. Finally, he even managed to subdue Famine’s body, making that soulless body into his avatar.

All advantages were taken by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

In this situation, the other True Divinities were certainly discontent.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had launched a great war focused on the primal god race. This war was to plunder the resources of the primeval ruins, and most of these resources would be taken by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

As for the war against the Divine Realm, this was also because of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s ambitions. The other saint race True Divinities weren’t necessarily willing to serve as the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s spear.

Amongst all the bad news, this was the only piece of good news.

As they continued passing through space, Diwuhen looked at the star chart, beads of sweat seeping out of his forehead.

“Three more great void shifts and we should arrive at the God Lamenting Wall beside the Divine Realm. There we will be able to pass through the God Lamenting Wall and enter the Divine Realm!”

Diwuhen said. But as he spoke his complexion suddenly changed. In that moment he could feel the Ark of Hope suddenly slow down as if it had fallen into a swamp!

“What’s happening!?” To Bagui’s complexion also changed. He could feel that the Ark of Hope had entered a giant force field. The surrounding space was sealed!

Bang!

The grand hall housing the Ark of Hope’s array formation suddenly shook like an earthquake passed through it. The martial artists managing the array formation were shaken off their positions.

Everyone was left panic-stricken. They looked out the porthole to see dozens of spirit ships before them. They had already been waiting there and had activated their array formations!

The Ark of Hope was a little fly that had landed on a spider’s web, unable to move!

And to create an array formation that could intercept the Ark of Hope, the strength of their opponents could be imagined!

“Saint race spirit ships!”

Diwuhen sucked in a breath of cold air. They had been ambushed!

“How could they be so quick!?”

A roaring bone race Empyrean clenched his fists, his voice filled with unwillingness. They were already so close to the Divine Realm! Just a little bit more and they would have been able to flee the Saint Strife Heaven. But now, all of their plans had fallen short!

“From the time that we escaped until now, only several days have passed. During the days we spent traveling through two universes of the 33 Heavens, we did so entirely within the Ark of Hope; it would be impossible for anyone to be faster than us. And logically speaking, even if our location was traced there shouldn’t have been anyone here who could have caught up and still had enough time to lay down these array formations… these people should have been transferred here from the Divine Realm…”

In a quiet corner, Lin Ming suddenly spoke up. Although his voice was calm and composed, his words couldn’t hide their tinge of weakness. In that battle against the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, Lin Ming had used up far too much energy. He had almost combusted his soul and had been forced to overdraw his mind and soul force.

“Transferred from the Divine Realm, huh…”

To Bagui muttered out loud. Lin Ming’s explanation was the most reasonable possibility. The saint races controlled seven Heavens, but in the end they still relied on Empyrean level spirit ships to travel. If they wanted to cross through a universe of the 33 Heavens, it would still require one or two months. In a short several days, wanting to summon so many martial artists to this area of a universe was easier said than done, much less not all Empyreans were commanded by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

However, if the martial artists that were sent to the Divine Realm were ordered to return and intercept the Ark of Hope, then that would be far easier.

“Ancient remnant races, I’ve been waiting for you for far too long!”

In the void, a loud and grand voice echoed outwards. A red-robed middle aged man slowly flew out from the middle of the saint race forces.

A faint smile hung on his face and he wore battle armor over his robes. His cultivation was at the peak Empyrean realm.

His eyes were like lightning. He casually swept over the Ark of Hope’s array formation and could see that its energy reserves were now down to 5%!

Although this was still a Beyond Divinity level spirit treasure, it was impossible for its true potential to be displayed.

“The background of these ancient remnant races is indeed deep. To think they could get their hands on such a supreme treasure. What a pity for them, but all of this will belong to the saints…”

The armored man diabolically grinned. Killing the ancient races and capturing Lin Ming alive, this would be a monumental merit. His fame and prestige amongst the saints would skyrocket and he would also obtain rich rewards from the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

At this time, behind the middle-aged man, space began to distort with ripples.

One after another, saint race Empyreans appeared, their figures slowly appearing as they broke through space.

Their cultivations were amazing and their blood vitality was overwhelming. As they stood in space they were like planets blocking the world. Among them there were several individuals that emanated an aura as deep as an abyss, as if they were unfathomable beings.

These were also peak Empyreans, not much worse than the armored Empyrean who first appeared.

The ancient race powerhouses within the Ark of Hope all had grim expressions. They could feel a great crisis and pressure pushing down on them!

They had fled the tiger’s den just to enter the wolf’s lair!

And it just so happened that they had used up nearly all of their strength in order to escape the Primeval Universe. Moreover, they only had two peak Empyreans left in To Bagui and Diwuhen. What capital did they have to fight with these saint Empyreans in front of them?

“Must the heavens destroy my people?”

Diwuhen clenched his fists so hard that his hands shivered. The old God Sovereign had sacrificed himself, handing the future of their people to him.

But… in the end, this… was all that resulted…

“Damn!”

Diwuhen’s nails dug so deep into his palms that blood began dripping.

At this time, the ancient race Empyreans began moving forwards, standing behind Diwuhen.

They faced the porthole and saw this force of saint Empyreans that was ten times stronger and had been biding their time here. For a time, a tragic desolateness spread in their hearts.

They were well aware that in this following battle, it was likely they would all be annihilated!

Chapter 1919 – Reunion

Bang!

After being struck by the joint attack of the saint Empyreans, the Ark of Hope was sent tumbling away. The protective shield covering the ship had been cracked open like an eggshell, with alarming fissures in the runes.

Some of the energy from the saint Empyreans’ attacks was already able to pierce through the protective shield and crash into the Ark of Hope.

“Lin Ming, who did you say is coming?”

Diwuhen grabbed Lin Ming’s shoulder. In such a critical situation he didn’t know whether the people Lin Ming spoke of were friends or enemies.

“The Divine Realm… human martial artists!”

Lin Ming said. At this time, within his mind, the Thousand Mile Heartlink was still reverberating with Xiao Moxian’s worried voice.

“Divine Realm! Humans!”

The ancient race powerhouses were stunned upon hearing this. The Divine Realm was separated from the Primeval Universe by another Heaven. Even if the great calamity descended and the God Lamenting Wall became extremely weak, it would be difficult for their races to meet. Even so, the two races had just the tiniest connection between them.

Empyrean Primordius was a human and Heavenly Empress Xuanqing had died in the Divine Realm.

Humanity was once a peak race of the 33 Heavens, but after the great calamity 3.6 billion years ago their inheritances had been severed and their True Divinities had died out. Even most of their Empyreans perished in the conflict and they had become a waning race.

Just what would humanity of the present era be like?

As the ancient race martial artists were stunned, there was a loud detonation as the Ark of Hope’s protective shield finally shattered into pieces!

In the midst of the terrifying attack, a beam of energy shot out, causing brilliant fireworks to light up the dark space!

“It’s finally broken, heh!”

The gold crowned Empyrean and the Saint General both chuckled. They used their techniques, about to fatally strike down the many martial artists within the Ark of Hope. But at this time, Diwuhen threw out two god decrees without a hint of hesitation!

Woosh!

The god decrees cut through space like a divine arrow, exploding in the cosmos. They formed a dreadful shockwave that swept over a million miles of space.

The gold crown Empyrean savagely grinned.

“Using the same old tricks to delay for time, but you still won’t be able to change your fate of annihilation!”

The gold crown Empyrean avoided the god decrees’ energy storm and was about to attack once more. But at this time his complexion changed. He turned to see that behind him, just 10,000 miles away, ripple-like distortions began to appear in the pitch black space…

Within these ripples an exquisite white building slowly surfaced. This was a palace!

This white jade palace seemed insignificant compared to the massive spatial ripples around it, like a leaf of jade floating in the water.

But as the gold crown Empyrean looked at this white jade palace he felt something bizarre and weird. Looking at this palace, he felt as if all of existence were unreal and this palace was slowly fluttering towards him from some distant dream.

And following that, right behind this palace, spirit ships began to rush out en masse. These spirit ships were all massive constructions, each one emitting a vast and solemn atmosphere!

And amidst these spirit ships there was a golden great buddha!

This golden great buddha sat upon a lotus throne, its body a thousand miles long, stabilizing the surrounding void. Rays of buddhic light lingered around it, giving it a solemn and hallowed atmosphere. Buddhist chants hummed in the air, ignoring distances of space to resound in the ears of all like a great bell enlightening the mind, so loud that even the deaf could hear it!

Like this, the great buddha flew forwards in space like a giant sun, dazzling to the eyes.

“Humanity!?”

The high commander of the saint race’s Divine Realm invasion force, the red-robed Saint General, narrowed his eye as he saw those spirit ships. After preparing for war in the Divine Realm for so many years he certainly recognized the influences of humanity.

The white jade palace originated from Divine Dream Heavenly Palace. As for the golden great buddha, it was from the most glorious and storied human Empyrean Holy Land – Mount Potala. This was Mount Potala’s supreme treasure for crossing through space!

“Humanity… these are human martial artists?”

Diwuhen, To Bagui, and the many other ancient race Empyreans had looks of surprise and disbelief twining together on their faces as they saw the forces of humanity arrive.

They had heard that humanity had long been on the decline. In the minds of the primal god race, the entire Divine Realm might be far more populous than the Primeval Universe, but the number of genuine masters probably wasn’t much higher. Thus, as they saw this sight before them today, all of them were filled with incredulity.

Whether it was that white jade palace or that golden great buddha, both gave off immeasurably deep feelings.

From a misty sea of white light around the white jade palace, a white-clothed woman stepped forth from the void. Millions of hazy white silk ribbons hung from her body, enveloping her in a faint fog. She was a genius of peerless talent and grace.

Looking at her was like looking at a goddess from a dream. Even though it was difficult to see her appearance, she actually gave off an inexplicable feeling, as if there was always a small voice in one’s head informing a person that she was beautiful to the extreme.

Her steps were calm and measured. She held a ribbon in her hand, as if she weren’t here to slaughter her enemies but simply taking a leisurely walk through the park, enjoying the sights.

Meanwhile, in the two eyes of the great golden buddha, there were two men in kasyas respectively sitting in the right eye and left eye.

The one in the right eye was an enlightened old monk. He held a monk’s staff, a khakkhara, in his hands, set horizontally above his lap. His eyes were closed as sutras were prayed from between his lips.

And in the left eye was a young monk. His face was sharp and polished. He was an incredibly handsome individual and he wore a crown atop his head. His eyes were as bright as the moon and his lips were red like cinnabar.

This young man wearing the kasya was one of humanity’s most talented Empyreans – Emperor Shakya!

And behind the great golden buddha was a magnificently built bright red divine warship. Atop the bow of this warship, a tall old man wielding a great sword arrogantly stood there. He wore red robes and his aura was aggressive and unfathomably deep.

In the negotiations between the saints and humanity, Lin Ming had once casually acquainted himself with this red-robed old man. He was a peak human Empyrean – Skyrend Godlord!

The four human Empyreans lined up, creating an array in the void. They formed a wall of energy that emitted a dreadful pressure, shocking the cosmos!

Even though both sides possessed peak Empyreans, the momentum of the saints was actually suppressed.

In particular, Divine Dream and Emperor Shakya. One yin, one yang, the two of them together nearly reached the realm of True Divinity!

“Empyrean Divine Dream, Senior Emperor Shakya, Great Limitless Buddha, Skyrend Godlord!”

As Lin Ming saw these four people he was ecstatic!

He had left the Divine Realm for dozens of years and had experienced hurdles and dangers, disregarding his own safety, risking his life and suffering countless hardships all the while. He had already felt constrained for a long time.

Now, when he was alone and without help, he saw the Empyreans of humanity arrive just in time!

“They are… humanity’s Empyreans?”

Diwuhen was shocked as he saw these people, especially Divine Dream and Emperor Shakya! In this great calamity the saints’ momentum had been overwhelming and unstoppable as they went to war in all directions, forcing other races to retreat again and again in defeat.

Some held the belief that the ancient remnant races were in the twilight of their years, soon to perish, and humanity’s destiny had already been exhausted. Although Diwuhen and To Bagui didn’t wish to acknowledge this, they also faintly had this idea in their hearts. But as they saw the sight before them, they actually discovered that humanity possessed mind-boggling peerless geniuses.

For contrast, even if the number one genius of the ancient remnant races, Smokeless, were to grow up, even she wouldn’t compare to Divine Dream and Emperor Shakya.

“Big Brother Lin!”

Lin Ming felt his breath leave him the moment he heard this familiar voice. He followed it to see that not too far behind Empyrean Divine Dream there was a young woman dressed in black. She was slim and elegant with skin as bright as porcelain. Her body was covered in a faint black fog and in the space around her, heaven and earth origin energy and starlight gathered, lingering about her.

The black-clothed woman’s belly was slightly raised. Exuding from it was a potent yet small life force. Even from such a distance, Lin Ming could feel that he shared the same roots as this life force.

This black-clothed woman was Xiao Moxian! Currently she was looking towards the Ark of Hope with worry on her face.

As for Lin Ming’s flesh and blood growing within her stomach, it had already been gestating for a long time. This was because for those of a God Beast bloodline, breeding a small life required a tremendously long period of time. But, once the child was born it would have a naturally gifted spiritual wisdom.

Lin Ming’s gaze pierced through the Ark of Hope’s porthole and looked right to Xiao Moxian.

Xiao Moxian couldn’t see Lin Ming but she could clearly feel his existence.

For a time, all sorts of feelings swelled up within his heart. He felt that he owed Xiao Moxian far too much…

During this time Lin Ming was unable to show himself as they were surrounded by the saints.

“Xian’er, how did you know we were in a crisis?”

In the Ark of Hope, Lin Ming used the Thousand Mile Heartlink to speak to Xiao Moxian.

“A woman told us. She wore a black dress and was as ephemeral as fog. She showed us images of you struggling in the Primeval Universe. Although Empyrean Divine Dream was suspicious she still quickly gathered the human elites to race here. Luckily we managed to catch up in time…”

As Xian Moxian happily spoke, Lin Ming was stunned. A black-dressed woman as ephemeral as fog… could it be Soul Empress Sheng Mei?

Only she would know that he was bitterly engaged with the saints.

“Sheng Mei… she saved us?”

Lin Ming didn’t know what to feel. There were too many riddles concerning Sheng Mei.

Lin Ming looked towards Empyrean Divine Dream once more. He knew that for Divine Dream to act according to such uncertain news and gather the elites of humanity to rush here was actually an incredibly great risk!

If this was a trap then there was a chance they could all be annihilated…

Even so, Empyrean Divine Dream had relied on her own instinct and judgment to make such a bold and decisive decision. And the reason she took such a risk was mostly to rescue Lin Ming!

Thinking of this, Lin Ming felt inexplicably moved. Empyrean Primordius, Heavenly Empress Xuanqing, the old God Sovereign, Divine Dream, even Empyrean Divine Seal from 3.6 billion years in the past, as well as the warriors of humanity and the ancient remnant races, all of these people were fighting beside him. He was not alone…

……

In the void, the red-robed Saint General stepped forwards. He looked at Empyrean Divine Dream and sneered, “Divine Dream… hehe! To think you would cross the God Lamenting Wall to challenge us. Are you planning to officially declare war with my saint race?”

Although the red-robed Saint General was the supreme commander of the saint race’s Divine Realm invasion force, the truth was that they had never actually truly struck at the Divine Realm.

Almost a hundred years ago, the saints sent the Good Fortune Saint Son to Mount Potala. There, the many Empyreans established a contract stating that the battlefield would be limited to the Bright Luster World, and those at the Empyrean level wouldn’t directly participate in the battles.

Humanity and the saints had existed in precarious peace.

But today, this temporary and false peace would be broken!

Let the curtains of the true war rise today!

Chapter 1921 – Emperor Shakya

Weng weng weng!

The blood red spear was unstoppable. It tore through the cosmos. During a bitter battle between peak Empyreans, another peak Empyrean had launched a sneak attack!

Ca!

The divine dream space was torn open. The blood red spear pierced in, thrusting straight towards the point between Empyrean Divine Dream’s eyebrows!

The golden crown Empyrean was crimson with effort; he attacked without holding anything back!

Seeing the blood red spear shoot towards her, Empyrean Divine Dream floated backwards. Her beautiful eyes opened and a light melody began to bloom from between her cherry red lips.

Although the sound was faint, it was enchanting and wondrous.

In that moment the surrounding space seemed to have a marvelous reaction to this faint sound.

Within the pitch black space, starlight surged.

Immediately, heavenly sounds appeared like sunshine reviving the dark world, all of it flowing out from Empyrean Divine Dream’s body.

From the emptiness of space sublime luminescence shot out. True Phoenixes appeared, dancing in the universe.

All sorts of beautiful sights began appearing in the dark universe.

Seeing this, Lin Ming’s pupils contracted.

Dreamsoul Immortal Melody!

At the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, Lin Ming had personally experienced Frost Dream’s immortal melody. It was because of this that he had tied with her.

As this mysterious melody appeared, from within the peaceful world, infinite killing intent rose.

Underneath the hands of Empyrean Divine Dream, the Dreamsoul Immortal Melody was countless times more formidable that Frost Dream’s version.

In an infinitely fascinating illusion, divine mountains appeared, floating up and down in space. Towering spiritual trees reached into the skies, on equal ground with the heavens.

These divine mountains floated atop planets. The planets roared as they crashed into that blood red lance.

As for the True Phoenixes, they flapped their wings and flames swept through the world, surrounding the golden crown Empyrean.

Raging flames even burnt through the void, as if a sheet of black paper had been ignited.

The golden crown Empyrean trembled. Beneath the high heat, his flesh and blood seemed to be baking and burning. As the blood red lance was struck by those planets it began to crack apart.

It wasn’t just the primal god Empyreans that were shocked, but even the human Empyreans were left dumbfounded!

“Divine Dream, she seems to have made a breakthrough…”

Skyrend Godlord and Great Limitless Buddha had only ever heard rumors of Divine Dream’s prestige and strength. Neither of them had truly seen her fight.

In the Divine Realm, although Empyrean Divine Dream had used her divine dream space before, it had always been seen as ethereal and wonderful, filled with a mystical rhythm and an exquisite aesthetic sense. Never before had it been used in such a horrifying manner, ringing with killing intent!

The top human powerhouses could feel that from the start, Empyrean Divine Dream had been fighting with everything she had, without holding anything back.

With her own power she contended with two peak saint Empyreans. And, it was obvious that she had completely suppressed the both of them. This was a nearly unimaginable strength!

Skyrend Godlord and Great Limitless Buddha both felt they were far inferior to her.

“This woman, how could she be so fierce!!” Amongst the saint race Empyreans, another person moved. A great black bow appeared in his hands.

He stepped forth into the void. Blood shot out from his hands, forming into a blood arrow.

With a deep roar, the bowstring tightened again without end. All light in the surrounding space seemed to gather on the tip of the arrow, causing everything to tremble.

Endless strength gathered onto the arrow points, aimed straight towards the distant Empyrean Divine Dream.

The arrow point exuded a boundless shaking. Pitch black ripples appeared, spreading out in all directions.

This strength was mighty and forceful, giving off a feeling that it could even pierce through the cosmos, a completely irresistible attack.

All starlight for a million miles began to sway and distort. The essence of the starlight began to gather towards the arrow point.

More and more energy gathered. The arrow began to howl as black light appeared around it.

Woosh!

The blood red divine arrow that gathered the endless starlight pierced through space and vanished without a trace.

This all-annihilating arrow shot to the edge of the divine dream space.

Once the arrow arrived at its target, it would be three against one.

Three peak Empyreans to fight Divine Dream!

And at this time, light bloomed. A golden buddha diagram spanned through space. It was incomparably large and shined with an eternal light, bathing the surrounding space in a warming glow.

In the boundless buddha light, small buddhas appeared.

These buddhas sat cross-legged within the endless buddha light, reciting ancient texts.

The broad texts gathered together, shaking the world.

The great buddha diagram collided with the pitch black arrow.

Waves of ringing sounds echoed through the world.

A boundless explosive light submerged all.

Finally, that black arrow vanished, completely submerged by this buddhic light.

“To bully one with so many, do you really think there is no one in my human race?” A cold voice resounded in space. The one who had moved was Emperor Shakya!

His figure floated in the center of the giant golden buddha diagram. His handsome face was flooded with a chilling killing intent.

It was rumored that even though Emperor Shakya was young, his strength had already surpassed that of Great Limitless Buddha. He was the number one master of Mount Potala!

In his hand, a wisp of black light glowed before being erased, as if he were extinguishing a candle.

His aura was deep and unbreakable like a prison, unfathomably deep. The anger on his face was like a volcano soon to erupt.

Emperor Shakya had blocked that cosmos-shaking arrow, his actions shocking the saint Empyreans. In particular, the peak Empyrean who shot out the arrow had a dignified look in his eyes.

That arrow just now had been condensed from that peak Empyrean’s blood vitality and energy. He didn’t know how much strength Emperor Shakya had used to block it, but he had used at least 80% of his strength.

Emperor Shakya’s body emitted a blinding radiance, like a great sun rising in space, dazzling to the eyes.

His eyes opened and endless buddhic light swirled in his palms, forming a vast dharmic wheel.

In the center of this dharmic wheel, six masses of power appeared, each one containing the irresistible strength of a samsara.

In the center of each mass of power, the figure of Emperor Shakya appeared.

Whorl whorl whorl.

These figures of Emperor Shakya emitted light that distorted the void. Like a boundless vortex, this light covered the world.

Bang!

The six Emperor Shakyas in the center of these six samsaras joined together with Emperor Shakya’s true body. They began to drag in the figure of the peak Empyrean with the pitch black bow.

This was a fierce battle!

“You are courting death!”

The saint Empyrean was enraged. He drew his bow and shot again and again.

Woosh! Woosh ! Woosh!

Pitch black shadows tore through the void, carrying with them a heaven-destroying momentum as millions of beams of black light appeared.

These black lights were from the peak saint Empyrean, shooting arrow after arrow.

Each arrow was infused with blood essence, easily able to pierce through a planet.

But those seemingly mighty black arrows were useless in front of Emperor Shakya.

Each arrow was stopped by the endless light of the golden buddha diagram, melting away.

Emperor Shakya’s six great avatars formed a buddha diagram with his main body. Within this buddha diagram, every Emperor Shakya was covered with a martial intent.

With the main body and the avatars added together there were seven martial intents – this was the basis of Emperor Shakya’s martial arts!

In the past, Emperor Shakya divided himself into a billion avatars, each avatar comprehending seven martial intents on their own and finally fusing them together. In terms of achievements in martial intents, Emperor Shakya had already reached the peak. It was impossible for anyone to surpass him in this aspect!

The seven layers of martial intents suddenly evolved into six samsaras. An incomparably powerful true meaning of the Great Dao swirled in space.

His fists were like planets, his pupils like suns. His vast and boundless aura locked in the surrounding world, suppressing all.

Inexhaustible buddhic light shot out from his body, brutally battling with the saint Empyrean before him.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

The sounds of explosions continued without end.

That saint Empyrean with astonishing archery skills was pushed back again and again by Emperor Shakya’s tide-like barrage. Explosions blew up in the void behind him.

As the peak saint Empyrean was forced backwards, the pressure on him increased with each step. His face became increasingly grim!

This saint Empyrean was still able to barely defend against Emperor Shakya. Although he wasn’t Emperor Shakya’s match, the difference wasn’t too great; he wouldn’t be immediately defeated.

But as he turned his head to see Divine Dream fighting the two saint Empyreans, he discovered that their situation was even worse than his own!

There were two of them, and the strength of those two was considered to be at the pinnacle of all saint Empyreans. Yet they were single-handedly beaten down by Divine Dream alone, with a chance that their lives would be ended.

It had to be known that once one reached the level of a peak Empyrean, it was difficult to die unless a True Divinity attacked.

“We should retreat!”

The bow-wielding Empyrean told the other peak Empyreans with a sound transmission. It was already impossible for them to win. Staying here would only mean more casualties.

“Withdraw!”

As the red-robed Saint General desperately resisted the divine dream space’s symbol attack, he grit his teeth and sent out a sound transmission.

The saint race Empyreans all felt humiliated by this. For these past years they had domineeringly wandered through the Divine Realm, and even human Empyreans were afraid to fight them. Yet, today they were the ones being beaten up instead!

Chapter 1923 – Evacuate

“Senior Divine Dream, are you alright?”

Lin Ming was highly concerned about Divine Dream’s situation. In truth he understood that Divine Dream had yet to break into the True Divinity realm; she was just a tiny bit away.

If Divine Dream didn’t temporarily fuse together with Frost Dream and only fought with her true self, then although she could still suppress a peak Empyrean, wanting to prevent them from escaping and killing them was extremely difficult. Moreover, that golden crown Empyrean and red-robed Saint General were both outstanding saint Empyreans.

At this time, blue misty light began glowing around Frost Dream. This misty light gathered on her supple figure, turning into a blue dress.

Frost Dream stretched her body. Floating in the air, she reached back her hands and flipped out her hair. As her long hair fell back in waves, fragrant wind blew through the air, enchanting the senses.

“Miss Frost Dream.”

Lin Ming greeted.

Frost Dream nodded in return, responding with “Sir Lin,” before composing herself and remaining quiet.

Lin Ming then discovered that Frost Dream’s cultivation had reached the World King realm. Compared to himself, she was even faster.

However, this was normal. Frost Dream was Divine Dream’s avatar and had Divine Dream’s soul as her foundation. Frost Dream’s cultivation speed would naturally be exorbitantly fast, and with the invasion of the saints, Divine Dream must have also decided to speed up Frost Dream’s breakthroughs in order to quickly step into True Divinity.

“You’ve heard that it was a black-clothed woman who sent me a sound transmission saying that you were in the Primeval Universe? Do you know who that woman is?”

Divine Dream asked Lin Ming. She clearly had some understandings of the Primeval Universe.

“Junior believes that this woman was likely Soul Empress Sheng Mei.”

Lin Ming said, glancing at Xiao Moxian. Xiao Moxian was astonished, but as she thought about it, it could only be her. That woman had been shrouded in a black fog and was incomparably mysterious. Even so, Xiao Moxian was able to faintly feel the terrifying strength that lurked beneath the surface.

Out of all the woman Lin Ming knew, only Sheng Mei could know so much and have such abilities.

“Let us return first. Now isn’t the time to stay here. This is the saints’ universe; it is too dangerous.”

As Divine Dream spoke, the fleet turned around and flew towards the Divine Realm.

After several great void shifts, the fleet returned to the God Lamenting Wall. Because of the great calamity, the God Lamenting Wall connecting this saint race universe and the Divine Realm was extremely fragile. Skyrend Godlord was able to forcefully form a connection through it.

The fleet returned to the Divine Realm in glory and victory.

Looking at these familiar starry skies and feeling the familiar heaven and earth origin energy, Lin Ming bathed himself in the atmosphere.

The Divine Realm – he had finally returned!

During this trip he had been gone for over 20 years. He had been to the Soul World and Primeval Universe, risking his life several times and now finally returning safely.

Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, within a grand hall of white jade –

The human Empyreans and ancient race Empyreans had gathered together. Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian were also included.

“You are descendants of the ancient races from 10 billion years past?”

For many human Empyreans, this was the first time they learned of the status of these ancient race Empyreans. The fame and magnificence of the ancient races from 10 billion years ago was too far-reaching and resounding. It was only that in the present era, they had declined to a miserable state.

“Yes… we have been fighting with the saints for many years now. The reason we fled this time was Little Brother Lin’s suggestion. But during the process, we encountered the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and were almost annihilated…”

Once upon a time, being from the ancient races was Diwuhen’s pride. But now he felt that there just wasn’t anything to be proud of.

“What! You encountered the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign!? Then you…!”

The human Empyreans were panic-stricken at hearing Diwuhen’s words. They had encountered the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and managed to survive somehow?

At this time, Divine Dream slowly said, “Everyone, quiet yourselves. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign has been severely wounded by the joint efforts of the ancient race martial artists, Lin Ming, and Empyrean Primordius. He is currently recovering from his injuries, and moreover… the ancient races and Lin Ming have brought the path to salvation for us. Perhaps… it is finally time for our human race to experience a favorable turn…”

As Divine Dream slowly spoke, all of the human Empyreans present were dumbstruck.

The information contained in her words was far too great.

Heavily wound the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign? How had they done that? Moreover… how was this related to Empyrean Primordius who had perished 100,000 years ago?

The path to salvation? What was that?

As the human Empyreans were puzzled, Divine Dream looked at Lin Ming and said, “Why don’t you come up and explain it yourself.”

Whether it was the ancient races or the human race, Lin Ming was the greatest contributor to there being such a favorable turn!

To bring back the method to salvation from the Asura forbidden land, to renew the god decrees, to contend with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, Lin Ming’s function during all of this was irreplaceable.

Lin Ming nodded. At a brisk pace, without showing arrogance or beings subservient, he explained everything that had happened during his adventure through the Soul World and Primeval Universe. The only things he omitted were the strange words Sheng Mei had said to him.

The human Empyreans were dumbfounded upon hearing this.

They knew that Lin Ming had left by himself, headed towards the world of the spiritas to seek out a path to salvation for humanity. But, almost no one had thought he would succeed.

In the eyes of those people, his actions had been nothing more than a joke!

Just what cultivation did Lin Ming have? Before he left, he was only able to defeat a Great World King.

And what humanity faced was a terrifying and massive race that had multiple True Divinities and over a thousand Empyreans!

In the impending universal calamity, Lin Ming couldn’t even be called a small wave. Even the human Empyreans felt the situation was hopeless and had nearly succumbed to sitting down and waiting for death.

In such an atmosphere, Lin Ming had gone to seek out a road for humanity to take. Was that even possible?

But the actual result had left them all bewildered.

Lin Ming had truly found the method to salvation. It wasn’t a way to directly face the saints, but instead an escape route for humanity!

Just an escape route was not enough. In the Divine Realm’s 3000 great worlds and innumerable other worlds, there were countless great human influences. If all of these influences had to be notified and evacuated, that would be a mission of monumental proportions. If the saint race decided to launch their all-out invasion of the Divine Realm now then humanity would have no time to flee.

But… Lin Ming had joined together with the ancient races and had managed to wound the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, buying time for humanity in the process. This was just unbelievable!

Many human Empyreans looked at Lin Ming with amazement in their eyes. When Lin Ming left the Divine Realm to go to the Soul World and Primeval Universe, he could be said to have created a miracle.

He had done a great service for humanity and could nearly be compared to Empyrean Divine Seal of 3.6 billion years ago.

“Everyone should be clear on what the method is… that is, before the saints’ total invasion begins, we shall evacuate to one of the wild universes within the 33 Heavens… the Divine Realm has over a trillion quadrillion people and there are even more people in the lower realms. To evacuate them all is a completely impossible task. But, we can evacuate the elites and preserve our martial arts civilization and inheritances.

“In other words, for at least the next 100,000 years, the general human population will have to live beneath the oppression of the saints. As for the elites of humanity, they must face the wilderness of the 33 Heavens, suffering the difficulties to develop it and survive there! As for the future, whether we are eliminated or find a chance to breathe, all of that will depend on the next 100,000 years. In that group of elites who develop within the wilderness, we shall see whether or not we can raise proud children of heaven who can resist the saints.

“If we can, then we shall slaughter our way back to the Divine Realm and destroy the saints. If we cannot, then we can only wait to perish. After all, the God Lamenting Wall is not an absolute protection.”

Empyrean Divine Dream’s words caused the human Empyreans to fall silent.

Of the 33 Heavens, seven Heavens belonged to the spiritas, seven Heavens belonged to the saints, one Heaven was the Primeval Universe, and another Heaven was the Divine Realm.

In total this was 16 Heavens. Besides these 16 Heavens there were also 17 more. These 17 Heavens were death lands or wildernesses. Because of the great hundred race war from 10 billion years ago, these universes had slowly declined. Moreover, the God Lamenting Walls dividing these universes were extremely firm, unlike the walls dividing the Divine Realm and saint universes. The walls between the Divine Realm and saint universes would weaken in cycles until they finally completely vanished.

Thus, for all this time, these 17 Heavens had never had intelligent humanoid life forces exist within them.

If the human elites were to use the Asura Decree to penetrate through the God Lamenting Wall and go to these abandoned Heavens, it would undoubtedly mean a bitter and grueling journey.

Many people would die as they pioneered new lands. Even those that survived would have to face the greedy gazes of the saints, unsure whether they would live to see the next day.

Many human martial artists understood this. They knew just what it meant to escape into the wild universes…

Moreover, they had heavy hearts upon thinking about abandoning the common people of the Divine Realm. But there was nothing they could do about this. After all, the elites of humanity were the targets of the saints. If these elites were killed then that would be the same as wiping out humanity’s inheritances.

As for the common folk, the truth was that they held no value for the saints.

The atmosphere in the grand hall become much more gloomy.

Lin Ming had indeed discovered a path for humanity. But, this path was filled with thorns!

Empyrean Divine Dream slowly stood up.

“I, as well as all disciples of Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, have already decided to leave the Divine Realm and develop ourselves in the wild universes. As for the rest of you, you can decide whether you wish to join me or stay in the Divine Realm. I understand that you have feelings for your homeland and to abandon the home you’ve known all your life is a difficult choice. But, sometimes, you have to abandon what you know…

“To leave means facing unknown perils and shouldering the burden of being humanity’s hopes and futures.

“To stay means living underneath the heel and oppression of the saints, struggling in battle…

“No matter what path you choose, your journey will be incredibly difficult. My only hope is that no matter when in the future, none of you will easily give up. This is because humanity truly stands on the precipice of life or death. 3.6 billion years ago, we were indeed defeated, but even then we still retained the Divine Realm. But if we are to be defeated again now then we truly will not have any road to escape to.”

Empyrean Divine Dream’s words were heavy and grim. All of the human Empyreans held their breath. For a time, the entire grand hall was silent, and even the sound of a needle dropping could be heard.

Everyone faintly realized this was an important meeting that concerned the future of humanity!

“I represent Mount Potala to say that we will leave the Divine Realm and follow Divine Dream Heavenly Palace.”

The first to speak was Great Limitless Buddha. The truth was that before this meeting began, he had already known of the situation. He was only making his stance clear here.

“I will also follow Empyrean Divine Dream.”

“Me too.”

Empyrean after Empyrean opened their mouth, all of them willing to follow Empyrean Divine Dream.

To abandon the Divine Realm was the only choice they could make in such a helpless situation.

“Good.”

Divine Dream took a deep breath. “If that’s the case then let us not delay. We will disperse now and assemble the various great influences to prepare the evacuation. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign may be heavily wounded but the most he will need is several years to recover… we must use this period of time to complete the evacuation mission and bring as many people as we can in the time limit.”

Chapter 1924 – Astral Vault God King

Primeval Universe, within the infinite deeps…

In the space that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was hidden in, over 20 saint Empyreans in full battle attire had laid down a Good Fortune Grand Array.

In addition, there were many World Kings and Holy Lords. They were distributed at the edges of the Good Fortune Grand Array, supporting it.

The saint Empyreans had grim complexions.

This was because the Divine Realm’s red-robed Saint General had led the dregs of his defeated forces back here.

The golden crown Empyrean had perished and the red-robed Saint General had been forced to burn his blood essence, causing his cultivation to drop. To the saints, this was an unprecedented disastrous loss.

But as these defeated troops came to the Primeval Universe, only then did they learn that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, before issuing his order, had been severely wounded by the joint efforts of Lin Ming and the ancient races and was now recovering.

This left them all dumbstruck.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was an outstanding existence even amongst True Divinities. Even with the ancient race Empyreans and Lin Ming added together, how could they possibly have wounded the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign?

“His Majesty Saint Sovereign, he…”

The red-robed Saint General was embittered. He had originally angrily come back, wanting to report the situation to the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign so that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign would mobilize his full army to trample over the Divine Realm.

But what he learned was actually something almost unbelievable.

“His Majesty has closed up in seclusion – no one may see him!”

The Empyreans responsible for protecting these grounds said. The red-robed Saint General gulped, feeling his head aching.

The saint race was at least 10 times more powerful than the primal god race, so how did that battle turn out with such a strange result?

As the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was in seclusion, the red-robed Saint General could only wait.

He faintly guessed that this period of seclusion would not be short. It would be at least two to three years.

At this time, a terrifying pressure arrived, like a galactic storm sweeping through the cosmos.

Underneath this tremendous pressure, all Holy Lords and World Kings were forced to their knees.

Although the saint race Empyreans weren’t suppressed to such a miserable degree, they still felt their hearts race with fear. Without a doubt, this sort of pressure could only belong to a True Divinity!

All of the saint martial artists rapidly bowed towards the void.

They felt a vast sea of astral essence swell towards them. This was proof that the one arriving was a saint race True Divinity!

At this time, the void trembled. A massive face appeared in the space a million miles away. This face seemed to be carved from metal, solemn and mighty, possessing an astonishing character!

As the saint martial artists saw this giant face, they shivered.

Astral Vault God King!

In the saint race’s seven Heavens there was more than one True Divinity.

Generally speaking, the True Divinities of the saints were extremely mysterious. They seldom appeared and even the common people didn’t know how many True Divinities were in the saint race or what their titles were.

“Astral Vault God King, one of the hidden God Kings of the saint world. It is said that he is a hundred million years older than His Majesty Saint Sovereign!”

“Astral Vault God King, he… shouldn’t have come to… harm the Saint Sovereign, right…”

Several peak Empyreans subordinate to the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign gulped as they thought of this.

According to rumors, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was on ill terms with Astral Vault God King. It was said that they might have fought before, and it wouldn’t be a surprise if there was some sort of personal grudge between them.

Now that Astral Vault God King had arrived, if he really came to take revenge then the Empyreans stationed here would only be able to stare helplessly on as he attacked the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

“Your Majesty Astral Vault…”

Several Empyreans greeted in awe.

“Out of my way!”

Astral Vault God King shouted out loud and these Empyreans were swept away as if they were caught in a storm. They could barely steady themselves as they felt completely helpless in their fear.

They were subordinates of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. It wasn’t likely that Astral Vault God King had any good impressions of them.

Astral Vault God King slowly flew forwards to the space distortion that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had hidden in and sneered.

With a mere thought, a massive metal hand stretched out from space. This hand casually moved and easily tore open the space distortion that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had closed up in. Then, Astral Vault God King stepped inside!

The many Empyreans could only watch. They were unable to do anything nor did they dare to do anything. All they could do was fervently hope that there would be no battle.

If the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was truly pushed to the edge then he would detonate Famine’s body. If so, then all the Empyreans here would perish in the aftermath!

……..

Within the endless darkness, two shadows faced each other. One was Astral Vault God King and the other was the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

Within the void, Astral Vault God King’s form was incomparably massive, like a structure formed from metal. He was completely without hair, not even eyelashes. His skull resembled polished crystal, translucent enough that one could faintly see his brain within. His appearance was extremely unique.

“Good Fortune!”

Astral Vault God King’s voice was as cold as metal as it filled the space distortion. “How did you end up like this? Weren’t you always a skilled one? You called me and Soaring Feather here, is it to beg for help?”

Astral Vault God King’s voice had a mocking tone to it. The reason he came here was unexpectedly at the request of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign looked at Astral Vault God King, no expression on his face. He only icily said, “And Soaring Feather?”

Astral Vault God King raised his right hand and twiddled a feather between his fingers. He lazily said, “She didn’t feel the need to come and see you herself, but if we speak she will naturally be able to hear us.”

“Is that so… I see.” Soaring Feather didn’t accept his invitation but the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign didn’t care. In the seven Heavens of the saint race, the truth was that there were three True Divinities.

Soaring Feather God King was the only woman amongst them and her whereabouts were always a mystery. She had gone into seclusion long ago and many peak Empyreans didn’t even know that there was such a True Divinity amongst the saints.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign looked at Astral Vault God King and unhurriedly said, “The reason I called you here today is because I want you, as well as Soaring Feather, to lead the armies to trample over the Divine Realm and exterminate humanity!”

Although the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was injured, his voice was filled with energy that shook the void.

Astral Vault God King’s eyes widened for a moment. Then, he began laughing. “Hahahaha! Did I hear wrongly? You want me and Soaring Feather to exterminate humanity? Why? You don’t need to mention something as mundane as the interests of our race to trick me. Although there are advantages to the saints in exterminating humanity, it’s nothing at all to me. Did you think I wouldn’t know that the reason you want to exterminate humanity is to accomplish your own goals? Why would Soaring Feather and I deign to help you?”

Astral Vault God King aggressively said. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign fell silent. Then, he stretched out his hands. Above his palm, a black bead traced with red lines slowly revolved – this was the Grandmist Spirit Bead.

Seeing the Grandmist Spirit Bead, Astral Vault God King’s eyes began to shine. This Spirit Bead was inestimably valuable to a body transformation system martial artist!

“You…”

“If you and Soaring Feather assist me then I will lend you this bead for one million years! But I have a requirement: when you destroy humanity, you must make sure you kill Lin Ming!”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s voice was filled with killing intent. The reason he had hurriedly summoned the other two True Divinities of the saint race here to have them attack the Divine Realm was because he had a deep foreboding feeling in his heart.

He felt that Lin Ming had brought something important back to humanity. If he couldn’t eliminate humanity here then the troubles would never end. Once the wildfires burnt down the fields, the new grass would grow once more.

In particular Lin Ming! His continued existence filled the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign with unease.

He was an unknown factor. At the mere peak Holy Lord realm he was able to have such a great impact on the war of the saints against the human race and ancient races. If he was allowed to grow up then he would certainly become a scourge upon the saints.

Before this, he had taken Lin Ming lightly because of his cultivation. Now he was willing to do anything within his power to kill him!

“Grandmist Spirit Bead…”

As the Astral Vault God King looked at this red and black bead, his eyes revealed a deep greed.

“What about it? Do you want to take it forever?” The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign coldly sneered but didn’t take away the Grandmist Spirit Bead. He only glared at Astral Vault God King, saying, “You want to work together with Soaring Feather to take my life while I am injured and steal away the Grandmist Spirit Bead?”

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign laid bare the thoughts within Astral Vault God King’s heart. Astral Vault God King only lightly smiled, not responding.

“You can give it a try! But I have ways to make you regret it!”

As the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign spoke, the massive body of Famine began to wriggle underneath him, causing innumerable fountains of blood to gush out.

Astral Vault God King’s pupils narrowed. He looked at the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, suspicion growing in his heart.

He didn’t know what hidden cards the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had, but he was certain that there must be some secret on him.

He even suspected that this concerned the abyssals.

In any case, even if he joined together with Soaring Feather to attack the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, he didn’t have full confidence that they would win. This was a purely instinctual feeling.

To reach the cultivation of the True Divinity realm, that meant one’s destiny had accumulated to the peak. Like this, a martial artist would be able to develop vague premonitions in their hearts. Although it wasn’t accurate every time, it was extremely valuable for reference.

The Samsara of Life and Death

Chapter 1925 – World Annihilation Crisis

Four months later, Mount Potala –

This was the most glorious and oldest Empyrean Holy Land in the current history of humanity. Within Mount Potala, one could deeply feel the inside story of this land. The houses, the winding corridors, the paintings, and even the tiles; everything was deeply marked by history.

3.6 billion years ago, the True Divinity leader of humanity, Divine Seal, had died. Most Empyreans had died in the battle and their Empyrean influences were destroyed with them, forever fading away into the sands of time.

However, Mount Potala had remained fully intact. Within their library pavilions they collected numerous ancient texts on martial arts. All of this played a vital role in the continued development of humanity’s martial arts civilization.

At this time, when humanity teetered on the edge of extinction, the many rulers and elites of humanity gathered once more at Mount Potala to face the upcoming storm.

Within Mount Potala, in a secret chamber of a buddhist temple.

This chamber was extremely peaceful. Wafts of incense smoke curled through the air. The walls were decorated with sculptures of towering golden arhats. Between these arhats, eight thick columns supported the ceiling. Each column was carved with a golden dragon that emitted a magnificent atmosphere.

These were the infamous eight celestial dragon columns of Mount Potala. This chamber was one of Mount Potala’s treasures, where eminent monks would come to calmly meditate. Now, Lin Ming was sitting on a cushion within this chamber.

In front of him was an old man in plain and humble clothing.

This old man’s face was withered and his eye sockets were deeply inset. His skin was dark and gray and there was only a light smattering of hair atop his head. His hair was not silver or white, but dry and yellow, like dying grass. As he sat in front of Lin Ming, his entire body brimmed with a faint death energy, as if he were already dead.

“Lin Ming… I’ve taught you everything I can… this is the entirety of my life’s secret techniques… I hope that it will be useful to you…”

The old man slowly spoke. This old man was Dragon Fang’s honorable master – Three Lives Old Man.

Out of all the Empyreans of humanity, Three Lives Old Man was unique and unconventional. Although he hadn’t been able to break into True Divinity, he had still managed to use all sorts of arcane techniques to live for 300 million years. He had experienced an incredible span of time and could be called a living history book of the human race.

When Lin Ming returned to the Divine Realm, Divine Dream had convened all peak young elites of the Divine Realm, including Jun Bluemoon, Hang Chi, Dragon Fang, and Xiao Moxian, and began their training.

In this training they were allowed to freely choose from all the secret techniques of human Empyreans – without any hidden at all!

Whatever they wanted to learn they could learn. In particular, Lin Ming was looked after and taken as a priority by all the Empyreans. A revered Empyrean didn’t hesitate to consume his own cultivation to help Lin Ming straighten his meridians and eliminate the small problems that had accumulated from Lin Ming developing his foundation so quickly.

But as for the Empyrean technique that Lin Ming finally chose, it was… Three Lives Pupils!

This was also the only secret technique he chose.

The other transcendent divine mights were indeed fierce, but to Lin Ming who studied the Asura Heavenly Dao, they weren’t too valuable. Only the Three Lives Pupils would be useful to him. It was an auxiliary technique that could be used to directly increase Lin Ming’s combat prowess. Lin Ming would be able to fuse it with his own daevic eye so that they mutually complemented each other. It was as if this secret technique was tailor-made for Lin Ming all along.

On the thick cushion, Three Lives Old Man’s eyes were still closed. “You have opened the Daevic Eye Dao Palace and that has made you even more suitable to inherit my secret technique than Dragon Fang. I have barely been managing to maintain a sad existence for 300 million years, and for me to have a direct descendant in Dragon Fang and a half descendant in you, I am glad I can see my own inheritances carried forwards in such a wondrous manner. When I die I can do so in peace…”

As Three Lives Old Man spoke, Lin Ming deeply bowed. He solemnly said, “I thank Senior for the kindness of your guidance.”

Three Lives Old Man shook his head. He quietly said, “I should be the one thanking you, and perhaps all of humanity should thank you…”

With Lin Ming’s return, not only did he bring back the method to salvation for the human race, but he even brought back a jade slip copy of the Holy Scripture’s golden pages.

These golden page duplicates came from Sheng Mei. As a Beyond Divinity level cultivation method, even a duplicate was able to provide a tremendous inspiration to human Empyreans.

This was especially true for Divine Dream, who cultivated energy and divine. The profound comprehensions of the soul contained within the golden pages were perfectly suited to her!

So for these past days, Empyrean Divine Dream had gone into seclusion as she studied the golden pages thoroughly. In these short several months she had obtained incalculable inspirations. This was all in order to establish as solid a foundation as she could so she could step into the realm of True Divinity as soon as possible.

Gradually, the early steps in the evacuation work for humanity had been completed. The evacuation from the Divine Realm was occurring a step at a time!

Those that could leave were the elites of humanity.

“Brother Lin, take this cup of wine!”

A young man handed him a cup of wine. There was a little bit of emotion on his face as well as a little bit of disappointment in himself. This person was White King, a direct disciple of the Vast Universe Holy Lands. He didn’t have some life and death friendship with Lin Ming; they were only acquaintances that had met at the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting and could be considered ordinary friends.

But due to the invasion of the saints, and in a situation where humanity could perish at any moment, even two strangers of the same race could be like brothers…

When parting approaching, the heart was always stirred. Lin Ming drank the wine.

“Brother Lin, you aren’t going?”

Lin Ming shook his head, “I’m not in a hurry…”

Lin Ming traced his spatial ring. This spatial ring contained the third emperor jade of fate. He wanted to go to the Asura Road and enter the seventh level of the final trial so he could obtain the highest completion percentage possible.

Using this, he wanted to struggle for an opportunity to turn the tides of war against the saints!

But currently, the final trial had yet to open…

White King walked away, leaving with the other elites of Vast Universe Heavenly Palace. Elites from other Empyrean influences joined them. What awaited them was a journey into an unknown and wild universe. This would be an adventure filled with hardship and slaughter.

Lin Ming knew that White King was only part of the first group of people to leave. There would be a second group, third group, fourth group…

This would continue until all the elites had left, until all the Empyrean Heavenly Palaces became deserted lands.

Partings occurred everywhere.

Masters sent off their disciples, sect masters sent off their disciples…

Some people drank and bid farewell. Some hugged as tightly as they could.

For those who were left behind, those that were leaving were family members, friends, comrades in arms…

For those that were leaving, they would leave the universe they grew up in, their most beloved homeland, the land of their ancestors, their bloodline, the happiness and laughter, their pain and sorrow…

Lin Ming deeply sighed. He turned and left, no longer participating in these sad partings.

He had too many matters to attend to. Every breath of time, every hour, was extremely precious to him.

Time passed a day at a time. With every period of time, another group of people left. Lin Ming had no idea how many people had departed, but at this time, the situation suddenly changed!

A panic-stricken World King rushed into Mount Potala. He brought with him terrible news – the saints had begun their full invasion of the Divine Realm!

Many people were stunned. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had clearly been grievously wounded by Lin Ming and the ancient races, so how could he have recovered so quickly?

And if the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign wasn’t leading the troops, then if the saint armies were to invade the Divine Realm they were bound to suffer serious casualties!

“How is this possible?!”

Empyrean Vast Universe was completely shocked. Deep in his heart he didn’t want to believe such terrifying news. He hoped there had been some sort of mistake!

But following that, the bloodied and almost disabled World King was escorted away and another piece of news was brought in. That was… the human Empyreans guarding the great worlds closest to the saints had all died in battle!

The saints had truly begun their invasion!

Moreover, the scale of this invasion was even greater than the invasion of the Primeval Universe. After all, the Divine Realm battlefield was far broader and every army could be utilized to their limits!

At this time, humanity also learned that there was a True Divinity leading the invasion of the saints. His name was… Astral Vault God King!

Nobody had heard this name before, but just his status as a True Divinity was enough to cause all Empyreans present to feel a heavy pressure!

A great saint army led by a True Divinity, this was simply impossible to contend with!

“So it is another True Divinity of the saints that is leading their armies… the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign is really recovering from his wounds…” Empyrean Divine Dream sighed as she obtained the news. Even though Astral Vault God King was weaker than the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, he still wasn’t something they could deal with.

Astral Vault God King had assembled the armies of the saint race and then took over military control for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. All of this had been done in a mere several months, but at this time, only half of humanity’s elites had been evacuated!

“Summon an emergency meeting!”

This meeting was convened hastily, but all human Empyreans, including some human elites that had yet to evacuate, rapidly arrived.

Humanity now ushered in the greatest crisis they had faced in history!

Chapter 1926 – Feather

From the moment the meeting was convened, the atmosphere was somber and dignified.

In the Divine Realm there were still many human elites who had yet to be gathered. If the Empyreans were to collectively evacuate the Divine Realm at this time then those elites remaining as well as their descendants would be slaughtered!

“We must speed up the evacuation…”

An Empyrean suggested. In truth, the so-called ‘speeding up’ of the evacuation was simply raising the threshold. They would only bring the most outstanding inheritances and geniuses. Ordinary geniuses would be left behind to fight for themselves.

“That doesn’t make sense… there are some peak talents in the innermost depths of the Divine Realm, even in some medium and small worlds. They are too far away for us to reach. Even if we raised the threshold they still wouldn’t be able to catch up in time.”

Another Empyrean argued. Concerning the invasion of the saints, everyone had their own opinions.

But during this time, Divine Dream remained silent.

A considerable number of people looked towards Divine Dream, waiting for her to express her intentions. By this time Divine Dream had long become the true and unanimous leader of humanity.

It could be said that every decision she made concerned the future of the human race.

At this time, Divine Dream’s expression was earnest but her breathing wasn’t uneven at all. She was as composed and tranquil as a placid lake.

She opened her mouth. Her voice was slow and unhurried, but each syllable she spoke was filled with a potent power.

“We will meet them head-on!”

“What!?”

Empyrean Divine Dream’s words shocked all the Empyreans and young elites present.

Meet the saints head-on?

The saints had a True Divinity powerhouse leading their armies to war – wasn’t fighting them the same as fighting a hopeless battle?

“How can we possibly do that?”

A red-robed Empyrean stood up to oppose.

“I didn’t say that we must win… the Divine Realm is the homeland of humanity and we are the protectors of the human race as well as gods to countless trillions of quadrillions of lives. Just because the saints have invaded doesn’t mean we can abandon all our subjects like this. Even if it is for the future of humanity, I cannot accept such an excuse. There must be some people staying behind in order to stand responsible for humanity…

“Moreover, we have to fight because we must delay for more time to evacuate. Half of the elites still haven’t evacuated and we will not discard them.”

As Divine Dream spoke to here she stood up. “I will remain… and meet the saints myself. Among you all, those who voluntarily choose to stay behind may do so. The others will leave the Divine Realm and go to the wild universe!”

As Divine Dream spoke many people were panic-stricken. Divine Dream wanted to stay in the Divine Realm?

No! Absolutely not!

This was because to the current human race, Divine Dream’s role was even more important than Lin Ming’s!

Whether it was fighting their way into the wilds of the 33 Heavens or returning to the Divine Realm in the future, none of this could be done without Divine Dream!

At this time, Three Lives Old Man stood up and slowly shook his head. “Divine Dream… It’s enough that I stay behind. I do not have much time remaining and for me to go to the wild universe is just a waste. I have already decided to stay in the Divine Realm and leave behind a lasting memory for the saints.”

Although Three Lives Old Man seemed on the verge of death, he was still an existence that had lived for 300 million years. No one dared to underestimate him nor did anyone know what cards he had hidden up his sleeves.

In particular, during the war against the saints, Three Lives Old Man had long since decided to martyr himself. A desperate and reckless peak Empyrean was a force that even a True Divinity couldn’t ignore.

After Three Lives Old Man spoke, another Empyrean stood up. “Although my human race has declined, our pride hasn’t. Even if we are to be defeated we will be defeated with dignity. I will also stay behind.”

“I… will also remain!”

Another old Empyrean stood up.

Without exception, all of these Empyreans were in the waning years of their lives; their cultivations had already started to drop.

The future of humanity belonged to the young.

Going to the wild universe was the same as beginning from zero. These old Empyreans didn’t have that much time to wait.

One after another, elderly Empyreans stood up and decided to stay behind.

Even old Empyreans of the ancient races planned to stay in the Divine Realm. Only Empyreans in their prime like Diwuhen and To Bagui would go to the wild universe and help develop the land there. These Empyreans were the hope of the ancient races.

At the same time, these old Empyreans also wanted to stop Empyrean Divine Dream. No matter what, she couldn’t be allowed to stay in the Divine Realm to die; that would be far too great a loss. Humanity still needed her leadership.

Divine Dream shook her head. “I am staying behind but not to die. I am confident that I can survive and eventually leave. And the other Empyreans that stay behind don’t necessarily need to sacrifice themselves…”

Divine Dream’s words left the other Empyreans shocked.

She was planning on leading the human Empyreans to resist a True Divinity, yet she still had the means to withdraw?

“If it is the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign then my chances are much slimmer. But, the other True Divinities aren’t necessarily invincible. Don’t forget, we have the Ark of Hope!”

Divine Dream added.

With the Ark of Hope, escape was indeed a possibility!

At this time, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred.

Just as he was about to speak, Divine Dream looked straight towards him and directly shot down whatever plan he was going to propose. “Do not even mention it, you must leave! Moreover, you must leave now!”

“I…” Lin Ming originally wanted to say that the Ark of Hope could display the strongest might in his hands, but Divine Dream was firm in her decision.

“Lin Ming, as long as you live then you will be the greatest threat to the saints. In this battle to delay for time, you are not needed. Rather, your appearance will cause the saints to try and kill you no matter what price they have to pay, causing the exact opposite of the effect that we want.”

Divine Dream’s words were approved by the many Empyreans present. Lin Ming had to leave. Staying was not worth the cost.

Lin Ming agreed.

After Divine Dream made her decision, the meeting ended.

The Ark of Hope remained at Mount Potala. Lin Ming and other young elites were led to the back mountains of Mount Potala by some younger Empyreans. Here, there was a crowd of spirit ships, spirit boats, and divine palaces. There were even soaring spirit birds and other mounts.

After a short period of time, Lin Ming and the others would board a spirit ship and travel to the wild universe.

Many people hugged and gave their farewells.

“Hey boy, the human race is going to depend on you. When you go to the wild universe make sure you slaughter your way until you shake up the world!”

Vast Universe lightly punched Lin Ming’s chest. Lin Ming was a young elite who had emerged from the First Martial Meeting that was managed by Vast Universe and Divine Dream; he could be called a part of their lineage.

Lin Ming had all sorts of feelings running through his mind. He didn’t speak, only nodding and deeply bowing to Empyrean Vast Universe.

Empyrean Vast Universe didn’t leave; he chose to remain with Divine Dream.

He was Divine Dream’s old comrade-in-arms as well as an old friend. He was also in his prime, but he steadfastly chose to remain because he believed in Divine Dream and because he also believed in himself.

He didn’t intend to die in battle, but he did want to fight for a little bit more time for humanity.

Only like this could he give an answer to the countless human lives of the Divine Realm.

This parting could be called a parting of life and death.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and stepped onto the spirit ship, not turning back to look.

But as Lin Ming stepped onto the spirit ship, there was something that occurred which no one noticed. A spirit bird flying in the skies came to a halt above the spirit ship. It spun around, and then a single feather fell off this bird, slowly fluttering downwards.

This feather was common and indistinguishable from an ordinary feather. But as it fell atop the spirit ship, it slowly stuck to the surface and then melted into the hull, vanishing from sight…

Chapter 1927 – Parting

The infinite universe, the vast and boundless space –

A massive spirit ship quietly sped through the starry space.

This spirit ship was named ‘Epoch’. The name signified humanity’s wish to usher in a new epoch, one where their people would rise to glory once more.

During this trip, Epoch would have to pass through over a dozen great worlds of the Divine Realm before finally arriving at a small world called the Bluesnow Realm.

This small world was hidden within a chaotic ocean of stars. Without accurate coordinates and a guide, it was basically impossible to find this land.

The end of the Bluesnow Realm pushed up against the God Lamenting Wall. And behind this God Lamenting Wall was another universe of the 33 Heavens – a wild universe.

Because the God Lamenting Wall separating the wild universes had never weakened, this universe hadn’t had an intelligent humanoid life form step foot in it for a long time.

Several months ago, 20 human Empyreans were sent to the Bluesnow Realm in order to join together and form a connection through the God Lamenting Wall using the Asura Decree and then maintain it.

Following that, the elites of humanity passed through this connection and entered the wild universe. They quickly sped towards the nearest lands, establishing their own bases to develop the area…

Epoch was an Empyrean level spirit treasure spirit ship. It was naturally far slower than the Ark of Hope, and from start to finish, it would require two months to reach its destination.

And during this long travel, many matters occurred. For instance, the great war between the remaining Empyreans and the saints…

In a grand hall within Epoch, many young elites had gathered.

Dragon Fang, Hang Chi, Xiao Moxian, Jun Bluemoon, Lin Ming, and even the celestial Smokeless…

These young elites had reunited once again.

Back during the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, these young elites had been 20-40 years of age. They were high-spirited back then, looking to climb to the highest mountaintops.

They showed their abilities above the arena stage. They attracted the attention of the cosmos and became renowned to trillions of quadrillions of people. That was an incomparably magnificent time!

And after 100 years of life, they reunited once more. Although they each made considerable progress in their strengths, they actually gathered under such circumstances. Facing the great calamity of the Divine Realm they had been forced to flee from their homeland and become fugitives…

At this time, Xiao Moxian was looking out a porthole, gazing upon the endless starry skies. She rubbed her belly. It was unknown just what she was thinking.

To abandon her homeland and go to an unknown world, it was inevitable that she would feel a deep melancholy in her heart.

But, what she could rejoice in was that Lin Ming would always be there at her side to accompany her.

She silently looked at Lin Ming as he meditated in the grand hall. Xiao Moxian pursed her lips. In this great calamity, Lin Ming had become nearly her everything.

“I wonder how the seniors of my people and Empyrean Divine Dream are doing right now…”

Smokeless whispered, finding it hard to calm her heart.

Beside her, Hang Chi was praying sutras and twisting the buddha beads in his hands, deep in meditation.

Dragon Fang embraced his black sword. He had a pot of wine in his hand and was quietly drinking from it.

At some time, Dragon Fang filled a cup of wine. Then he silently raised it up in the air and slowly sprinkled it to the ground.

Seeing this, Lin Ming sighed. He knew that Dragon Fang was giving his farewells to his master…

In this bitter battle between the humans and saints, Divine Dream, Vast Universe, and some others might be able to return safely. But the older Empyreans had already entered the fray with the determination to die…

Lin Ming stood up and walked over to Dragon Fang. He joined him in drinking a cup of wine.

But at this time, his mind shivered and he nearly fell over.

“Big Brother Lin! What’s happening?”

Xiao Moxian had been looking at Lin Ming and his sudden reaction had left her startled. With his cultivation it was impossible that he would nearly tumble over for no reason at all.

“Lin Ming!”

The others stood up, all of them looking at Lin Ming with concern. Now was an extremely tense time. Even if they were fleeing to a relatively safe universe, all of them were on guard for any abnormalities. Lin Ming’s sudden change left them wary.

“I’m fine…” Lin Ming waved his hand, his complexion somewhat ill.

Just now, he had clearly felt an indescribable divine sense sweep through this hall, nearly causing his mind to fall to illusion. During this time his mind had completely blanked out, and he felt as if a feather had fallen into his spiritual sea, slowly immersing within it.

This feather was simple like an ordinary father, but this ordinariness was what scared Lin Ming.

This was the wisp of someone’s divine sense mark! He had been locked onto by someone!

And, what stunned Lin Ming the most was that no one else had detected it. If he was the only one who had sensed it then that meant this divine sense was most likely aimed at a single person!

This thought left Lin Ming’s palms cold with sweat. Not to mention the terrifying intensity of that divine sense, there was also the fact that this other party’s divine sense had quietly penetrated through the protective wards of Epoch without alarming the many peak Empyreans on board.

This was not something an Empyrean could accomplish.

This other party…

True Divinity!?

In that moment, Lin Ming felt as if he had fallen into a sea of ice. He had been locked onto by a True Divinity!?

This was incomparably horrifying information!

Without the peak masters of the Divine Realm like Divine Dream present, there was no one on this entire spirit ship capable of contending with a True Divinity!

Moreover, even the Ark of Hope wasn’t here. They didn’t even have the Asura Decrees that could wound a True Divinity…

In this situation, to be locked onto by a True Divinity was the same as being sentenced to death!

“Is it intentionally targeting me… or was it an unconscious probing…”

Lin Ming’s limbs were icy cold. He didn’t believe that there was a True Divinity randomly passing by, just happening to use their divine sense to investigate this spirit ship…

With a 99% certainty, this other party had come for him!

“Big Brother Lin, just what is going on!?”

Xiao Moxian anxiously looked at Lin Ming, worry filling her face.

“Benefactor Lin, what happened just now? At this time there is no need to hide anything from us. We must all be on the same boat. All these difficulties can be solved together. If we cannot solve them, then there are also the Empyreans here that can help.”

Hang Chi slowly said. Lin Ming bitterly sighed in his heart. This was something that not even an Empyrean could fix…

“I’m fine. I just felt an intense foreboding premonition, as if something unfortunate is going to occur.”

Lin Ming eventually didn’t speak the truth. This was because he wasn’t absolutely sure, and also because there was no meaning in saying it anyways. Instead, it would cause Xiao Moxian and the others to panic for no good reason. At this moment, no one here could stop a True Divinity.

It would be the same as telling everyone that he was going to die.

Moreover, the worst thing was that once this True Divinity overtook Epoch, everyone in this spirit ship would be buried along with him!

Lin Ming’s words left everyone half-doubting and half-believing him. Indeed, once a martial artist’s destiny accumulated to a certain level, they could indeed have strange premonitions which could allow them to avoid disasters.

Lin Ming’s unlucky premonition just now… could there have been some problem at the front lines?

Did Empyrean Divine Dream encounter an accident?

Gloomy clouds formed over everyone’s hearts. Divine Dream was the spiritual pillar of humanity. If she perished, not to mention the loss in strength it would mean for the human race, but the morale of the people would fall through the ground.

Finally, the group quieted down. During this time Lin Ming gripped his fists, his heart and mind on pins and needles, filled with unease.

That terrifying sense was like the summons of a death god. Would it come again?

Lin Ming thought. And indeed, after a quarter hour, that terrifying sense covered Lin Ming!

This time, the sense was extremely light, like a feather gently crossing over Lin Ming’s mind. But the resulting pressure nearly caused his spiritual sea to fall into chaos.

Moreover, this sense brought with it a faint and clear… killing intent!!

As delicate as a feather, a killing intent that left one drowning in desperation!

A True Divinity had truly locked onto him!

This feather was the mark of a True Divinity. Back in the Soul World’s Akashic Dream Universe, the Great Brahmic God King had used a similar method to mark Lin Ming.

This was a transcendent secret technique. When a person left behind blood, skin, hair, or even items they used before, these things would be marked with their ‘vital characteristics’. Then, by paying a sufficient price and using a certain amount of soul force, one could search the vast cosmos for these ‘vital characteristics’ and mark the position of the person.

In the past, the Great Brahmic God King hadn’t searched too large an area. It was normal for Lin Ming to be found by him.

But this time, the other party was able to search the entire Divine Realm with its 3000 great worlds and countless other smaller worlds to find and lock onto Lin Ming all the same!

Such supernatural powers left Lin Ming drowning in despair!

“Heavens, do you really wish for my end? I have resolved myself to climb to the peak of martial arts, yet I must perish here?”

Lin Ming mirthlessly smiled. The saints really thought highly of him. If he wasn’t wrong then the saints had especially sent a True Divinity to hunt him down and kill him.

Currently he didn’t even have the strength to fight an Empyrean, but now the enemy had sent a True Divinity to kill him. They had truly laid down the capital!

They wanted to take advantage of the time before he had grown to erase him from existence, forever severing any future troubles!

Lin Ming stood up in an absent-minded daze.

From when he had stepped upon his road of martial arts until now, he had faced death numerous times. But, never before had he felt despair like today!

“Lin Ming, you…”

Smokeless, Hang Chi, Jun Bluemoon, and the others all looked at Lin Ming. They felt that something was wrong.

“What is going on? What are you trying to hide?”

“Nothing.” Lin Ming suddenly smiled, his smile somewhat sad. “I’m sorry, I… don’t think I can go to the wild universe with you all and open up a new world…”

“What!?”

Lin Ming’s few words left everyone shocked. In particular, Xiao Moxian felt her heart shrink.

“Why!?”

Tears began to appear at the corners of Xiao Moxian’s eyes. She bit her lips and stared at Lin Ming, her voice shaking.

Lin Ming looked at Xiao Moxian, his heart mourning. He couldn’t remain on this spirit ship because it would only mean everyone here dying in vain. Even humanity’s gathering point would be exposed.

He wanted to say that he had been locked onto by a True Divinity, but as he saw Xiao Moxian’s teary eyes he couldn’t bring himself to say the words…

He didn’t want his last image of Xiao Moxian before he left to be that of her dying inside.

Moreover, he knew that if he said such words, if Xiao Moxian knew he would die without a doubt, she would not let him leave alone. She would die with him.

Finally, Lin Ming said, “There are some matters I must attend to. I will be leaving first…”

Hearing Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian’s response was to quickly rush over and throw herself into his arms. She tightly grasped him as if letting go would mean losing him forever.

“Take me with you.”

Xiao Moxian had already made up her mind to never let go. She had a faint premonition in her mind that after this parting, she would not see Lin Ming again.

Lin Ming could feel Xiao Moxian gently trembling in his arms and her vulnerable heart. He didn’t know just what taste was in his heart, but eventually he pushed her away. His expression was resolute as he said, “Stop this nonsense. Not only will you not be able to help me but you will only drag me down. If so then I will die for sure!”

Lin Ming’s heartless words and his heartless expression left Xiao Moxian stunned.

The other young elites were also helpless to do anything, but they knew something had happened with Lin Ming.

It was just that he wasn’t willing to tell them.

“If you go like this, the Empyreans on board will not agree.”

Jun Bluemoon frowned. Although he didn’t know what was happening, he could faintly feel that the reason Lin Ming left was for the lives of everyone on board.

“At these times, none of us fear death. What happened?” Dragon Fang stated in a manner more direct than the others. He pulled out his sword.

“I will explain myself to the guiding Empyreans. If I leave, there is still a chance to live. If I stay, I will die.”

Lin Ming turned around after he spoke. To leave the spirit ship he needed to inform the Empyreans in the main control room so that they could open the doors.

At this time, Xiao Moxian held onto Lin Ming once more.

“Big Brother Lin…” Xiao Moxian seemed to exhaust all of her strength as she grabbed Lin Ming’s hand. Her tone was nearly that of begging.

“Do you remember the Monster Emperor’s grand longevity feast where the Good Fortune Saint Son came to propose marriage to me, but you defeated him and married me instead?

“The you of the longevity feast was strong, aggressive, unstoppable. Numerous rulers of the universe were suppressed by you. And that was also the happiest day of my life.

“I have given up my race, abandoned my grandfather, and chosen to follow you to the wild universe. Even so, I have never regretted my decisions, not once, because no matter what I still have you… but… do you want me to lose even you?”

Xiao Moxian’s words were like a knife that thrust into Lin Ming’s heart.

Lin Ming’s body shook. His heart hurt so much he couldn’t even take a breath. He turned to Xiao Moxian to see her crying.

Finally, he held onto her.

He leaned down to her ears and said in a gentle voice, “Look after our child. It… is the continuation of my life…”

Lin Ming no longer tarried. He stepped away, leaving behind the mourning and shaking Xiao Moxian.

She helplessly collapsed against a wall, staring at Lin Ming’s back as he vanished into the corridors of the ship…

…….

The hatch leading out of Epoch opened.

A frail figure silently departed from the spirit ship, heading deep into space.

Lin Ming didn’t conceal anything from the Empyreans leading the ship and explained everything he could.

Although everyone was willing to join Lin Ming in blood-filled battle, senselessly sacrificing everyone was meaningless. Moreover, those onboard Epoch were the future hopes of humanity…

Like this, Lin Ming left.

In the infinite cosmos, Lin Ming’s form appeared more and more lonely…

“Life, really is small…”

Lin Ming looked at the endless space around him. This world would exist for dozens of billions of years or even trillions of years.

Compared to the universe, his life was only a short moment.

Even all those once peerless rulers of history had disappeared by now, turned to dust.

Years from now, would he also be nothing but a grain of dust?

Chapter 1929A – A Beautiful Trap

Within the void, a terrifying storm brewed. Lin Ming felt countless sharp knives cut into his body as a web of pain radiated throughout him.

At this time, Lin Ming could already confirm that there was a problem with the Asura Command as he used it to transmit him to the Asura Road!

Perhaps it was because he had poured too much strength in or perhaps it was because of some inexplicable relationship with the three emperor jades he had gathered, but in short, this transmission space channel was completely different from what he had experienced in the past.

The last time he had entered the Asura Road, the space storm then wasn’t even a tenth as intense as it was now.

If a martial artist weaker than himself was sucked into this space storm they would have already become ground meat.

Peng!

With a solid thumping sound, Lin Ming felt as if he had struck something hard, nearly fainting in the process.

In the next moment, a cool breeze passed over his skin. He opened his eyes and saw that he was in a bleak and desolate gray world.

Gloomy clouds floated high in the skies and the light here was dim.

Scattered rocks covered the ground. These rocks were all of similar size and shape and they also looked somewhat familiar. As Lin Ming looked closer, he could see that they weren’t rocks but shattered stone tablets.

The writings on the stone tablets had long worn away and were incomparably strange.

As Lin Ming stepped through this desolate land, he felt as if his entire being was fiercely suppressed.

Where was he?

Lin Ming had no idea where he could be. He spread out his divine sense but couldn’t find the edges of this world.

He took out the Asura Command and looked at it. Then, he sucked in a light breath of air.

That plain-looking Asura Command had cracked in half; it was unable to be used again.

What had happened?

An absurd feeling appeared in Lin Ming’s mind, as if the world he was in was the true world and everything he had experienced before had been nothing but an illusion.

From the examination of the Seven Profound Martial House, the great tournament of the Seven Profound Valleys, his arrival at the Holy Demon Continent, the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, the invasion of the saints, it was like all of that had been nothing but a dream…

These sorts of bewildering thoughts left Lin Ming flustered.

But at this time, Lin Ming’s mind shook. He felt a weak sense gently and swiftly pass over him before vanishing.

This was… Soaring Feather God King’s divine sense!

Such a real and deadly killing intent caused Lin Ming to calm down. The strange dream-like feeling of before also disappeared.

Composing himself, Lin Ming looked within himself and saw that the True Divinity mark that Soaring Feather God King left within him was still there. He could even feel the spiritual connection between him and Soaring Feather God King, with the exception that this connection was much weaker than before.

As if he and Soaring Feather God King were in two different worlds.

Perhaps after another period of time, she would find him…

Thinking of this, Lin Ming wryly smiled.

He didn’t know how much time he had left to live.

If there was some accident with the transmission, then was this still the Asura Road? If so, where was it in the Asura Road?

Could it be that this was… deep within the Great Desolate?

Lin Ming thought of the Great Desolate in the Asura Road. It was said to be a natural wall that existed between the inner Asura Road and outer Asura Road.

Rumors said that the Asura Road’s Great Desolate was endless and not even a peak Empyrean dared to enter its depths. However, as to what was within those depths, that remained a riddle.

Even so, perhaps even the depths of the Great Desolate couldn’t stop a True Divinity.

In this universe there didn’t seem to be anything that could block the path of a True Divinity. Even the God Lamenting Wall could be broken through if a True Divinity paid a great price…

Soaring Feather God King’s mark hadn’t weakened at all. In this completely strange and unknown world, Lin Ming had no idea what he could do.

He began to aimlessly search through this world, hoping to discover some favorable turn.

However, this seemed to be an endlessly barren world. There wasn’t even a strand of grass or a little bug.

In this boundless world, Lin Ming walked alone. Weak light fell down from above, casting long shadows on the ground.

His tiny figure appeared increasingly desolate on this gloomy world.

In that moment, Lin Ming truly felt an unprecedented solitude.

He suddenly missed Xiao Moxian, missed his own child, missed Mu Qianyu, missed Qin Xingxuan, missed his parents.

He walked forwards. The True Divinity mark that Soaring Feather God King left on him was like a life-sucking curse. From time to time it was strong, from time to time it weakened, but it never left him.

Lin Ming didn’t know just what was occurring outside. Did Empyrean Divine Dream manage to escape? Did Xiao Moxian and his child arrive in the wild universe safely?

In a different universe, would his wives and his child live well?

Humanity, was there still a chance for them to rise from the dirt?

Towards all of this, Lin Ming’s mind was filled with worries.

He had always been strong of will. For the past 150 some years, even in his most difficult times and even when he suffered the most, he had never given up.

He deeply loved life. He yearned to reach the peak of martial arts.

He blazed a path forwards, without fear. He fought for his family, friends, and for himself. He didn’t know how many rivals he had forced down, how many times he had turned the tides!

Xuan Wuji, Yang Yun, Tian Mingzi, Good Fortune Saint Son, powerful enemies were out-strategized by Lin Ming or overwhelmed by him. One after another, they suffered defeat beneath Lin Ming’s hands…

In Lin Ming’s life, he had rarely been defeated!

He had never been as lost and confused as he was today.

Perhaps no matter how strong a person was, they also had their fragile side.

No matter how outstanding a person was, there would always be a day when they fell into distress…

Lin Ming continued walking, walking, and walking. He discovered that this bleak world had no origin energy, and energy was even being drawn out from his own body.

He didn’t know how many days he walked for. Because energy was continuously absorbed by the surrounding wilderness, he felt exhausted.

This world was extremely strange!

He even seemed like a mortal, hunger and thirst pressing him from all sides.

He knew that this was the result of his energy being exhausted, otherwise he simply wouldn’t need food and water.

He sat down on a stone tablet. This stone tablet was cold and pieces of ice covered it.

He broke off a piece of ice and placed it in his mouth.

The melted ice brought with it the bitter taste of soil. The water moistened Lin Ming’s parched throat, causing him to feel something faintly familiar.

But at this time, on the far off horizon, Lin Ming saw someone’s shadow!

His mind shook as he saw this. He sprung up.

This person’s figure rapidly vanished. But, Lin Ming could confirm that he absolutely hadn’t misread.

Moreover, it seemed to be that of a woman!

Soaring Feather God King?

This thought passed through Lin Ming’s mind but he couldn’t confirm it.

Yet he didn’t hesitate. He headed straight towards this person’s shadow.

He didn’t wildly run nor did he fly. He walked forwards one step at a time, slowly drawing out the Black Dragon Spear.

No matter who she was, Lin Ming would face her. If it was Soaring Feather God King then he wouldn’t be able to escape anyways.

However, when he truly arrived at the horizon and saw what lay before him, he was startled.

Before him was a giant mirror that towered into the skies.

This mirror resembled the Cold Ice Mirror that Lin Ming had seen in the Asura forbidden zone. It seemed to contain an entirely different world.

The other world contained fresh flowers and trees, birds and animals. It stood in stark contrast to this bleak land.

And the surface of this mirror was the entrance to the other world.

“How come this is like the Cold Ice Mirror left behind by the Asura Road Master?”

Lin Ming wasn’t sure if this was a coincidence. He stepped through the mirror. Lush, fresh grass was thick beneath his feet and all sorts of spirit plants bloomed brightly.

A rainbow of spirit birds soared through the blue skies. Immortal apes shuttled back and forth in the verdant jungles. Bright sunlight fell from the skies, sparkling across gurgling spirit springs in bursts of auspicious light.

Lin Ming was dazed for a long time. Although the difference was only a single step, one side was a dead land and the other side was a paradise.

He had walked through the wilderness for far too long. As he stepped into this mirror world and felt the air that was thick with life, he felt as if everything that occurred was a lifetime ago.

Heaven and earth origin energy had returned. His body began to spontaneously absorb this rich heaven and earth origin energy, continuously restoring itself.

He greedily breathed in the air. He drank from the spirit springs and ate the spirit fruit until his strength was completely restored and slowly returned to its peak state.

He walked forwards. He wanted to see who this woman was.

He didn’t find a woman, but he did see a mountain.

From the top of this mountain, infinite origin energy fell down, as if it were the source of origin energy in this mirror world.

Lin Ming climbed up, slowly ascending the mountain.

At the summit of the mountain, he saw a divine tree.

Chapter 1930 – Soul Source

Sheng Mei slowly melted into Lin Ming. He drowned in her incomparably warm and soft touch.

Lin Ming gradually lost himself. This demonic fruit from the Dark Abyss contained an irresistible power. Whether it was Lin Ming or Sheng Mei, neither of them could resist it.

Soon, they each forgot their hostilities.

Like lovers who had been long separated and met once again, they were inseparable once more.

Sheng Mei’s voice began to soften. Her breathing also quickened.

She was like a cat as she bit on Lin Ming’s shoulder. Her noble and indifferent persona was completely discarded at this moment. She recklessly grasped around, tangling herself with Lin Ming.

But before this all began, she had already revolved a secret technique of the Holy Scripture to absorb Lin Ming’s Eternal Soul.

The soul was the foundation of a person.

The characteristics of the Eternal Soul were completely condensed into Lin Ming’s own soul and were closely integrated with his very being. Once it was taken away, the consequences would be unimaginable!

His life would wither and his strength would drop. Like this, let alone rising in cultivation, he simply wouldn’t have much longer to live.

But all of this didn’t occur as Sheng Mei envisioned. As Sheng Mei lost her consciousness and was under the complete control of her instincts, as she was tangled with Lin Ming, for some reason, a little bit of Lin Ming’s soul force remained within him…

Time slowly passed. The two were utterly intoxicated in each other.

Beneath the overbearing potency of that Dark Abyss fruit, not even a True Divinity could maintain their reasoning. With Lin Ming’s cultivation, he completely lost all brightness in his mind. He greedily stroked Sheng Mei’s soft body, his happiness reaching the peak.

Their souls blended together and even their inner worlds seemed to become one.

Between the two of them, they took from each other and gained from each other countless times.

Until they were both utterly exhausted.

A heavy sleepiness hit them. Like this, the two fell into a deep slumber…

………….

At some unknown time, Lin Ming felt drops of water falling on his face. The cold feeling caused him to slowly regain consciousness.

His body felt utterly weak and a splitting headache tore through him. Even taking a simple breath was incredibly difficult.

A terrifying emptiness rushed through Lin Ming. His eyes popped open, as if he had lost the most important thing in his life.

Eternal Soul!

He panicked. He quickly inspected his spiritual world and nearly suffocated on himself. In the throes of passion, his source soul force had been greedily taken by Sheng Mei. There wasn’t much left!

Even his fires of life had become extremely weak.

For a time, Lin Ming was filled with utter disconsolateness.

Because he had eaten that abyssal fruit, his mind had been blurry and he hadn’t been able to clearly feel what was happening. But now that he was fully awake, he could feel the pinnacle of pain.

The soul was the most basic foundation of a martial artist. Even for martial artists that practiced the essence gathering system and body transformation system, although they didn’t cultivate the soul, their soul source was still extremely powerful!

This was because an essence gathering system martial artist had to control the energy of the world and a body transformation system martial artist had to control their formidable God Beast-like body, and to do this they needed the soul. In other words, the support of a martial artist’s will!

In addition, if a martial artist wanted to resist a spiritual attack, they also needed their soul.

A martial artist’s source soul force was similar to their fires of life; it was the basis of a martial artist’s life. Once they lost it, that meant their life was reaching its end.

Lin Ming humorlessly smiled. He turned to see Sheng Mei standing not too far away.

At this time, Sheng Mei had already dressed herself and had even wrapped her face in a veil. Her proud calmness and indifference had returned, as if she was completely unrelated to the passionate woman from before.

Lin Ming wanted to stand up, but because of his extreme weakness he wasn’t able to move.

Lin Ming looked at Sheng Mei and Sheng Mei looked at Lin Ming. The two stared at each other, neither speaking for a long time.

The grass was cold and a mountain breeze blew past them. In this paradise surrounded by celestial mountains, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei were like a fated pair, destined to love each other and kill each other. At the summit of this mountain, gazing at one another, this scene seemed to freeze into an eternal image.

Finally, Sheng Mei spoke. She no longer looked at Lin Ming but at the world beneath the mountain.

She whispered, “Hate me…”

Lin Ming bitterly smiled. “What reason do I have to hate you? If it wasn’t for you then I would have already been killed by Soaring Feather and would be nothing but an icy cold corpse. In fact, I could even say that without you I would never have left the Soul World and would already have died to the Great Brahmic God King…

“I only hate myself. I hate how useless I am. In this great calamity, I cannot even become a small wave. Let alone the destiny of humanity, I cannot even control my own destiny… really, how laughable I am.”

Lin Ming’s voice was deeply miserable and helpless.

He was well aware that when Soaring Feather God King chased after him, the reason he had come to this strange world was because of Sheng Mei.

However, Sheng Mei didn’t have this ability. Although she was powerful she could not conceal the truth from Soaring Feather. This was likely the work of the Soul Emperor manipulating things behind the scenes!

The Soul Emperor, just what was he planning?

Lin Ming didn’t know, or perhaps it could be said that he didn’t need to know.

With the loss of his source soul force, his fires of life would begin to weaken…

With his current condition, Lin Ming had no idea how he could stop any of this.

Lin Ming struggled to sit up. He leaned against the abyssal tree behind him and looked at Sheng Mei. A sad smile crossed his lips. “I thought I wanted to go to the Primeval Universe, but were you the one purposefully leading me in that direction?”

Sheng Mei sighed, shaking her head. “I really did wish to persuade you, but you did not listen. I had no other choice. The reason I led you to the Primeval Universe was because I wanted you to leave that place, but… he already discovered you, and he already desired to obtain your Eternal Soul…”

Lin Ming naturally knew that this so-called ‘he’ was the Soul Emperor.

“Why didn’t he do so at the start? Why did he wait until I went to the Primeval Universe, struggle with everything I had, wait until the moment I exhausted myself, nearly losing all hope, before he then moved against me?”

Lin Ming angrily said. His eyes were also beginning to turn red.

He loathed his own incompetence. Everything had been controlled by the Soul Emperor all along!

He… was too weak!

“This is because… when you were at the Soul World, your Eternal Soul was not perfect.” Sheng Mei’s voice was plaintive, a hint of sorrow and frustration in her eyes. “Do you not remember? He said to you that your life had been far too smooth. Although you experienced trials and tribulations, it was still insufficient. You had yet to experience true defeat and your spiritual journey was incomplete, thus your Eternal Soul was also unstable. He couldn’t do anything to you just yet…

“So, when you left the Soul World he plotted to use the hand of the saints to force you to the edge. Your soul, in your despair, in your helplessness, began to slowly transform as you endured these hardships. It became more and more stable, and this was something not even you discovered…

“If it wasn’t for this day where I ruined you, then after experiencing all this you would definitely have made more terrifying progress, perhaps even stepping Beyond Divinity, becoming an unprecedented existence in this universe. But… no one will give you this chance. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign won’t and neither will the Soul Emperor. If you want to blame something, then blame this era in which you were born…”

Chapter 1931B – Love and Hate

In the universe, in the boundless darkness, two figures stood high in space.

These two people were wrapped in black robes. But, one was a beautiful woman and the other was an old youth.

They were Sheng Mei and the Soul Emperor.

“Are you satisfied…?”

The old youth had a taunting smile.

Sheng Mei’s expression was cold. She didn’t respond.

“I agreed with your final condition. I did not use a dreamland soul refining technique but instead allowed you to conjure up all of this. You gave the primordial yin of your seven reincarnations as well as your body and mind to him, freely offering it all to obtain his Eternal Soul. You gave Lin Ming your most precious treasures, but in the end, his judgment of you came down to nothing but a single word… whore.”

The Soul Emperor’s tone was thoughtful. Indeed, the Eternal Soul had to be voluntarily offered by Lin Ming, but in this universe, the Soul Emperor was the one with the highest attainments in the complexities of the soul and the spiritual sea. He had his own methods he could use, such as creating a dreamland and using illusions to easily deceive Lin Ming. To trick Lin Ming into offering up everything of his own will wouldn’t have been difficult at all.

“You understood all that has happened and all that you have done, but yet you still chose to pour your emotions into him and offer the primordial yin of your seven reincarnations to him… just what use is that? His soul force has been sucked dry by you… oh, there seems to be a little left, enough for him to live for another short span of time, but in the end he will die no matter what. This is just like taking your most precious treasure and tossing it into the trash. Did you do all this just to satisfy your own obsessions?”

The Soul Emperor slowly said. But at this time, Sheng Mei’s complexion had become colder than ice.

She clearly and unhurriedly said, “You… shut up!”

The Soul Emperor was stunned for a brief moment, but he still coldly sneered as before.

Sheng Mei coldly said, “Do not forget that we have an agreement. Do not force me, otherwise, I will die against you! And if I die, all your plans will come to nothing!”

A thick killing intent and hate flashed in Sheng Mei’s eyes. This killing intent left the Soul Emperor frowning, but he immediately chuckled. “It’s these eyes again. That is, I am the most hated person in your life, a person that you want to slice into a million pieces. However… you may hate me, but doesn’t Lin Ming also hate you? You took away his everything and left him nothing but a cheap life… oh, that’s right, you did offer your sincere feelings to him, but what significance is there in that? It is worthless!”

“I never imagined that even after seven reincarnations, you would still be so mesmerized by that word ‘love’. You are just like a little girl with your naïve little expectations of others. Since you want to maintain that fragile and ridiculous bubble in your heart, then I won’t pop it for you. I want something else, bring it here…”

The Soul Emperor put out a hand. Sheng Mei grit her teeth, her eyes thick with murderous thoughts. But in the end, she composed herself and completely opened her spiritual sea.

Slowly, from between her eyebrows, countless motes of light condensed, finally forming into a bean-sized deep red and purple sphere of light.

This sphere of light slowly floated away. In the void of space, a constant flow of energy came from this small sphere of light, as if it contained an infinite universe within.

This was… Lin Ming’s Eternal Soul. Unless it was offered voluntarily, it could not be taken.

When Lin Ming and Sheng Mei had made love, his mind had completely fallen into her hands. At the pinnacle of joy and passion, he had voluntarily handed it over.

And now, Sheng Mei was giving this Eternal Soul to the Soul Emperor on her own volition.

It was different than what Lin Ming had thought. Sheng Mei didn’t retain half of the Eternal Soul but gave it all to the Soul Emperor.

In the boundless starry skies, it was like a mystical seed. As if it could form a world just by being planted.

“The Eternal Soul, it’s finally mine!”

Looking at this Eternal Soul, the Soul Emperor’s eyes shined with incomparable excitement.

“I did everything in my power in order to nourish it! And now, I have obtained it.”

The Soul Emperor licked his lips. He waved his hands and the Eternal Soul fell into his grasp. He smiled, revealing brutally white teeth. Combined with his horrifying face, his smile left one shuddering with fear.

The Soul Emperor excitedly looked at the soul seed in his hands.

He first investigated it with his sense. Once he was sure that it hadn’t been tampered with, he slowly pressed this soul seed into the point between his eyebrows.

He was always careful in order to not give anyone a chance to harm him.

As the Eternal Soul entered his body, the Soul Emperor seemed to have obtained the most wonderful thing in the world. He was like an opium addict that had been denied his drugs, finally obtaining a box of the most precious drugs. He was like a sexual deviant who had been deprived of the joys of the flesh for years, finally obtaining the most beautiful woman in the world.

Because of the Soul Emperor’s extreme excitement, his face turned fierce.

His filthy old eyes slowly changed, filling with a profoundly pure brightness.

This process continued for two hours.

The Soul Emperor looked more and more like a youth. The depressing atmosphere around him had also dissipated by a great deal.

It was just that his face was still pale white without a trace of blood, so drained that it left one’s heart chilled.

“Good, very good!”

The Soul Emperor stretched out his right hand, cracking his knuckles.

“I will agree to your request. As for Soaring Feather God King, I will deal with her myself. Of course, this is also for myself… right now, I don’t want the saints to notice anything out of the ordinary!”

The Eternal Soul couldn’t be directly absorbed by the Soul Emperor. Rather, it had been sealed into his spiritual sea and wrapped in layers of bindings.

Absorbing a soul was easier said than done.

The complex spirit marks would cause the person absorbing it to lose themselves and form split personalities.

Empyrean Primordius was an extremely good example.

Even though the Soul Emperor had profound understandings of the soul, he still couldn’t accomplish this. In fact, it would be an extremely long process for the Soul Emperor to refine the Eternal Soul; he would need at least 100 thousand years.

Beside the Soul Emperor, Sheng Mei formed seals with her hands, creating layers of illusion space that completely sealed away the Sky Spill Planet.

This enchantment she casually created could last for tens of thousands of years.

The Soul Emperor disdainfully smiled. “You want to protect this planet? The saints may have invaded the Divine Realm, but they are only interested in the Divine Realm itself, not the mortal realms. At least, this will be true for the next several tens of thousands of years…”

Sheng Mei didn’t speak. She quietly turned around, tore open the void and departed.

Chapter 1932 – Sword Mountain

The sun and moon passed by; spring left and fall came.

In this wilderness, Lin Ming seemed to have fallen into an eternal sleep.

His body was covered with fallen leaves and then dust. Layer after layer, he was covered.

This immortal fairyland was originally nothing but an illusion. Now that Sheng Mei left, the illusion also vanished.

Not too far away from Lin Ming, wild animals frequently emerged from the untamed forests.

There were starving corrupt wolves that wanted to eat Lin Ming as their meal, but as they approached they were actually frightened by the aura of the demonic tree beside him, and scurried away with their tails between their legs.

Year after year, Lin Ming lay here, an empty shell.

He could feel his fires of life dimming and his cultivation slowly falling.

With the disappearance of his source soul force, his life force collapsed.

He felt that he couldn’t live for much longer.

The Sky Spill Planet was the world that gave birth to him, and now this world would also become his grave…

He didn’t know how humanity was doing. Had they founded their own base in the wild lands and begun developing the new generations?

Empyrean Divine Dream, did she manage to escape being hunted by the saints?

Three Lives Old Man, did he live his life without regrets?

There was also Empyrean Vast Universe… relatively speaking, he wasn’t too strong and he wasn’t too old. Still, he stubbornly followed Empyrean Divine Dream to venture into that battle with nine chances of death and one chance of survival. Was he fortunate enough to escape alive?

Lin Ming lightly sighed. At this time he no longer possessed the qualifications to care about these things. He was an infinitely gifted talent of the heavens, and was even recognized as someone who was destined to become an extreme True Divinity, perhaps even reaching the boundary of the Asura Road Master.

But in the end, his cultivation had only reached the peak Holy Lord realm; he hadn’t even managed to step into the World King realm. For all the praise and admiration he received, he was nothing but a joke.

On this day, Lin Ming struggled to slowly stand up. A thick crust of soil and green grass had grown over his body.

He felt that he didn’t have much life force remaining, but he didn’t want to return to dirt here.

In the final moments of his life, he wanted to visit some places of the Sky Spill Planet and see some sights.

Then, he could tranquilly wait for death to arrive.

He walked away.

He departed this wild land.

He didn’t fly and he didn’t tear through space, even though he could easily accomplish this with his current remaining cultivation.

He only used his own feet. One footprint at a time, he measured this land with each step he took.

His pace was slow but persistent.

He spread out his sense and found the direction he wished to go in.

He climbed over mountains, waded through rivers, swam across seas…

The seas of the Sky Spill Continent were vast. He broke into the rough waves, swimming along with whales as large as mountains. He saw thick bolts of lightning cut through the sky, shattering open the waters. He saw rainbows appear after the rain, stretching through the horizon.

All of these scenes he saw in the deep sea would have left mortals sighing in praise, their minds opened and expanded.

However, Lin Ming was quiet as he saw all of this.

Finally, he crossed this sea. He had already used his sense to investigate his surroundings and knew that this sea was called the South Sea.

The Xuan Wuji that he fought in the past had come from the South Sea Demon Region.

He crossed the South Sea and drew closer to his destination. He wanted to go to Green Mulberry City, return to the place where he lived in his youth and see his past there…

This was his life’s final wish.

He took out a wood spirit jade mask from his spatial ring. The one he chose was the mask he once wore in the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom.

He knew that in the South Horizon Region and Sky Fortune Kingdom, there were many people who had seen his portrait. He didn’t want to be recognized by anyone, because he could guess that by this time, the Divine Realm would have fallen into the hands of the enemy.

Although the flames of war had yet to reach the Sky Spill Planet, this was only temporary. If the saints learned that he was at the Sky Spill Planet then the consequences would be unimaginable.

Lin Ming might not care about his own life, but this would bring a grave catastrophe upon the Sky Spill Planet.

All the people on this planet would die along with him.

He wore the mask and continued forwards, one step at a time.

Then, in front of him, a mountain appeared.

This mountain was majestically high and its sides were steep and dangerous. It was like a divine sword that had been stabbed into the ground.

Lin Ming looked at this mountain. He was silent for a moment before he started to climb up.

“Hey, brother, do not crawl up this mountain, you cannot climb it.”

As Lin Ming began ascending the mountain he suddenly heard people speak up behind him. He turned and saw a young man and woman.

They held swords in their hands and were clearly mortal martial artists.

The man was in his twenties and the young woman seemed around 18-19 years old. Their cultivations were respectively at the Houtian realm and Pulse Condensation realm. According to the standards of the mortal world, for two youths to have such a cultivation absolutely meant they were elites.

They were stunned upon seeing Lin Ming’s mask, as if they didn’t expect such a strange person to appear. This person seemed eccentric and yet wore such a cold and heartless mask. It seemed that they had met a weirdo.

However, they still spoke politely to him. “I can see that you aren’t young, but your physical strength is quite good and you also cultivate the martial path. If you want to climb up Sword Mountain, could it be because you wish to seek out the Sword Immortal on this mountain and request to be his apprentice? If so, then I urge you to give up. I don’t mean to be rude, but with your cultivation it is impossible for you to climb this mountain, and even if you can, you will not succeed in becoming an apprentice. I heard that after a little more time, Sword Mountain’s Sword Immortal will be holding a gathering of swordsman, and at that time all sorts of masters from across the South Horizon Region will be arriving here. But even so, there are many people that cannot ascend the mountain. Because of our masters, we can go up once ourselves!”

As the young pair spoke, the young woman had a somewhat satisfied expression. It was clear they were fellow disciples and their master was also extremely famous in the South Horizon Region.

Lin Ming quietly turned back round. He continued to climb upwards. From start to finish, he didn’t say a single word.

His heart had already been burned to ash. The final wish of his life was to see places he had once lived at on the Sky Spill Planet; he didn’t want to come into contact with the people here.

To this world, he was only a traveler, a single stroke of the pen…

Seeing Lin Ming’s reaction, the youth’s mouth fell open. He was left dumbstruck.

But, the youth’s junior-apprentice sister stamped her feet and angrily said, “He really thinks our good intentions have evil meanings behind them. A person like this should get what they deserve!”

The senior-apprentice brother sighed. He spread his arms wide and said, “Looking at the strange mask he’s wearing and his character, he should be some bizarre character. Let’s wait another couple hours for Master to return. I wonder what gift he brought for the Sword Immortal…”

The young pair spoke, no longer bothering with Lin Ming.

They thought that Lin Ming wouldn’t be able to last much longer and would descend the mountain in distress, and then they would be at the base of the mountain where they could help him. But, what left them surprised was that Lin Ming climbed up the mountain and vanished without any news, as if he had truly succeeded in ascending to the top.

At this time, Lin Ming was indeed halfway up the mountainside. He could leap over such a mountain with a single step, but today he climbed up, and very slowly at that.

He could feel a rich sword energy coming from this mountain.

In Lin Ming’s eyes, this sword energy wasn’t strong at all.

But in the mortal world, in particular the South Horizon Region, this sword energy was considerably powerful. Even Lin Ming could feel a mighty and endless force from this sword energy, like surging seas and mountains.

This was a type of Concept, a Concept of the Sword.

The reason the young pair had said that the martial artists of the South Horizon Region couldn’t climb up this mountain was likely because of the sword intent here.

In the South Horizon Region, it was extremely rare for there to be such a sword-wielding talent.

However, Lin Ming didn’t have a single ounce of interest in this. He only passed by, his face still indifferent as he climbed this mountain.

But at this time, he heard a clear laugh. A blue beam of light tore through the blue skies and ripped apart the clouds.

High in the sky, the vague figure of a blue-clothed man appeared. This man seemed to be around 30 years old.

The man held dual swords and his eyebrows were straight and slanted. He was a dashing and heroic man.

Although this was only a glance, just what sort of eyesight did Lin Ming have? He could clearly see who this man was.

So it was him…

Lin Ming’s complexion faintly changed. After more than 130 years, even though this other person’s appearance had changed from the past, Lin Ming could still recognize him.

This person was the man he fought in the finals of the Seven Profound Valleys’ Total Faction Martial Meeting. His surname was Jiang, Jiang Baoyun.

Jiang Baoyun. So the Sword Immortal of Sword Mountain was actually him…

Lin Ming was surprised for a brief moment.

That’s right… in the entire South Horizon Region, Jiang Baoyun could have been considered an extraordinary young elite. At his age, being considered a Sword Immortal and possessing such a sword intent was also reasonable.

Chapter 1934 – Old Friends Meet Once More

Atop the cold pond, Jiang Baoyun and Jiang Lanjian’s match was reaching its superheated phase.

Each move condensed the essence of their swordsmanship. The surrounding martial artists cheered out loud, their voices reaching into the heavens.

But at this moment, the surrounding noise served to sharply contrast Lin Ming’s deepest feelings.

Peng!

Metal rang against metal. Jiang Lanjian’s sword was knocked out of his hand.

A blue sword spun out. Sword energy wildly surged, reaching a thousand feet high.

“99 moves, just one away from my goal!” Jiang Lanjian looked at Jiang Baoyun with suspicion. “You shouldn’t have been intentionally doing that, right…”

Jiang Baoyun shook his head. “Nine through nine, all returns to one. My dance of 99 sword moves just then was a single samsara…”

The sword moves also contained samsara?

Before the surrounding martial artists could think of what happened, at this time, Jiang Lanjian’s sword came crashing down from the air. Although its accompanying sword energy had weakened a great deal, it still rang out sharply.

This long sword fell onto one of the pavilions.

“Be careful!”

Many young disciples cried out in alarm, retreating as fast as they could.

Ding!

The long sword thrust into the ground, burying itself straight to the sword hilt.

And what a coincidence – the sword had nailed itself to the pavilion stage that Lin Ming was standing on.

The truth was that the sword’s landing point was quite far from Lin Ming. But, the surrounding disciples had fled like a pack of surprised birds, leaving only Lin Ming behind, standing motionlessly where he was. He was like a stone sculpture, extremely glaring for some time.

Many people looked towards Lin Ming.

This mysterious person was special enough; he actually wore a wood spirit jade mask. In the South Horizon Region, wood spirit jade was a precious treasure. Not many people knew of it but there were some knowledgeable individuals who recognized it.

The icy cold wood spirit jade mask seemed slightly distorted, giving off a strange feeling.

However, what was weird was that this youth wearing the mask had a restrained cultivation and it was impossible to see what boundary he was at.

This sort of person was either a peerless master or someone proficient in concealing their cultivation, or even a truly ordinary commoner.

But presently, the last possibility didn’t seem too likely.

Jiang Lanjian and Jiang Baoyun both noticed Lin Ming. Jiang Baoyun nodded.

“Friend, may I know your name?”

Jiang Baoyun could feel a familiar aura from this youth’s body, but he wasn’t sure just where he had sensed it before.

Lin Ming remained silent.

“How rude! Cloudsword Immortal asked you a question!”

The Sovereign of a third grade sect scolded Lin Ming. This Sovereign wanted to maintain Jiang Baoyun’s authority and enhance his own impression to everyone present. But, Lin Ming remained motionless like before, as if he hadn’t heard anything at all.

“You…”

In the South Horizon Region, a third grade sect Sovereign could be considered a top character in their own right, so when had they ever been ignored like this? The Sovereign became enraged and began preparing to teach Lin Ming a lesson.

But then, Jiang Baoyun said, “Sovereign Liu, please be patient.”

His words were light but carried a strange tone to them, a calm affinity that caused anyone who heard him to immediately subside their anger.

Jiang Baoyun turned to Lin Ming. “Friend, my name is Jiang Baoyun, an ascetic swordsman of the South Horizon Region. If you have nothing to do right now, then how about coming to my humble abode for a drink. I happen to have a pot of thousand year fog flower wine and I would like to invite a few friends to come drink with me.”

Jiang Baoyun’s polite words left everyone shocked.

Thousand year fog flower wine! That was made from the spring water of Sword Mountain combined with innumerable rare treasures; it was incredibly advantageous to a martial artist! Countless people would have fought each other to drink a single cup, yet Jiang Baoyun was actually asking this unknown and seemingly mentally disturbed person to drink to his heart's content?

Jiang Lanjian’s two apprentices, the young man and woman, were left staring with wide eyes. This was thousand year fog flower wine!

And the two of them knew that whether it was their honorable master Jiang Lanjian or senior master Jiang Baoyun, both were addicted to alcohol as if it was their life.

Sword and alcohol, those were the two things most essential to their lives.

Jiang Baoyun only had half a jar of this thousand year fog flower wine. Each time he invited his friends to drink he would only have a mere few cups, and yet he was asking this unknown person to drink with him?

Who was he? Wasn’t this the same as a meat pie falling down from the heavens?

Jiang Baoyun’s invitation caused Lin Ming to sigh with emotion. After a period of silence, he finally nodded.

This left many people so depressed they nearly spat out blood.

This idiot simply didn’t know what thousand year fog flower wine was, right? To be so reluctant to drink it, he could anger people to death and not know of it!

“Please!”

Jiang Baoyun straightforwardly said.

The place Jiang Baoyun lived was very simple.

A bamboo house, a few huts, that was all.

The arrangement of the house was also simple.

An old and plain wooden table. Several chairs. A bottle of bamboo. A written poem portrait filled with overbearing sword intent.

And… rows of wine jars.

Jiang Baoyun leisurely took out the thousand year fog flower wine and heated it with warm water. Then, he washed a few cups and filled them.

There were three people in the house.

Jiang Baoyun, Jiang Lanjian, as well as Lin Ming.

After 130 years, these three old friends had unexpectedly reunited.

“Brother, may I know your honored name?”

This question was not asked by Jiang Baoyun but by Jiang Lanjian. He was also curious as to who Lin Ming was.

This individual was a complete enigma, but he could feel that… he was somewhat familiar.

But just based on this familiarity alone, Jiang Lanjian would never have thought, would never have dared to imagine it was that person…

“Very well, if this brother doesn’t wish to speak his name, then there is no need to ask. When sharing a drink, all we need to do is raise our cups. Why must we know each other?”

“Let’s drink!”

The three people raised their cups and drank the wine.

“Good wine!”

Jiang Lanjian praised.

Jiang Baoyun also savored the aftertaste for a long time. He praised, “The charm of wine comes from the mood of drinking wine. Those that understand wine taste not just the wine but also the mood. From the spiciness when it first enters the throat, to the fresh heat once it is swallowed, to the lasting fragrance that one can mull over. It’s just like life. In the world, countless people struggle. They experience hardship, they experience tribulations, and if they can survive all of that then they can return to their true state and release the mellow fragrance of life.

“For me, whether it is thousand year fog flower wine or some coarse distilled grain wine, the truth is that there is no essential difference, because what I am drinking is not wine, but life…”

Jiang Baoyun’s words caused Jiang Lanjian to laugh and cheer.

As for Lin Ming, his mind shook. He quietly thought about these words.

In a man’s life there was rise and fall, hardship and suffering. Just how many people experienced this?

To overcome this and return to one’s true self, achieving supreme enlightenment and becoming a legend…

The Soul Emperor was right. What he lacked in his life was tribulations.

He had come from nothing and had indeed experienced countless life and death slaughters, walking on the precipice of death innumerable times.

Lan Yunyue’s betrayal, Xuan Wuji’s hunting, Yang Yun’s plotting, Tian Mingzi’s calculations, and then the step-by-step pressure of the Good Fortune Saint Son…

All of these were considered setbacks.

But they weren’t too remarkable.

Because when many martial artists grew up, they all experienced such things.

Lin Ming remembered Dragon Fang; he remembered Jun Bluemoon. They were people who had their own stories, and their experiences, their tribulations, were not necessarily any less than his own.

However, a true great tribulation, a true great setback…

When they encountered it, they simply didn’t know what path to take out.

Chapter 1935A – Revisiting Familiar Lands

“Brother?”

Seeing Lin Ming quietly looking at his wine cup, Jiang Baoyun couldn’t help but ask.

Lin Ming looked up. “Thank you…”

Jiang Baoyun was startled. He didn’t know what Lin Ming was thanking him for, but this was unimportant. He openly smiled and said, “It seems that I have hit it off with a new friend. Today, none of us will rest without being drunk!”

Jiang Lanjian also echoed this sentiment. He laughed, “Haha, no drunk no sleep!”

Jiang Baoyun looked at Lin Ming and suddenly said, “Truthfully speaking, you look like someone I knew once, so that was why I invited you here to drink wine.”

“Oh…”

Lin Ming fell silent, not speaking too much.

“Friend, you’re quite the special one.” Jiang Baoyun was stunned. Normally, one would ask just which person they reminded him of, but this masked man only uttered a single ‘oh’.

Jiang Baoyun finished off his cup of wine. He recalled that time 130 years ago at the Seven Profound Valleys when he had fought Lin Ming in that unrivalled battle. In his life, that was his most unforgettable fight.

He sighed, saying, “You are indeed somewhat similar to my old friend, but you are actually different. You don’t seem as persevering as he was, but instead like an old man in the twilight of his life. But, that makes the weight on your back seem that much heavier…

“That old friend… I once tried to chase after his footsteps, but he kept running further and further away until I could no longer see him. Now, he should have already stepped onto the road towards the peak of martial arts, after all, that was his dream…”

“The peak of martial arts…” Lin Ming quietly said, somewhat at a loss. “What is the peak of martial arts?”

He asked Jiang Baoyun this question, but he also asked himself.

The truth was that in these past years, Lin Ming already had his doubts as to what the peak of martial arts was.

Countless peerless masters had searched for the peak of martial arts since ancient times.

For the peak of martial arts, Sheng Mei had done everything in her power, even giving up her body.

For the peak of martial arts, Divine Dream diligently strived and struggled.

For the peak of martial arts, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was willing to fuse with an abyssal without any hesitation…

But, just how far did they manage to go?

Not mentioning them, even the Asura Road Master or the creator of the Holy Scripture, the two of them… did they ever reach the peak of martial arts?

Jiang Baoyun said, “As to what that peak is, I don’t know. But I believe that when people see a group of mountains together, they call the top of the highest mountain the peak. If so, then my Sword Mountain is also the peak.”

Lin Ming shook his head, “Sword Mountain… is not enough.”

“Yes, it is not enough! When I mount the summit of Sword Mountain, I can overlook a country, but overlooking a country is far from enough. In this world there are endless mountain peaks. But, there must be a single mountain that is the highest. The higher a mountain peak, the more difficult it is for me. And to me, the most terrifying, the most horrifying thing is that I simply don’t know where this mountain is.”

Lin Ming calmly stared at this wine cup. Perhaps he already knew where this mountain was…

Between the three great universal divine tools, the roads of essence, energy, and divine, the Holy Scripture that cultivated the inner universe and the Heavenly Sutra that cultivated the outer universe. To fuse them together…

This was the highest peak?

Lin Ming wasn’t sure. But what he knew was that when Jiang Baoyun displayed his samsara sword arts, his dual swords weren’t anything at all when compared to the cultivation of essence, energy, divine, or the outer and inner universes.

Even if Jiang Baoyun had reached the limit of his road, that was only the heights of Sword Mountain.

“And will you keep searching?” Lin Ming suddenly asked Jiang Baoyun.

“Why wouldn’t I?” Jiang Baoyun laughed and filled his wine cup once more. “I will never stop searching. I know that my vision is limited and I might never be able to find it, but I will climb up as I did before, unendingly. I do not need to truly reach the highest peak in the world, but as I climb, I will be more than happy to simply see that peak above me!

“This is because when I climb to a new peak, my vision will expand further and I will be able to see where a higher peak lies. And when I climb up that new peak, I will find yet another higher one, and I will keep repeating this…”

“Is there any meaning to it?”

Lin Ming asked.

He knew how short a martial artist’s life was. If they took detour after detour, that would only make them waste away their youth.

“There is.” Jiang Baoyun solemnly nodded. He tossed back the wine in his cup. “Even if I have to climb without end in my life, even if I forever remain small and never see where the highest peak is, then at the very least… I will keep surpassing myself, I will keep defeating myself.”

Defeating myself?

At that moment, Lin Ming’s heart shook, as if something touched it.

Defeating himself… in life, a person’s greatest enemy was themselves.

Jiang Baoyun was doomed to never be able to step onto the peak of martial arts in his life, but, he still continued to seek it out, because every time he climbed a new mountain peak it would mean he had defeated his old self.

Sometimes, even if a person knew that what they were trying to do was impossible, they would still rush in without hesitation.

A moth to a flame – wasn’t this what it was?

Lin Ming was silent. He mulled over these new sentiments in his heart, not speaking.

He had once said that he was a moth willing to fly into the fire.

However, a human was not a moth.

For those who were willing to be moths that flew into the flames, the truth was that when they really did rush into that blazing inferno, they would still see a glimmer of hope within.

In the past, Lin Ming was also like this.

He said he would be a moth that flew into the flames, and he did do that, moreover, he even succeeded.

However, a real moth would not succeed.

For them to fly into a flame, what they faced was certain death.

When one truly saw no hope, when the flames burned brightly before them, how many people would still be willing to rush in?

“Let’s have another drink!”

Jiang Baoyun’s words broke Lin Ming’s reverie. Lin Ming drank another cup of wine.

Cup after cup, the thousand year fog flower wine was finished.

They changed to a new wine. Jar after jar, it was unknown how many jars they drank.

These three normally wouldn’t become drunk. But today, they did.

When a person was drunk, their thoughts would become muddled.

The lives of the people.

The common folk worked for their livelihoods, bustling about.

Nobles and officials engaged in intrigue and plotting for their countries and people.

Common martial artists fought in life and death slaughters to struggle for a higher boundary.

Empyreans and True Divinities schemed for their races and for the survival of their people…

Life was a battle, all muddled up together.

To savor the mellowness and spiciness of life, when the thoughts were truly muddled, perhaps that was when one could truly understand the mysteries...

This was the mood of wine, as well as the abstraction of life…

Lin Ming didn’t know how many jars of wine he drank. He only stopped when all three people were lying in a drunken daze on the ground, drifting off to sleep.

With this thought in mind, Lin Ming slept deeply.

It had been many years since he had rested like this.

He didn’t worry about humanity’s great calamity, he didn’t worry about being hunted by a True Divinity, and he didn’t worry about his fading fires of the soul.

A rare indulgence, a rare moment of muddled mindedness.

…

The awakening of a dream.

The night was deep.

Jiang Baoyun and Jiang Lanjian were still sleeping. The table was covered with messy bottles and cups of wine, and beside it were several empty wine jars.

Lin Ming looked at them for a while and then stood up.

And at this time, Jiang Baoyun also awoke.

“Leaving?”

Jiang Baoyun looked towards Lin Ming. Lin Ming nodded.

“Where to?”

Lin Ming was silent for a moment before saying, “To another place…”

He had a premonition that this would be the last time he ever saw Jiang Baoyun.

Lin Ming continued, “And you?”

Jiang Baoyun smiled. “Me? I will be searching… for a higher mountain peak…”

Chapter 1935B – Revisiting Familiar Lands

Lin Ming departed. His visit to Sword Mountain had left him with an inexplicable feeling.

Although during this period he did not perceive cultivation methods, enlighten himself on the Heavenly Dao, or even sit in meditation, Lin Ming knew that in truth, his heart had gone through an unprecedented baptism.

If the fires of his soul were still vibrant, then these feelings and sentiments would bring him unimaginable accomplishments in the future.

However, he still hadn’t found a way to restore his source soul force…

He crossed Sword Mountain, passing through a vast wilderness and then arriving at the Sky Fortune Kingdom.

The Sky Fortune Kingdom – the land where he was born and raised.

This land carried far too many memories for him.

Lin Ming stood on a mountain, looking down over the country. In the infinite vastness of the cosmos, this tiny nation was far too small. It wouldn’t even be able to be described as a grain of sand in the desert.

But even so, this tiny land was burdened with Lin Ming’s memories…

He spread out his sense, easily covering the entire nation.

He found Green Mulberry City; this was the city he grew up in as a child.

In the past, Green Mulberry City was a small town. Its walls were 200 feet high and it had less than a hundred thousand citizens living within.

But in the current era, Green Mulberry City had already surpassed the capital, Sky Fortune City, and had become the number one city of the Sky Fortune Kingdom.

This city was extremely lively and bustling. The streets were wide and spacious and filled with crowds of boisterous people.

This world-overturning change was naturally because of Lin Ming. Lin Ming had come from this city and was the legendary hero of Green Mulberry City. Because of this, innumerable martial artists came to visit, and these martial artists possessed a massive amount of wealth that boosted Green Mulberry’s rapid growth.

At the city entrance there were three 30 foot high rock sculptures.

The sculpture in the city was that of Lin Ming. Lin Ming’s statue grasped a long spear that pointed straight into the bright blue skies.

Behind Lin Ming, there were two sculptures of peerless women. They were as beautiful as ephemeral fairies; they were Mu Qianyu and Qin Xingxuan.

These three statues were worshipped by countless people every year.

Lin Ming stood at the entrance of the city for a long time, looking around.

Finally, he stepped into the city.

In the busy crowds there was everyone one could think of: students, martial artists, actors, maids, chair-bearers, stall owners selling sesame cakes…

“Come on, take a look! Take a look! Don’t miss out on this! I can crack a stone on my chest and a jar on my head! Those with money come and try, those without money, come and look!” A man with a bare upper body excitedly shouted out to the crowd, his fists cupped together.

“Feng shui can tell your fortune. If you believe, then come and try it, and if you don’t…” A fortune teller had set up a stall to divine the futures of gullible customers.

Lin Ming listened to the sounds all around him. Slowly, he blended into the crowd, becoming a common and inconspicuous individual. Only the mask covering his face caused people to notice him.

Luxurious carriages could be seen everywhere. Exquisite sedan chairs came one after another.

Some people rode towering horses into the city. Some people walked in with their heads held high, and some people sat at the city entrance in rags, begging atop their straw mats.

“Buy a sesame cake! These are fresh sesame cakes that just came out of the oven! Two pennies for one! Fresh and fragrant, these are made with the secret recipe of my ancestors! Little brother, how about trying one?”

As Lin Ming passed over a stone bridge, an aunty selling sesame cakes shouted out to him.

Lin Ming turned to see an aunty. Her face was wrapped in a scarf. Her exposed skin was reddened from years of sun exposure and harsh winds. She wore simple and coarse clothes, and a pair of worn out shoes.

At this time, she had wrapped a sesame cake with a piece of paper. The hands that held the sesame cake were gnarled with age.

Lin Ming looked at this aunty and felt a burning feeling in his nose. He felt over his body, but he knew he didn’t have any copper coins or even gold or silver.

He couldn’t take out anything from his spatial ring. Any single item taken out and placed in the mortal world would cause a catastrophe.

Thus, he shook his head.

The aunty looked at Lin Ming’s clothes. He didn’t seem like a poor person, but he didn’t have a single penny on him. Perhaps he had forgotten to bring money.

She smiled, “Little brother, did you forget to bring money? It’s already noon, you might not have eaten yet. Here, take a sesame cake, it’s free of charge.”

The aunty took the paper-wrapped sesame cake and stuffed it into Lin Ming’s hands.

Lin Ming took the sesame cake. He stood there, not knowing what feeling was in his heart.

In the past when Lin Ming was still a child, his family circumstances hadn’t been bad or good. His parents managed a restaurant for their clan and would receive money every year. When his mother gave him pocket money, Lin Ming would frequently stroll through the streets, buying sesame cakes and candied fruits.

Lin Ming held the sesame cake in his hands and slowly brought it up to his mouth. He took a small bite.

The mild taste melted in his mouth, bringing with it a unique fragrance.

The flavor hadn’t changed, even after over 100 years.

The only change was… those who ate the sesame cake…

Lin Ming cautiously ate.

This was a food unique to mortals. For many years, Lin Ming had eaten innumerable heavenly materials. Just a tiny bit of what he ate for a single meal couldn’t even be afforded by the entire wealth of a nation. But… he couldn’t remember any heavenly materials that tasted as good as this sesame cake did today. Lin Ming ate it up.

“Little brother, how is it?”

The aunty saw tears form at the corners of Lin Ming’s eyes as he ate the sesame cake, and she was flustered a little. “Does the cake not taste good? Or did you have some troubles with your family and run away…?”

“No, I’m fine… thank you, aunty…”

Lin Ming shook his head. He respectfully bowed and then turned to leave.

Lin Ming walked forwards step by step. Along the way, he saw many dignitaries and nobles. He saw young masters riding atop horses and spoiled misses in their sedans.

He saw even more poor people. He saw prostitutes displaying their bodies in front of brothels and he saw beggars begging on the streets.

The life of a mortal was less than a mere hundred years. From young to old, who knew how many peoples had been born and died, living through happiness and suffering.

Lin Ming had seen these sights in his youth. But, he had never truly experienced it.

When martial artists cultivated the Heavenly Dao, that was a type of enlightenment.

And returning to the mortal world and feeling the soil, that was also another type of enlightenment.

Yet, there were far too many people who perceived the Heavenly Dao and far too few people who understood the toils of mortals…

A martial artist stood at too high a height. Compared to an ordinary person, there was a natural moat as great at the skies that separated them; they were naturally unable to feel the sweet, sour, spicy, and all the other tastes of a mortal’s life.

Imperceptibly, Lin Ming arrived at the center of Green Mulberry City. Here was where the Lin Family was located.

For the past 100 some years, because of Lin Ming, they had become the number one mortal family clan of the entire Sky Fortune Kingdom and even the entire South Horizon Region.

Even the royal families of great nations weren’t as prominent or prestigious as the Lin Family.

No matter who it was or what influence they came from, no one dared to provoke the Lin Family.

In the past, Lin Ming had taken his parents away from the Lin Family and had ended his karma with them. Today, Lin Ming returned to the Lin Family, but only quietly stood at the front gates.

For two hours, Lin Ming watched as all sorts of famed and powerful individuals walked in and out of the Lin Family. Each one was respectful as they walked in, and didn’t dare to hurry their steps.

He also saw some disciples of the Lin Family practice their martial artists on the military field, their movements intense and vigorous.

The current head of the Lin Family was an intelligent individual. He understood that one’s own strength was the most important thing.

Lin Ming silently looked at all of this and then silently departed. From start to finish, he never passed through the gates of the Lin Family.

Life and death was fated, wealth and honor came and went. The Lin Family should be able to live prosperously for thousands of years, but in this world, there was no such thing as eternal wealth and glory.

Perhaps in the future, this respected family would be ruined, one day reverting to an ordinary family…

In Lin Ming’s eyes, this was a natural samsara. There was no need to change it…

Chapter 1936A – A Snowy Night

Lin Ming’s last stop in Green Mulberry City was the restaurant that his parents had managed for the Lin Family in the past.

However, the restaurant was no longer a restaurant. It was no longer open for business, but closed up against outsiders.

This restaurant was a treasure land of the Lin Family. Let alone eating a meal, one couldn’t even visit.

Even every new generation of the Sky Fortune Kingdom’s emperor would only be able to distantly pay their respects when they came to visit Green Mulberry City.

In the Sky Fortune Kingdom, the truth was that the Lin Family represented something similar to divine right. They were a force that stood above imperial authority and were insurmountable.

Seeing this restaurant that no one could even enter, Lin Ming seemed to lose interest in revisiting the familiar places.

In revisiting familiar places, he didn’t come to see the sights, but to recall memories.

When the Lin Family restaurant was no longer the same and instead had taken on a completely different significance, Lin Ming no longer wished to go in.

Because, from there, in the end these memories could not be found…

Lin Ming left. He left Green Mulberry City and left the Sky Fortune Kingdom…

Thinking about it, ever since Sheng Mei drew out Lin Ming’s source soul force, around seven or eight years had passed.

Lin Ming could feel his cultivation fall every day. Although the tiny amount of source soul force left in his body made it so that he didn’t age and turn senile, his weak fires of life weren’t able to be summoned. He also couldn’t withstand the burden of the massive energy and cultivation contained within his body.

Slowly, these strengths dissipated.

He began to weaken.

He travelled to the north. He passed through villages and eventually arrived at a northern grassland.

This land was not as peaceful as the Sky Fortune Kingdom.

Soldiers and cavalry chaotically wandered about. War happened year-round. Lin Ming walked through the streets and could feel the worry and panic in the hearts of the walking pedestrians. They often had scarves wrapped around their heads, their footsteps hurried and their expressions tense.

War, famine, plagues; to mortals these were three of the most terrifying events.

And once war, famine, and plagues erupted it would likely spread.

On this day, there was heavy snow.

Lin Ming went to a remote mountain. The day was late and the path of the road couldn’t be seen. The snow was knee-deep. If this was a valley, an entire person could be swallowed up.

Lin Ming looked at the vast white mountain ridge that was illuminated in a pall of night. He wanted to climb the mountain, but at this time, he suddenly felt inexplicably cold. He couldn’t help but shiver.

Although Lin Ming’s cultivation had fallen, he still wasn’t so weak that he couldn’t withstand the cold on this snowy mountain. In fact, even if the most powerful ice-attribute martial artist of the Sky Spill Planet were to freely attack Lin Ming, he wouldn’t feel anything at all.

But on this day, he felt an inexplicable chill.

This was a coldness that came from the soul, making it nearly impossible for Lin Ming to withstand.

He knew that the wounds Sheng Mei left in him couldn’t be cured. Moreover… they would become increasingly heavy until finally, they took his life.

He used his sense to cover this mountain. He wanted to look for a place to rest.

But as he searched, his mind suddenly shook. He… saw a person, a person he recognized. Although this person’s appearance had greatly changed, Lin Ming was still able to recognize him.

There were far too many shadows of the past on his appearance. And, his saber hadn’t changed for over 130 years…

……..

“This damnable weather, what hellish luck!”

“To hurry on the road on such a snowy night can take a man’s life. I wonder if the cold weather will sicken his highness the crown prince.”

Two youths complained in low voices. They spoke in whispers. On such a snowy and windy night, their voices couldn’t travel too far.

“Just forget it. We have to find the little princess within three days, evacuate from this area and return to our base. If we stay too long then the White Guard will definitely find us.”

An old man spoke. He wore a bamboo hat and carried a child in his arms.

He wore a long coat and tried to cover the shivering child in his arms as much as possible. He kept his head lowered as he hurried along.

“What if we can’t find her?” A youth anxiously asked…

“If we can’t find her then that is the will of heaven…” The old man deeply sighed and shook his head. “If I remember correctly then the cave we stopped by last year is just in front of us. There should still be some hay and firewood left inside, so let’s rest in there tonight.”

As the old man spoke he searched out the snow road before him. He had a sharp memory, and after a quarter hour he found the cave he remembered from the past.

Everyone let out a long breath of relief. To cross a mountain on a snowy night, that was something they could withstand, but the child with them wouldn’t be able to bear it.

The group quickly ran into the cave. They brushed the snow off their bodies and took off their bamboo hats.

Although the cave was still cold, the air inside was dry. And as the old man remembered, there really was hay and firewood within.

They planned to use the firewood to light a fire.

But when they lit the flames, at the moment the cave was illuminated in light, they were all startled and quickly drew backwards.

With sharp ringing sounds, everyone drew out their weapons!

This was because there was someone sitting in the cave. He wore a jade-green mask that had an extremely cold and indifferent expression carved into it. Moreover, this person hadn’t made a single sound nor did he release any aura. This was why when the group entered the cave, no one had noticed him.

“Who are you?”

Everyone had their guards raised. This was because they were all being hunted down by the White Guard.

In this remote part of a snowy mountain, a mysterious person had suddenly appeared, making them all feel as if they were in a perilous situation.

“Just a passerby…”

Lin Ming quietly said. His eyes were focused on the old man in the group.

This old man appeared to be around 60 years of age. His face was engraved with the years of wind and frost. From the outline of his face, one could vaguely sense that in his youth, this old man had also once been a considerably dashing individual.

This old man only had a single arm. His hair was white and a full white mustache fell down like whiskers. There was a deep scar on his face. It started from his eyebrows and extended down to his neck, nearly splitting through his entire face.

Although this old man was extremely vigilant, there was a deep weariness emanating from him. His old and dirty eyes were bloodshot, and one could see that he hadn’t slept well for several days.

At this time, the old man held out his sword to confront Lin Ming and simultaneously pushed the child to his back to protect him. This child was also sensible and aware of the situation. He didn’t cry nor make noise, but instead quietly stood behind the old man and peeked out at Lin Ming.

Lin Ming was slightly moved. The image of this exhausted old man in front of him began to slowly overlap with another image in his mind.

This image wore embroidered robes and a golden crown tied up his hair. He had an elegant sword strapped onto his waist and his appearance was bold and heroic. Moreover, the corners of his lips had a slight touch of taunting contempt to them, as if to show off his disdain for all others.

If it weren’t for the deep red sword wrapped in snakeskin that was in the old man’s hand, if it weren’t for the familiar fire-attribute true essence emanating from this old man…

Then Lin Ming would never have believed that this old man was an old enemy from his past – Zhu Yan.

Zhu Yan.

In Green Mulberry City, Zhu Yan had stolen away his first love – Lan Yunyue.

Afterwards, Lin Ming had firmed his determination to enter the Seven Profound Martial House. He took his small amount of money and travelled to the Sky Fortune Kingdom to partake in the examinations there. Because he just happened to encounter Zhu Yan by chance when he was registering, one of Zhu Yan’s friends had Lin Ming secretly expelled from his living quarters in order to curry favor. Because of that, Lin Ming went to Great Clarity Pavilion where he worked as a deboner, and it was there that Lin Ming obtained the Magic Cube.

Afterwards, Lin Ming’s cultivation rapidly rose. When his true ability was revealed to the world, this caused Sky Fortune City’s royal family to take notice of him and do everything in their power to win him over.

As for Zhu Yan, because there was a grudge between him and Lin Ming, he was forced to endure great pressure and isolation.

Even his lord, the Tenth Prince Yang Zhen, had started to force Zhu Yan’s hand in his quest for the throne. Yang Zhen had forced Zhu Yan to break his engagement with Lan Yunyue.

Finally, Zhu Yan was defeated by Lin Ming.

Then, whether it was the Zhu Family or the Tenth Prince, Zhu Yan had lost all value to them. Instead he had become a burden.

Thus, Zhu Yan had been expelled.

From that point on, Lin Ming no longer saw Zhu Yan again. It had been over 130 years since they last saw each other.

Lin Ming never thought that after the day he last saw Zhu Yan, the next time they met, Zhu Yan would already be like this.

The scar on his face. His single arm. His old and exhausted face…

Lin Ming could even see the internal injuries left in his body. These hidden wounds had likely even affected Zhu Yan’s road of martial arts.

Because of all of this, Lin Ming could imagine just how much change and hardship Zhu Yan had experienced over the years.

“You… know me?”

Zhu Yan noticed Lin Ming’s gaze and was startled.

Lin Ming didn’t reply. He leaned against the rock behind him. A little hay covered the ground he sat on. At this time, he still felt that biting cold from within.

This pain that came from the soul was nearly unbearable.

“He… he looks like he’s shivering.” Someone said in a whisper as they looked at Lin Ming.

“Is he too cold?”

Everyone thought the situation a little absurd. With the sudden appearance of a masked individual, they thought this might be some peerless master sent to assassinate them. But now, this person was violently shivering as if they couldn’t stand this cold mountain wind.

“That scared me. I thought it was some master…”

“Don’t lower your guard!”

The group chose the corner furthest from Lin Ming and carefully sat down, keeping an eye on him the entire time.

“Old Flame, should we do something about him…” A person said with a true essence sound transmission, “I don’t know whether he heard our conversation from before…”

“The snow is heavy and the winds are great. He shouldn’t have heard us. And if he did, that proves his cultivation is far above ours. If we fight him, we might be the ones killed instead. So… just don’t try to stir up any unnecessary trouble with someone, especially when you don’t know what their origin is. Although he looks sick, for some reason I feel strange when I see him.”

Zhu Yan slowly said. He no longer went by his old name, but instead called himself by a single character – Flame.

Chapter 1936B – A Snowy Night

The group set up a bonfire. They sat around the warm edges eating dried meats and drinking water. The entire time, they remained vigilant against Lin Ming.

The little boy in Zhu Yan’s arms was quiet from beginning to end. His large eyes blinked as he stared at Lin Ming.

Lin Ming noticed that this little boy had a thread of red silk hanging around his neck and adorned with a common-looking bronze medal. This bronze medal had a unique flower petal design on it.

Zhu Yan seemed to realize something. Unhurriedly, he slipped the bronze medal into the boy’s collar…

After eating, Zhu Yan sat in rest with his eyes closed. But, his attention was focused on Lin Ming the entire time.

He didn’t know why, but the more he looked at this person, the stranger the feeling that tickled his mind. He just couldn’t identify what it was.

Lin Ming was also looking at Zhu Yan. Over 130 years had passed and the endless changes of mortal life had been and gone. Recalling the proud and arrogant youth of the past, Lin Ming found it hard to imagine that such a person had undergone such a dramatic transformation.

Lin Ming had heard their words when they were outside the cave just then. It was clear that they were searching for children from the royal family.

As Lin Ming crossed through the northern deserts and grasslands, he had seen the turmoil of war and the chaos of battle. He was able to guess just what was occurring.

This was a war of a mortal nation. When a nation was destroyed by another nation, the royal family fled the capital and the prince and princess were separated…

As for Zhu Yan, he and his subordinates were assigned to seek out the lost children of the royal family. It was clear that this was a dangerous mission.

If they weren’t careful then they would all be killed.

Lin Ming could feel that Zhu Yan didn’t do all of this for glory and riches. This was because Zhu Yan didn’t have much life left to live. At his current cultivation boundary, a hundred some years was his limit.

He likely wouldn’t be able to wait for the revival of the nation. Moreover, such a defeated dynasty usually found it impossibly difficult to stage a comeback.

Then for what reason did he support all of these meaningless actions that were also extremely dangerous?

As this thought was crossing through Lin Ming’s mind, a sheepskin bag of water was tossed towards him.

Lin Ming reached out a hand and grabbed the water bag. The bag was hot in his hands; the water had been heated over the bonfire and then poured into the bag.

This water bag was thrown over by Zhu Yan.

“Aren’t you cold? Drink some hot water.” Zhu Yan looked at Lin Ming, his eyes wary.

Lin Ming took off the lid and drank a mouthful before tossing the water bag back.

He didn’t speak to Zhu Yan. The several people in his group rested in the cave and took turns on watch, but Lin Ming didn’t sleep a single moment throughout the night.

Early in the morning, Zhu Yan and the others donned their bamboo hats and left. Their group trudged through the boundless heavy snow, quickly vanishing from sight…

Lin Ming quietly watched Zhu Yan’s fading back and also stepped into the snow…

He arrived at a small town. There weren’t many people here. Without anyone to sweep away the snow, the ground was a blank white canvas.

Walking through the streets, Lin Ming could feel the coldness within his body becoming increasingly heavy and thick.

Suddenly, his body shook and his face paled. In that moment, an indescribably agonizing pain swelled up from his spiritual sea.

Puff!

Lin Ming spat out a mouthful of blood. The bright red blood splashed onto the front of his clothes. This was a grisly and shocking sight.

Lin Ming trembled. He somehow couldn’t support himself and slowly slumped to the ground.

Many people saw him. A woman cried out in alarm and several people began hurrying far away.

As war echoed through the land, everyone remained vigilant of others. They thought that someone had been killed on the streets.

But upon further inspection, they discovered that Lin Ming seemed to have randomly spat out a mouthful of blood.

“What’s wrong with him?”

“Who knows? Perhaps he has some hidden wounds that were suddenly stirred up.”

“Look at that mask on his face. He definitely isn’t an ordinary person. He might be someone from the organization, or even an assassin…”

“He definitely knows martial arts, and if so then he was wounded by someone even stronger.”

As people said this they began to draw further and further away. A kind and soft-hearted woman couldn’t help what she was seeing and wanted to aid Lin Ming, but she was stopped by her husband.

“War is everywhere now. Don’t stir up needless troubles. If he is someone from the old dynasty and we rescue him then that will be the death penalty for us.”

People fled far away, as if they were hiding from a god of plagues.

Lin Ming’s body shivered as he withstood this scorching pain. This sort of pain originated from his soul and came from its depletion; it was unbearable.

He felt his strength rapidly drain away. His meridians and blood vessels were crudely and savagely torn open.

The pain continued for a full two hours. The white snowy canvas beneath him was already dyed red with blood. White and red, these two bright contrasting colors formed a fierce and chilling image.

“Big brother, you… are you alright…?”

As Lin Ming nearly fainted from the pain, he heard a shy voice echo out from nearby.

He opened his eyes to see a dirty little girl with big and bright eyes looking at him. She wore a tattered cloth bag over her body and a broken piece of pottery hung across her neck. It was unknown just where she had picked it up from. From the looks of it, she was a young beggar.

“Big brother, if you drink some water you might feel better.” The little girl timidly held out a canteen of water. “I haven’t eaten and I don’t have any food, so I can only give you some water…”

The little girl was extremely pitiable. With the cold weather and her ragged clothing, her small face and hands almost seemed frozen.

Lin Ming wiped the blood from the corners of his lips and shook his head, “There’s no need…”

In this era when war ravaged the lands, this little girl was likely an orphan. Her parents had probably died in the chaos of war…

Without her parents, she could only beg for food. But in this tumultuous times when the common people didn’t even have enough food to fill their own stomachs, how could they have anything to give to a small child?

Her destiny was likely to die alone, drowning in fear, cold, and hunger…

As Lin Ming thought of this, he felt his heart tighten.

The hardships of a mortal were everywhere.

To a martial artist, these hardships might not even seem worthy of mentioning. But when these hardships befell these mortal commoners, it was actually a monumental matter.

Lin Ming wanted to help this little girl, but unfortunately he didn’t have anything to give her. He wasn’t even able to give her a steamed bun or a few copper coins.

As he was saddened, he suddenly noticed a thin red thread around the little girl’s neck.

Lin Ming had seen this red silk thread before. It was exactly the same as the one that the little boy in the mountain cave had been wearing.

Sweeping out his sense, Lin Ming discovered that beneath this little girl’s tattered clothing, there was a bronze medal. This bronze medal had a unique flower design, also similar to the boy’s bronze medal…

Lin Ming suddenly recalled the conversation Zhu Yan had with his subordinate. Zhu Yan had said, “Just forget it. We have to find the little princess within three days, evacuate from this area and return to our base. If we stay too long then the White Guard will definitely find us.”

Little princess…

Was this little girl in front of him the little princess that Zhu Yan was searching for?

An orphan from the old dynasty. She once lived an extravagant and sumptuous lifestyle every day, but now she suffered the distresses and miseries of the mortal world…

It was likely because she experienced such drastic changes that she was able to sympathize with others at such a young age.

Lin Ming was silent for a moment. He held onto the little girl’s hand.

The little girl didn’t resist and allowed Lin Ming to pull her along.

Lin Ming spread out his sense, covering an area of several hundred miles.

Then, Lin Ming easily found Zhu Yan and the others. They were stationed in a humble little restaurant, eating a meal as they spoke with the restaurant owner.

Lin Ming turned to the little girl. He said, “Would you like to come with me? I’ll bring you to look for your big brother.”

Lin Ming’s words left the little girl startled. She took a step back, her eyes somewhat wary.

However, Lin Ming’s eyes seemed to contain an indescribable feeling, one that seemed filled with kindness and understanding. Slowly, she nodded.

Lin Ming hugged the little girl and packed her in his coat. Then, he moved towards that common-looking restaurant.

The restaurant was only 70-80 miles away from Lin Ming, in another small town.

Lin Ming didn’t walk quickly. But for some reason, that distance only took an incense stick of time beneath his feet.

Lin Ming held the little girl and walked into the restaurant.

Zhu Yan and the others were immediately on guard. They all drew their weapons.

As for the restaurant owner, he reflexively acted and closed the restaurant doors.

“It’s you… just how…”

Zhu Yan looked at Lin Ming and was surprised to see him.

They had crossed paths twice now. The first time could be called a coincidence but the second time could not.

This common restaurant was in truth one of their secret hideouts. The restaurant owner was actually vice-commander of the royal guard and was a loyal and devoted servant of the emperor.

It was at this time that Lin Ming and the others also noticed the child held tightly to his chest.

Facing so many drawn weapons, the little girl was scared. Her hold on Lin Ming tightened and her small and dirty face paled.

Zhu Yan didn’t know who this little girl was, but the boy behind him did.

The boy was stunned for a moment and then finally called out, “Ping’er, is that you?”

The little girl looked at the boy and was dumbfounded. After a long time, tears began to fall down her cheeks. “Big brother! It really is you!”

This little girl remembered that Lin Ming had told her he would lead her to her big brother, but she didn’t think they would really find him.

Half a year ago when their nation perished, that could have been called a parting of life and death. She never imagined that they would see each other once more.

Lin Ming set down the little girl, who ran forward and hugged her big brother.

Seeing this, Zhu Yan was bewildered.

Everyone was also left in a stunned daze. This was no different from a dream.

What was going on?

Why was this masked man holding the little princess?

It was impossible that this was a coincidence. This masked man before them had clearly brought the little princess over to look for them.

How did the masked man know they were searching for the little princess and how did they know she was this little girl?

Even if he did find the little princess, how did he know this was their secret hideout?

Everything was simply far too unbelievable!

Zhu Yan looked at Lin Ming, his sword held the entire time. He noticed the chin that was revealed outside of Lin Ming’s mask as well as Lin Ming’s two hands.

From the looks of it, Lin Ming didn’t seem too old; he seemed like someone in his twenties. At this age, he couldn’t be some peerless master, right?

Then at this time, Lin Ming suddenly began to hack and cough. He used his hands to support the lower corner of his mask. He couldn’t stop the violent coughs from continuing, and it seemed as if he would cough out his lungs.

Slowly, from between the seams of Lin Ming’s fingers, blood flowed out. Stream after stream, this was an alarming sight!

The people around Zhu Yan gulped as they saw this sight. This person was coughing so badly that he was vomiting blood.

No matter how they saw it, this person had reached the terminal stages of an illness and didn’t have much longer to live.

But at this time, Lin Ming was startled. In that instant he felt a change; there was killing intent… that had locked onto this location!

He spread out his sense and discovered that outside the restaurant was a crowd of white-clothed swordsmen approaching at rapid speed.

Wherever they went, citizens would flee in all directions as if they were running from snakes!

The goal of these white-clothed swordsmen was the little restaurant where Lin Ming was!

Chapter 1938A – Live Without Regret

If a mortal were to vomit so much blood, they would have long exhausted themselves of any blood in their body.

But this masked person seemed as if he could continue spewing blood. Then, there was only a single explanation for this, and that was that his body was regenerating blood at an unimaginable speed.

Zhu Yan could tell from Lin Ming’s chin and hands that he was an extremely young person. Yet his strength had reached impossibly high boundaries. Could even a Revolving Core master accomplish what he did?

“You… are you alright?”

Zhu Yan reluctantly said after some hesitation.

Lin Ming turned to Zhu Yan. He was no longer vomiting blood, however this wasn’t because his body had recovered but because of that bout of pain just then, his mortal body was now weak to the extreme and could no longer continue producing blood.

“Benefactor, you rescued all of our lives. I will carve this graciousness in my mind!”

Zhu Yan deeply bowed.

Behind Zhu Yan, the other people as well as the two children also bowed.

Lin Ming waved his hand, signaling for everyone to stand.

“Benefactor, do you plan on resting here or… would you like to travel with us?”

Zhu Yan said with some difficulty after looking at Lin Ming for some time. He certainly wished for Lin Ming to travel with them.

He was well aware that Lin Ming wasn’t a person of this world. As for the illness Lin Ming was stricken with, none of them could help and none of them would be able to understand it.

Lin Ming looked at Zhu Yan and then at the little prince and princess behind him. As he saw the worry in the eyes of the little princess, he slowly nodded.

“Perhaps you would like to rest here and then we can continue our journey in the morning?”

According to Zhu Yan’s thoughts, the earlier they left the better. But, he feared Lin Ming wouldn’t have time to rest.

Lin Ming shook his head. “Rest is useless to me. Let us go.”

“Well… okay.”

The group gathered their valuables and disguised themselves as a caravan. Then, they set off towards the northern desert.

They didn’t know whether it was because Lin Ming had frightened everyone, but even after journeying for hundreds of miles, they hadn’t encountered the White Guard again. They met two groups of mountain bandits, but this level of opponent was something Zhu Yan and the others could easily handle.

The road was bumpy. The little princess was listless and wan all day. After suffering malnutrition for such a long time and experiencing constant hunger and cold, her body had become weak. To travel a long-distance journey like this without stopping was unbearable for her.

She was extremely tired, but as the carriage jolted about, she wasn’t able to fall asleep at all.

As for the small prince, he was slightly better. However, as the cold northern winds blew on his face, he was also pale.

During a temporary rest on the road, Lin Ming came over to the little prince and little princess’ side, then handed a sheepskin water bag to them.

“Big brother, this is…”

The little girl was a little more familiar with Lin Ming. She opened her wide eyes towards him.

“It’s snow pear water. It’s tasty…”

Lin Ming smiled. The two children listened in delight and happily took the sheepskin water bag, each one taking big gulps of it.

They were children born and raised in the imperial palace and had drunk luxury snow pear water all their lives. But, the snow pear water that Lin Ming gave them was clearly different.

It didn’t taste sweet, but it was fragrant, far more fragrant than any top quality cooking wine in the royal kitchen. Moreover, as soon as they drank it they began to feel a little faint, as if they were drunk.

The two children only drank a little before their faces turned ruddy and they managed to fall asleep.

Zhu Yan watched all of this from the corner of his eyes.

“Benefactor, this is…”

Zhu Yan looked at the sheepskin water bag in the little girl’s hand. A little bit of liquid dripped down from it and emitted a light fragrance that warmed the heart.

This might be… a supreme medicine of the world!

This thought flashed through Zhu Yan’s mind. He had seen Lin Ming take out a pill and then dip it in the water bag before immediately taking it back out. Then the water had become a treasure medicine. If so, then the value of this pill was…

Zhu Yan felt this was unbelievable.

At this time, Lin Ming took the water bag and casually said, “You drink some too.”

“I…” Zhu Yan felt somewhat apologetic. He declined, “I’m already too old… drinking it is a waste…”

“There’s a lot of it.” Lin Ming thoughtlessly said. Zhu Yan finally couldn’t help it and received the water bag. He drank a big gulp and then felt a stream of heat pour into his dantian, causing his entire body to be warmed.

Not only was all of his exhaustion swept away but even his dantian that had remained quiet for so many years begin to stir. This sort of feeling was like his injured body being revitalized and coming back to life. He was simultaneously overjoyed but also filled with disbelief!

He had fought year after year and injuries had accumulated in his body for far too long.

Due to this, he had sought out famed doctors, and even these doctors said his wounds were impossible to cure. Zhu Yan was well aware of his bodily situation and felt that this was what his life would be like.

He never thought that this masked person would only wet some water with a medicine, and then with a single drink it would have such an effect. It was far too inconceivable!

Zhu Yan couldn’t imagine just what sort of effect there would be if he ate this pill.

Lin Ming silently wrapped up the pill and handed it to Zhu Yan. “Take it. Dip it in some warm water and you can use it to restore the hidden wounds that have accumulated in your body. It will allow you to live for several dozen more years, and can also help those two children recuperate and lay down their foundation. But, remember that you cannot eat it up directly. Otherwise your body will explode from the energy. Also, do not allow anyone to know about this pill, otherwise you will draw a fatal disaster upon yourself.”

Out of the countless pills Lin Ming had on his body, this pill had a low value and was one of the most temperate.

Zhu Yan was flustered as he looked at the pill. This was a medicine that could even stir the heart of a Divine Sea Sovereign!

He refused again and again, saying, “This is far too precious; I cannot take it. Moreover, Benefactor is injured, so you will need nourishing medicines…”

Zhu Yan didn’t understand. If this masked person has such a wonderful spirit medicine, how come he didn’t eat it?

Lin Ming sighed. He shook his head, “Even if it was a hundred times or a thousand times more precious, it would still be useless to me. Take it.”

Zhu Yan was stunned. Even a medicine a hundred times more precious was useless to this masked person?

He didn’t even have time to respond. Lin Ming simply flicked his fingers and this pill flew into Zhu Yan’s spatial ring, without Zhu Yan’s involvement at all.

To Lin Ming, who was skilled in the Space Laws, such a low level spatial ring existed in name only.

Zhu Yan looked at Lin Ming and was left speechless. He could faintly guess that such a priceless-seeming pill might be nothing to Lin Ming.

He couldn’t help but ask, “Why does Benefactor bestow such a generous gift on someone like me? If I am not wrong, then Benefactor should be a peak person in this world? However, you somehow ended up in distress here. I fear that to Benefactor, everyone here is nothing more than ants… why would you meddle in the affairs of mortals?”

When a person walked down the road and saw a group of ants fall into a puddle of water, they would rarely go and help them. Thus, Zhu Yan couldn’t understand just why Lin Ming searched for the little princess and also killed the White Guard, sending them running away. Lin Ming even gave him a pill and accompanied their group to the north.

This was all inconceivable.

Lin Ming spookily said, “This is the circle of cause and effect…”

Originally, the samsara of a mortal’s life and death was a part of the Heavenly Dao. Lin Ming didn’t want to interfere in it; however, Zhu Yan was different.

This was because Zhu Yan had become like he had today because of Lin Ming. At the same time, the trajectory of Lin Ming’s life had been greatly influenced by Zhu Yan.

If it weren’t for Zhu Yan stealing Lan Yunyue away, then Lin Ming’s current life might be completely different.

However… history had no ifs and whats. What happened was what happened.

Lin Ming and Zhu Yan. One was a person who once stood at the highest levels of the 33 Heavens, and the other was thoroughly a mortal. Yet, between these two there was a convoluted karma that bound them.

And this karma was planted the moment Lin Ming stepped onto the road of martial arts.

Today, Lin Ming had rescued Zhu Yan not to interfere with the natural samsara of the Heavenly Dao, but in order to bring their karmic circle to an end.

These were things that Lin Ming naturally couldn’t explain to Zhu Yan, and as Zhu Yan saw that Lin Ming didn’t wish to speak of it, he also gave up asking.

The two people were silent for a long time.

Chapter 1938B – Live Without Regret

The two people were silent for a long time.

Then, Lin Ming looked at Zhu Yan and asked, “The nation has already fallen, so why are you still loyal to the old dynasty? You should know that once the destiny of a dynasty has come to its end, wanting to revive it is an extremely difficult matter.”

Lin Ming felt sad for Zhu Yan. Ever since ancient times, once an old dynasty was destroyed and replaced, it rarely ever managed to stage a comeback. Even if they somehow managed to establish some semblance of political power, they would last at most 10-20 years while lingering around in a pitiful state.

Zhu Yan’s future was uncertain and perilous. Even if he tried his best until the last beat of his heart, he might not be able to produce any results.

Zhu Yan was silent. He looked at the skies. His old eyes seemed to flash with a sense of loss, as if he were recalling days gone by.

 Slowly, he said, “I am loyal to the previous emperor because of… graciousness!

“My surname was originally Zhu. Over 100 years ago… my family was prosperous and my aunt was an imperial consort. My road in life was to help the prince seize the throne, where he would afterwards appoint me to a position high in the court and where I would enjoy great wealth and riches.

“I could have been called young and talented. But it was because of this that I was stubborn and unruly, frivolous with my actions. And because of who I had been, I made a mistake… I never thought that this minor matter which was nothing in my mind would actually turn my life upside down. My life, from the highest peak, fell into the lowest abyss…

“I was defeated. Under the gaze of everyone, I lost in a fair battle. And, my opponent was much younger than I was.

“My woman left me, but it wasn’t because she abandoned me, but because I forced her away. At that time I had no choice but to do that.

“After that one battle I was severely wounded. But before I could recover, I was expelled from my family and the patriarch publicly severed all relations with me. I could no longer take the name of Zhu and even the prince thought of me like some living plague, afraid that I would negatively affect his great cause.

“Alone, with nothing but my injuries, I left my family and lord and started to roam the world…

“My future was nothing but dark gloominess. I was able to see the fickleness and changes of the human heart and at that time my life was without any rays of hope. But, I was unwilling. The young me had a heart higher than the heavens. I thought, this world is unfair to me! I hardened my resolve to break into the Xiantian realm and have all those people who doubted and betrayed me know that they were mistaken.

“I wanted to prove to myself that I didn’t need to depend on my family or anyone else, that I could fight my way through life on my own…

“I wanted to make a name for myself and return to my homeland with riches and glory. I wanted my family to know just how stupid they were for abandoning me.”

As Zhu Yan spoke, he seemed to shiver. He found it hard to maintain his calm. He took out a pot of wine from his waist and began drinking it.

He rarely mentioned these past events to anyone.

“After that, for several decades, I experienced innumerable hardships. I experienced the warmth and coldness of humans. I understood the hundred changes of the human heart. I worked as a stableman, a soldier, an assassin, a warrior, and much more. Without the protection and shelter of my family, I could only rely on myself to cultivate the martial path and I couldn’t afford to use any resources.

“For resources, I risked my life countless times to obtain them. I wanted to soar to the heavens with a single step, but it was only afterwards I realized the truth. Reality, is far… too brutal. The young me simply wasn’t strong at all. Those people that struggled with me were far, far stronger than I was, and there was a never-ending sea of them.

“This sort of competition couldn’t even be described as tragic. To lose meant death!

“Several times as I was fighting for lucky chances I received heavy wounds. However, because I didn’t have good medicines to restore my body, the hidden wounds within me began to accumulate.

“Thus, my injuries became heavier and the condition of my body became increasingly poor. As I aged, my chances of breaking into the Xiantian realm became more and more uncertain…

“Later, I accidently learned that my opponent had already reached an incomprehensibly lofty height. He entered the four Divine Kingdoms and even broke through the void with his martial path, ascending to the starry skies.

“But as for me, let alone the Xiantian realm, even breaking into the Houtian realm was difficult. The difference between us two was greater than the heavens and earth!

“Your idealistic dreams might seem wonderful, but reality is just brutally cruel. I finally realized that the young me was far too naïve. With my heart that was higher than the heavens, I was sure that I would have tremendous success in life. I thought I could return home, famous and renowned, and slap the faces of all those who spoke ill of me. But in truth, I failed to achieve any of that…

“Later I understood that there were too many people who were just like me. They all thought they were different, existences that were unique in this world. Everyone dreams of accomplishing their desires, but we… are inevitably nothing more than mortals.

“I eventually had to accept the path that destiny had arranged for me and wake up from that beautiful dream I had… because, I… was no longer young…

“During those days, although I experienced innumerable tribulations, these tribulations slowly grinded away my edges and corners, causing my character to change and become completely different from what I used to be…

“I began to learn how to restrain myself, learn how to think deeply of my actions and their consequences, learn to accept reality for what it was, learn to be grateful…

“The reason I am loyal to the old dynasty is because the first emperor, who has already passed away, once saved my life. When I was severely wounded and was on the precipice of death, he didn’t give up on me. Rather, he gave his horse to me and afterwards he even spent an exorbitant amount of money to help cure my wounds, even if I didn’t manage to cure my wounds in the end…

“So… even if the destiny of the old dynasty has been exhausted, I will still fight for it. The reason I do this is not to restore the old dynasty. I no longer desire glory or riches, and only do what I do for peace of mind once I die…”

As Zhu Yan spoke to here, his old eyes were already wet with tears. He could no longer speak.

He drank deeply and also gave his wine pot to Lin Ming.

Lin Ming felt something stirring deep in his heart. He brought the wine pot to his lips and began pouring the wine down his throat.

The warm wine, the simple sheepskin covering, the fluttering wind, the boundless desert…

As well as two people who had once known each other and fought each other. Although their lives had taken completely different paths, at this point they were two people with similar moods, seemingly watching the fading horizon…

This was a scene that couldn’t be described with words.

Somewhere, somehow, there seemed to be some inexplicable karmic cycle that brought Lin Ming and Zhu Yan, people of two completely different worlds, back together.

Men do not cry easily, but that is because they haven’t reached the source of sadness. Lin Ming didn’t know just what feeling was in his heart. He stood up, silent, welcoming the strong winds.

Whether it was mortals or the Empyreans and True Divinities that stood above all, everyone had their own suffering, their own bitterness.

Zhu Yan’s life also had its tumultuous rises and falls. Perhaps his experiences might not be worthy of mentioning to those who came from a higher realm. In comparison, Lin Ming’s experiences were great matters that concerned the continued existence of the Divine Realm.

Between these two, there were certainly differences.

But in Lin Ming’s eyes, people may be divided into the weak and strong, but when it came to suffering of the self, there was no difference.

The pain in Zhu Yan’s heart when he faced his tribulations was likely no less than his own.

Zhu Yan’s life, Lin Ming’s life, were both equal.

From this meaning, Lin Ming was also a mortal.

Zhu Yan had experienced the ups and downs of mortal life. He dreamed and hoped that he would rise in the future and strived for it, doing everything in his power to accomplish it, but in the end… he failed.

Although he failed, he clearly recognized himself and recognized his own fate. He found himself and transformed himself, finding a new faith and fighting for it.

Then what about Lin Ming?

Without seeking riches and glory, only seeking peace of mind after death.

Lin Ming quietly mulled over these words. He drank down more wine.

Currently, he despaired far more than Zhu Yan of the past. Although Zhu Yan has lost everything, he had still been young and had a life ahead of him to continue struggling for the future.

But as for himself, he wouldn’t even have his life…

He wanted to struggle, but there was no place to struggle.

But Lin Ming didn’t want to give up. Even if he died, he still wished to be at peace.

Without asking to reverse his destiny, he would only ask to live a life without regrets.

He…could die because he had lost his soul force...

But… he could not allow himself to be defeated just because he lost his soul force…

Chapter 1939 – Dispersing Cultivation

After accompanying Zhu Yan to his destination, Lin Ming left.

Placed within the vast world, Zhu Yan might be some common and unnoticeable mortal. But because of some unknown and unpredictable karmic cycle, he had appeared twice in Lin Ming’s life, and these two times were both when Lin Ming had reached his lowest point…

Lin Ming’s heart had changed. This transformation wasn’t solely because of Zhu Yan.

During these years, where he had walked, what he had seen, what he had heard, what he had felt, all of these things marked themselves in Lin Ming’s mind, changing his mood and his outlook on life.

He didn’t seek a reversal of fate. Rather, he only wished to live a life without regret…

Lin Ming no longer roamed around. He estimated that he only had 30-40 years of life left.

He didn’t want to quietly die.

In the last days of his life he would put forth one final struggle!

…..

On this day, Lin Ming arrived at a barren hill that was far off from civilization.

He used his fingers as a spear and slashed out.

With a loud explosion, a deep cave was cut open into the hill.

Lin Ming decided that from now until the end, he would go into deep seclusion training.

Perhaps there was a chance. Although this chance approached zero, he would still try his best.

If in the end he was still dying, then in the last few years of his life he would leave this barren hill and go to one last place – Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom.

He would go there and see his parents one final time. Then, he could die.

Lin Ming walked into the cave and then sealed up the entrance.

After resolving to walk down this final road, his heart was filled with determination.

And this road was the only method Lin Ming could think of to cultivate.

Moreover, the price of this cultivation was inexorably painful. It would cause Lin Ming’s strength to fall to an unprecedented valley and it would also reduce the little lifespan he had left.

The 30-40 years of life he had left to live would be reduced to 10-20 years. And this could even be called a death road!

Still, Lin Ming had to desperately risk his life.

Faint traces of the power of divinity fluctuated within Lin Ming’s body. Because of his weak fires of the soul, Lin Ming could no longer manipulate the massive amount of energy saved within his inner world. Instead, this energy had become a burden on him.

But, if he were to slowly dissipate these energies, then that was something he could accomplish.

Each time, Lin Ming could move around a thousandth of the energy in his inner world. He drew this energy into his meridians and let it scatter outwards. In other words, this was… dispersing his cultivation!

Because of his weak soul, Lin Ming could no longer bear the potency of his own cultivation. If so, then he would simply force his cultivation to drop until it reached a level his soul force could withstand!

This was a crazy decision! Dispersing one’s cultivation was itself tremendously injurious to one’s body, and Lin Ming’s fires of life were already fading away like a candle in a storm!

All of Lin Ming’s pores opened. As the source energy escaped from his body, his eyebrows tightly wrinkled together. Pure agony swelled forth from within his body.

Even so, Lin Ming’s face revealed a decisiveness and resolution that was harder than metal. His eyes seemed to contain a stubborn unyieldingness, an unwillingness to yield to the fate that the heavens had arranged for him!

As his source energy escaped, this affected Lin Ming’s essence energy.

Although Lin Ming’s soul was weak and his fires of life were nearly extinguished, his mortal body was still incredibly powerful. Once his essence energy and blood were affected, the pores throughout his body would begin to release faint streams of blood.

This fresh blood transpired from Lin Ming’s body, mixed with the power of divinity, condensing into layers of blood mist around him.

At the same time, Lin Ming’s boundary began to constantly fall.

From Divine Lord to Divine Transformation, and then from Divine Transformation to Divine Sea… all the way to Life Destruction…

This speed of falling cultivation was alarming!

If a martial artist were to disperse their cultivation like this, then that was no different from suicide!

Lin Ming’s mortal body was far too formidable. As his blood flowed out, his body constantly produced more. The mist of blood emitting from his pores scattered without end.

This blood mist dyed the ground red, dyed the walls red, and dyed the ceiling red.

Soon, the entire cave Lin Ming was in was dyed a deep blood red.

More and more blood accumulated in layers. Lin Ming’s face was pale white, but he grit his teeth and continued.

He wanted to disperse everything in a single breath, breaking himself and then standing back up from the rubble!

At this time, Lin Ming’s cultivation had already fallen to the Revolving Core realm. His face was distorted beyond recognition and his teeth screeched as he bit down tight.

Then, Lin Ming’s inner world suddenly shook and began to crack open…

A Revolving Core martial artist did not have an inner world. What they had was a dantian.

An inner world was something that began opening when a martial artist reached the Divine Sea, and when they became a Divine Lord, their inner world would turn into a microcosm. But as Lin Ming’s cultivation dropped, his inner world wouldn’t transform into a dantian. Rather, it began collapsing in on itself.

This was an even greater attack on Lin Ming. He slumped forwards and thrust his arms against the ground, his knuckles deeply embedding themselves into the rock.

He began to retch, nearly vomiting out his stomach. Almost all of his blood had been drained. This inhuman pain was something Lin Ming had to bear. He clenched his teeth and didn’t even mutter a single sound.

In his heart, a desperate unyielding spirit was struggling to survive!

And at this time, something worth feeling grateful for suddenly occurred.

That was, as his cultivation fell to the Revolving Core realm, the little bit of soul force left in his spiritual sea began to fuse together with the energy in his inner world.

In other words, Lin Ming’s cultivation had finally reached parity with his source soul force.

He could cultivate like a normal martial artist could.

He could train his soul again, train his cultivation again, moving forwards one step at a time, continuing to climb upwards…

However… there was just a little something that was different.

He was old.

The fires of life and fires of the soul of a young Revolving Core martial artist might be small and weak, but they could be grown. As for Lin Ming’s fires of life and fires of the soul, the majority had been taken away by someone else, making Lin Ming the equivalent of a person in the twilight of their years.

He had less than 20 years of life remaining. This was the same as an old person at the end of their road.

Although Lin Ming’s appearance was still young, his eyes were muddy and gloomy, and this was all because his powerful mortal body was continuing to support him.

If he hadn’t absorbed so much God Beast blood and the Asura blood, then Lin Ming feared he would have completely become like an old man on the verge of death.

An old person with his remaining 20 some years of life had to increase his cultivation to at least the Holy Lord realm. Just what was the possibility of this?

Lin Ming didn’t know, but he would continue to desperately push forwards.

Whether or not he could increase his cultivation he would still try his best to cultivate, not even wasting a single moment.

More than once he had affirmed to himself that he would be a moth fluttering towards the fire.

He had said to Lan Yunyue, had said to Sheng Mei, and had even said to himself –

“Even if I am a small and weak moth, I will walk into the flames without hesitation. I will fight my destiny for a one in a million chance that I will experience my own samsara and be reborn as a flaming phoenix…”

But, that oath had never been tested in such a tragic and brutal manner as today, where he was placed in such a hopeless death trap!

Lin Ming knew just how little hope there was on this road, but if he cultivated, there was at least a tiny ray of hope, a chance to turn everything around.

If he gave up, that would just be waiting for death.

Chapter 1940 – Understanding Life and Death

Lin Ming didn’t walk the same path of cultivation.

In the past when Lin Ming was at the Revolving Core realm he had gone to the Holy Demon Continent and the Eternal Demon Abyss to adventure. Then, he returned to the Sky Spill Continent to strike down Xuan Wuji before making a trip to the four Divine Kingdoms. After absorbing all sorts of resources, he managed to break into Life Destruction.

That sort of cultivation method was the best possible given Lin Ming’s circumstances at the time.

But to the present Lin Ming, all of that was meaningless.

All the previous cultivation methods of his past weren’t of much value to Lin Ming currently.

Lin Ming’s only hope for revival was the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra.

The Great Dao was boundless and limitless. According to Jiang Baoyun’s words, if there was a highest martial arts peak in this world then it would likely be the fusion of the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra, as well as the triumvirate of essence, energy, and divine.

Lin Ming’s life source was ruined and conventional cultivation methods had no significance to him.

His only possible path out was to search the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra for a turning point to reverse the Heavenly Dao.

However, he only had 20 some years left to live.

Day after day, year after year.

Training continued without sense of time. Soon, 15 years passed.

Lin Ming sat motionless in the stone cave.

His cultivation had paused at the Revolving Core realm and didn’t break into Life Destruction.

This was because he didn’t cultivate at all during these past 15 years. Rather, he was enlightening himself.

With his return to the mortal realm for so many years, he had seen the myriad changes and moods of mortality, and he used these feelings to become more aware of the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra.

The Heavenly Sutra that cultivated the universe of the world was in essence the Heavenly Dao and nature itself.

In the past, Lin Ming’s understanding of the Heavenly Dao had been confined to perceiving each Law, where he was limited in the 33 Great Daos.

In truth, this was already an incredibly deep level of comprehension. Let alone the martial artists of the lower realms who couldn’t even walk down the road of a single Law to its extremes, even a supreme elder of the Divine Realm would often only cultivate a single Law to the peak in their entire life. They simply wouldn’t have the good fortune to come into contact with the 33 Great Daos.

But now, the Heavenly Sutra that Lin Ming was understanding was no longer just becoming enlightened on these things.

The Laws were a part of the Heavenly Dao, but they weren’t everything.

There was much, much more.

As Lin Ming walked through the world during these years, he had seen the samsara of the Heavenly Dao, he had seen birth and death; all of this was a part of the Heavenly Dao.

The Heavenly Dao was constant, but life was forever changing. Lin Ming now possessed a deeper understanding of the Heavenly Dao.

And these understandings were all fused into the Heavenly Sutra, causing the Heavenly Sutra to include many things that it didn’t before.

It had to be known that when the Asura Road Master created the Heavenly Sutra, he had used 3.3 billion years to do so. One life one Empyrean, one life one Divinity. The Heavenly Sutra could be called broad and profound, but if one wished to add to it, wanted to fuse their own feelings and understandings into it, wasn’t that easier said than done?

But Lin Ming was boldly doing all of this. He didn’t know if what he added was right or wrong, but what he did know was that what he added was most perfectly suited to himself.

After the Heavenly Sutra was the Holy Scripture.

To the current Lin Ming, the Holy Scripture was in truth more important.

This was because the Holy Scripture that cultivated the inner universe was in essence cultivating one’s existence, cultivating one’s life. In these years, Lin Ming’s understanding of life had become more deep than it was.

He slowly savored the taste of life. It savored not only his own life, but the life of others. Suffering children, a poor aunty who set up a stall, Zhu Yan whose heart was higher than the heavens but was eventually defeated by reality and even then didn’t give up, but decided to pursue a new goal in life. And even Jiang Baoyun, who desperately chased after his goals without any hesitation…

He had seen a hundred ways of life. Now that he looked through the Holy Scripture again, his mentality had become completely different from before.

The Holy Scripture that Lin Ming obtained was in truth extremely incomplete.

He hadn’t seen the pages of death from the Holy Scripture. When Sheng Mei had given Lin Ming the duplicate copy jade slip of the golden pages, their content had been that of the pages of life. Moreover, as a mere copy, there was inevitably wrong information in what was recorded.

As for the black book that was recorded in the Holy Scripture and was now in the Soul Emperor’s hands, Lin Ming hadn’t even seen it.

The pages of death from the Holy Scripture were even more mysterious. If Lin Ming wished to enlighten himself on the Holy Scripture like this, it was an impossible task. After all, Lin Ming hadn’t even lived for 200 years.

However, Lin Ming truly did become aware of some things.

Of course, the things he comprehended weren’t as deep and all-encompassing as what would be written in the pages of death. Still, as long as he could perceive things that were most suited to himself, that was more than enough.

This was because currently, Lin Ming was experiencing death!

He could watch as his own fires of life faded more and more with each passing day, and could feel death arriving closer with each moment. He could even clearly hear the footsteps of the grim reaper coming for him.

To understand life and death on the verge of oblivion, there was no situation that was more profound than now!

In fact, even the creator of the Holy Scripture didn’t manage to thoroughly comprehend death. The Art of Eternal Life that he established also had its flaws.

At the very least, the creator of the Holy Scripture didn’t manage to obtain immortality.

Perhaps, this might have been because the creator of the Holy Scripture hadn’t experienced the despair of witnessing his own fires of life dimming down with each day. That creator had never experienced what Lin Ming was feeling now…

To understand the Heavenly Dao and perceive life and death.

Lin Ming sat motionlessly in the cave.

Dust fell over his body.

Like this, three more years passed.

Lin Ming’s fires of life were now a candle in the wind, seeming as if it could be extinguished at any moment. However, Lin Ming’s face was like a rock sculpture, lacking any emotion at all.

His heart was calm to the extreme.

In this absolute silence, Lin Ming quietly comprehended the Holy Scripture’s pages of death.

He wanted to thoroughly understand death and then seek out life from death.

He had far too many matters left unfinished…

His life passed. Lin Ming’s eyes became increasingly cloudy with each day. His eyes were like the Soul Emperor’s eyes in the past. After opening them, the cataracts were so pronounced that he nearly lost his sight.

His mortal body remained as formidable as it was before. But because of his feeble soul, he lost control over his own body.

He could no longer move his lower legs…

Lin Ming was silent. He had been sitting cross-legged on the ground for all this time, and now he could no longer feel his calves.

This sort of feeling, or lack of feeling, slowly spread upwards.

As if he were being petrified over time.

From his calves, next was his thighs, his waist…

Currently, Lin Ming truly was like a statue. If his soul were to completely die away at this time then his life would have reached its end.

But his mortal body would remain behind, not rotting even after 100,000 years.

Gradually, Lin Ming lost all feeling in his chest. Even the movement of his arms slowed down.

Although his heart was still beating and blood was pumping through his veins, it wasn’t something controlled by Lin Ming at all.

Death had never been this close.

Still, he didn’t manage to find a way to live through comprehending the pages of death.

All of this was just far too difficult!

Even if Lin Ming’s foundation was solid to the limit, even if he had experienced the ups and downs of life, had seen the myriad states of humanity, had become thoroughly aware of his own life…

Even then, wanting to find a way to live from the threat of certain death was as difficult as ascending to the heavens!

“How hateful… if only I was given another hundred years to perceive, if only I could use the Magic Cube….”

Lin Ming was unwilling. He didn’t want to die through the depletion of his soul.

If he could use a divine instrument of the soul like the Magic Cube, then although it wouldn’t cause Lin Ming’s fires of life to blaze brightly once more, he could still use it to stabilize his spiritual sea and slow down the collapse of his inner world.

Lin Ming could feel that his days were numbered; he didn’t have much time left remaining. If things continued like this then he absolutely would not be able to find a turning point in his own fate.

However, he didn’t want to give up like before. He called upon the tiny bit of soul force left remaining within his body and poured it into his collapsed inner world where it would flutter towards the Magic Cube.

In Lin Ming’s fragmented inner universe that was filled with holes everywhere, the Magic Cube floated in space. This space was deathly still, with massive spatial cracks spreading out in all directions.

A tiny, imperceptible stream of soul fire flew out from the space crack and towards the Magic Cube. This was nearly all of the little bit of soul force that Lin Ming had left remaining.

This tiny trace of soul force was infused with the entirety of the feelings that Lin Ming had realized. He poured in his complete understandings of the Heavenly Dao samsara that mortals encountered. He added in everything he had learned about the samsara of life and death.

This was the fruit that resulted from Lin Ming’s last 20 years of cultivation.

The weak bit of soul fire fluttered towards the Magic Cube and then disappeared into it.

Like a tiny stream converging into a lake, there was no change at all.

The Magic Cube continued to revolve in that shattered space, spinning as it did before.

Lin Ming quietly waited. What he waited for was death, or perhaps a miracle.

His mind was as still as a placid like. Even though he could sense his source soul force weakening with every day, even when he couldn’t operate the Magic Cube, he still maintained his calm and quiet expression from beginning to end.

Lin Ming felt his heart tighten. If he were to fail here then that was the will of the heavens and the fate of those who live and die.

If he died here, then that would be a part of the Heavenly Dao samsara.

If humanity was on the decline and would eventually be annihilated by the saints and the spiritas, then this was simply the will of the heavens. In the long river of history, there had never been a race that was glorious until the end of time!

Time silently passed. Lin Ming’s heart reached an unprecedented state of clarity.

He recalled his life.

In his short several dozen years of life, he had experienced glory, had experienced despair, and had shown nothing but disdain for any rivals who dared to challenge him. In the end, he even made a saint True Divinity unable to remain calm. But in the end, he had come to such a result?

As Lin Ming recalled his life, he heard a light sound.

This impossibly weak sound seemed to be from his inner world sympathetically resonating with him. This caused Lin Ming’s nearly dried up spiritual sea to slowly tremble!

This was a never before seen degree of clarity!

He could see that in his inner world, the Magic Cube was lightly trembling!

This trembling was weak, but Lin Ming could immediately feel a warm and loving soul force. This soul force was connecting to his own spiritual sea, and was even related to the Magic Cube!

However, Lin Ming’s current soul force was far from enough to open the Magic Cube.

Thus, he was surprised to hear an elderly voice echo in his ears.

“Lin Ming… it’s been a while since we last saw each other…”

This sound was…

Lin Ming was stunned.

This was Empyrean Divine Mist!

In the past, Lin Ming entered the Asura Road and was forced into Tragic Death Valley by Tian Mingzi.

In Tragic Death Valley, he met Empyrean Divine Mist. Empyrean Divine Mist showed Lin Ming graciousness by teaching him.

Because Empyrean Divine Mist had been trapped there for so many years, he had consumed a great deal of his soul force and didn’t have much time left remaining. Thus, Lin Ming sealed his soul into the Magic Cube where he could rest deeply. Lin Ming hoped that there would be a day in the future when he could help Empyrean Divine Mist restore his vitality and remold his soul. Although Empyrean Divine Mist might not be restored to his situation from the past, Empyrean Divine Mist hoped he could still live out the rest of his natural lifespan.

After that, Lin Ming fell into a slaughter of life and death. Because of humanity’s great calamity and the fact that Empyrean Divine Mist had fallen asleep in the Magic Cube, he had never thought of a day when Empyrean Divine Mist would awaken…

Chapter 1942 – Restoring the Origin

“Senior Divine Mist, please lend this junior a hand one more time…”

Lin Ming was unable to activate the Magic Cube on his own; he needed support from Divine Mist’s strength.

Empyrean Divine Mist manifested into a dim figure within the Magic Cube. He looked at Lin Ming and said, “Alright.”

To refine someone else’s source soul force wasn’t easy at all. But if Lin Ming were to use the Magic Cube to do this, it would be far more simple.

When Lin Ming sucked the source soul force left behind by Sheng Mei into his own spiritual sea, he didn’t feel any backlash come from it.

It slowly fused into Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, becoming part of it.

This point left a hundred different tastes percolating in Lin Ming’s mind. Perhaps this was because Sheng Mei consciously made this decision; perhaps this was because Lin Ming’s soul had fused with Sheng Mei’s, but no matter what the reason was, Lin Ming’s spiritual sea and Sheng Mei’s spiritual sea now shared an inexplicable relationship with each other.

For a time, memories swelled towards him like waves, all of these memories containing Sheng Mei’s comprehensions of the Holy Scripture’s pages of death.

These experiences and feelings fused with Lin Ming’s own comprehensions of death, a little at a time…

Slowly, Lin Ming’s soul immersed itself in the Magic Cube. With the nourishment of the Magic Cube he began to understand death.

His soul had already reached the edge of complete exhaustion. But because of the Magic Cube, it didn’t collapse.

And this condition continued for a long time.

Over time, Lin Ming’s hair began to wither. The sockets of his eyes deepened, his skin grayed, and his pupils were no longer black but had lost all color.

Lin Ming now lived on the precipice of life and death. His eyes had lost their sight and his breath nearly disappeared, as if he would die in the next moment.

But as Lin Ming reached this unprecedented border of death, his understandings of the pages of death also reached a new peak.

This process continued for a month.

Late one night, Lin Ming’s unbelievably weakened fires of life finally extinguished.

His heart stopped beating…

In that moment, all of the life activity in Lin Ming’s body had stopped.

He experienced true death.

The truth was that the moment Sheng Mei drew out Lin Ming’s source soul force, Lin Ming was doomed to die. This was an irreversible road.

His soul weakened year after year. It was no longer possible to restore his ruined vitality and dwindling fires of life. His body was like rotten wood, having lost all life.

But…

Even dead wood could bring forth new growth.

However, even though dead wood could summon new growth, an old tree was still an old tree. A lush new branch and leaf could bring a bit of green to dead wood, but it could never restore that tree to the true vibrant vitality of a small newborn sapling. And, it was even more impossible for that dead wood to grow up as a towering new tree.

Lin Ming was now in such a situation. To have his current mortal body and spiritual sea glow with the light of rebirth was something that violated the Heavenly Dao rules, just like an old man on the verge of death becoming rejuvenated and being restored to his youth. This was simply impossible.

But, there was one possible situation. That was…

If the new shoot that grew from a piece of dead wood could absorb all the nutrition from that old tree and then take root in the ground, then it could truly grow into a towering tree that reached into the skies.

Break everything down to nothing and then stand back up tall – this was an eternal truth.

If one could simultaneously comprehend the Holy Scripture’s pages of life and pages of death to the extreme, then the truth was that this was equal to comprehending the most core cultivation method within the Holy Scripture – the Grand Reincarnation Art.

Reincarnation, that was the process of returning from death to life.

Contained within this technique were the secrets of life and death. If one couldn’t comprehend them then not only would their reincarnation fail but anyone that tried cultivating the Grand Reincarnation Art would perish into dust, forever disappearing from the world.

What Lin Ming did now was the equivalent of stepping into the first revolution of the Grand Reincarnation Art.

The first revolution should have been simple. But, since Lin Ming was doing all of this with his utterly ruined body, it was the same as gaining a new lease on life. This technique became far, far more difficult.

Lin Ming’s dead mortal body remained silent. His spiritual sea lost all vitality and his inner world was already covered in horrifying fissures and had become a devastated land.

This process continued for several days.

Then, Lin Ming’s mortal body began to decay.

His skin wrinkled and dried out. His blood vessels shrank. His organs started to rot.

Originally, with Lin Ming having opened the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace and having absorbed the bloodlines of many God Beasts and also the Asura blood, with such a powerful mortal body, even if he died his body still wouldn’t have decayed after 100,000 years.

But now, not only was Lin Ming’s mortal body decaying, but it was decaying at a speed visible to the eyes, as if hundreds of years were compressed into quarter hours of time.

The reason this occurred was because all of Lin Ming’s flesh and blood essence had been drawn out and gathered into the Magic Cube.

With all the essence energy screened out, all that was left remaining was a mortal body that had lost all vitality; the speed of decay would naturally be faster.

And as Lin Ming’s mortal body decayed, his withered spiritual sea and sundered inner world started to thoroughly collapse. For a time, two avatars appeared beside Lin Ming’s dilapidated body. These two avatars were Lin Ming’s essence energy avatar, the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone, and the soul force avatar, the Soul Springs Divine Embryo.

The two avatars were motionless. These two avatars were under the control of Lin Ming’s true self. With the true self’s soul force completely withered away, Lin Ming had no mental strength to command them.

Besides the two avatars, there was also a black dragon egg that was covered with snaking patterns. This dragon egg slowly shimmered, one moment light, one moment dark. An intensely potent fluctuation of life blazed within this dragon egg, seeming to be closely connected to Lin Ming’s body…

Seeing this dragon egg, Empyrean Divine Mist was stunned.

“This is…”

He faintly felt that the moment Lin Ming’s flesh and blood essence began to gather, the vitality within this dragon egg seemed to gather with Lin Ming’s own vitality.

The small life within the dragon egg was finally ready to emerge!

Empyrean Divine Mist didn’t have time to probe what was occurring. At this time, Lin Ming’s mortal body finally completely withered away and all of his flesh and blood essence gathered itself into the Magic Cube.

Besides Lin Ming’s flesh and blood essence, the phantom of a Heretical God Tree that was emblazoned with fantastical runes also flew into the Magic Cube.

A vivid True Dragon phantom, True Phoenix phantom, Bodhi Tree phantom, Asura war god phantom – all sorts of phantoms flew into the Magic Cube, one after another…

At the same time, Lin Ming’s body shrank more and more. Finally it rotted away into nothing and even the bones eroded.

And in the air above this ruined body, the Magic Cube slowly floated. At the place where all the essence was gathered, a dazzling divine light shined. Within the dark cave it was like a sun was dawning, incredibly beautiful!

This sphere of divine light constantly changed. Finally, it converged within the space of the Magic Cube. The energy also gradually solidified until it formed a cocoon. In the center of this cocoon, one could faintly make out a small embryonic life form that was slowly breeding.

However, this life form was even smaller than a baby in a mortal mother’s belly. It was only the size of a palm and looked extremely fragile.

This was Lin Ming’s body after rebirth.

Empyrean Divine Mist witnessed all of these changes, his mind quaking all the while.

This was truly what it meant to break down everything and then stand back up. Lin Ming had completed the first revolution from death to life of the Grand Reincarnation Art.

Because Lin Ming had been on the verge of death, this reincarnation was far more thorough. Compared to the Grand Reincarnation Art of Sheng Mei and the Soul Emperor, his first revolution likely far exceeded theirs.

To have such an effect was because Lin Ming had begun walking down his own road. He didn’t totally depend on the pages of life and pages of death from the Holy Scripture alone, but had instead added in his own understandings.

What he felt and had become aware of after wandering the world for dozens of years, the samsara of the Heavenly Dao, all of this was completely fused with the Grand Reincarnation Art, allowing him to find a road to reincarnation that suited him the most.

“Lin Ming… perhaps you might be the only one in history…”

Empyrean Divine Mist quietly mumbled. In the past, Empyrean Divine Mist believed that if Lin Ming could become a character similar to the Asura Road Master, then that would be the greatest achievement he could ever obtain. But now, Empyrean Divine Mist had a faint premonition that because Lin Ming had risen from the ashes, rebirthing himself through reincarnation, then there was a chance that he could establish his own road of martial arts in which he could fuse together the inner universe and the outer universe, climbing up to an unprecedented peak of martial arts that no one had ever managed to reach!

From this day on, Lin Ming was completely different from in the past.

Chapter 1945 - A Single Life (2)

Lin Ming played with the small black wolf. He frequently accompanied his parents and enjoyed their love and doting. Sometimes he would go off by himself and ride a horse upon the grasslands, recklessly galloping about.

He was like an ordinary child, enjoying the pleasures of childhood.

This sort of happy and comfortable life which was filled with the warm love of his parents was a pleasant current that cleared away Lin Ming’s mind.

He had wandered the world for too long and had experienced far too many things. He had exhausted himself far too much and needed to experience such a life to dilute all that had happened to him.

At eight years of age, Lin Ming entered the Lin Academy that was established by the Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom.

The Vermilion Bird Divine Kingdom had only existed for a short period of time. Although they had prestige and resources, they were actually sorely lacking in talent.

In order to find talented individuals, the Vermilion Bird Divine Kingdom first set up a grand martial artist meeting as well as the Lin Academy. With the martial artists school section of the academy, they could raise outstanding martial artists on a massive scale and form all sorts of factions.

The front gates of the academy had a hundred foot high statue of white jade standing tall. This statue was of Lin Ming in his twenties.

The Lin Academy had been founded a mere 150 years ago yet it had already become the most infamous martial arts school in the entire Sky Spill Continent.

Old Man Good Fortune as well as the Divine Kingdom’s Guardian Holy Beast, Demonshine, both held positions as honorary deans at the Lin Academy. In the academy there were Divine Sea powerhouses that personally taught the students.

It was even said that the Guardian Holy Beast Demonshine would occasionally lecture. It was rumored that these teachings could only be encountered through a stroke of luck.

Regarding this, Lin Ming was left speechless. He simply found it hard to imagine what it would look like for a silly dog to be teaching others…

Because of the Lin Family’s fame, not only were great figures from the Sky Spill Continent willing to gather here, but all sorts of heroic young elites from the central mainland wished to enter the Lin Academy and were proud and honored to do so.

The threshold to enter the Lin Academy was extremely high. Many chosen prides of heaven were eliminated in the entrance examinations.

Lin Ming was personally recommended to enter the Lin Academy. Within the Lin Academy he possessed a special status.

However, his presence didn’t arouse too much happiness.

If it really was a disciple of the Lin Family then no one would object to them enjoying extra privileges. After all, the entire Sky Spill Continent was saved by Sage Lin, and Lin Ming had rescued countless Divine Sea powerhouses from being killed by Yang Yun.

The Lin Family descendants were perfectly justified to have such privileges. But, the key problem was that Lin Ming, who was now known as Lin An, was not a descendant of the Lin Family but had been adopted.

People thought that he didn’t have a single bit of relations with Lin Ming, nor did they think he was the reincarnation of Lin Ming. They only believed he was a baby who had been abandoned and then luckily adopted by the Lin Family.

Everyone was the same, so why did he get to enjoy special privileges? Let alone the common people, even disciples of the Divine Kingdoms’ royal families wanted to enter the Lin Academy, but they all had to go through the examinations no matter who they were. Only Lin Ming, who was so favored by the Lin couple, was able to use resources however he wished. Other people certainly weren’t willing to see such a sight.

“Lin An, Lin An, how come you keep skipping classes? What are you doing? This lessons is one of the most crucial classes concerning how to revolve energy in your dantian. If you don’t complete the course how will you make up for it later?”

A green-clothed young girl panted in indignation at Lin Ming. This young girl had run a long distance and had finally managed to find Lin Ming.

She had a long ponytail and wore the uniform of the Lin Academy. Her trousers were long and her sleeves were pulled high. Her figure was busty and full, filled with the energetic vibrancy of youth.

At this time, Lin Ming was comfortably lying down on a green lawn, a stalk of grass in his mouth. He slowly chewed on it, recalling his memories of childhood.

A small black wolf quietly sat beside him. This small black wolf was extremely peaceful. Its large and pitch-black eyes were gazing at this young girl.

This year, Lin Ming was 15.

In the past when Lin Ming had left Green Mulberry City, bid farewell to his parents, and reached the capital city, he had also been 15 years old.

It was that year when Lin Ming and Lan Yunyue broke up, and he began his difficult road of martial arts.

Seeing this young girl, Lin Ming faintly smiled. He couldn’t help but recall the youthful spring of his past life. At that time, it was like this, ah…

He didn’t reply. Rather, he continued chewing on the grass stalk.

The grass stems of the early spring were tender. When biting one, there was a trace of bitterness as well as a faint sweetness, like the perfect representation of his youth.

The young girl appeared upset. She curled her lips and flung up her ponytail. “You can’t keep doing this. Even if there are people spoiling you it doesn’t mean you can get away with whatever you want. It is impossible for you to separate yourself from the road of martial artists. If you don’t try your best, no one can help you.”

This young girl that was only 15 years old began to speak of the great principles of living.

Lin Ming thought this was quite funny. In truth, not everyone was unhappy with his presence at the Lin Academy.

Some people liked him.

For instance, girls.

After Lin Ming’s rebirth, his appearance had become even more handsome and there was a certain temperament around him that was beyond description. His eyes were bright and fathomless, seeming as if they contained a trace of the changing years, leaving those that looked into them fascinated.

Many girls spoke endless praise of Lin Ming, even if Lin Ming seemed to be an unmotivated student who didn’t make much progress.

“You’re really noisy.” Lin Ming spat out the grass stalk and jumped up. The current him seemed to have recovered the rebellious nature of his childhood and now he had perfectly fit into playing that role.

Only by completely adapting to the present could he see more from this perspective and look at his entire life.

“You…” The young girl flushed red with anger.

And at this time, Lin Ming had already left with a smile.

“Where are you going?”

“To class!”

Lin Ming walked away. The young girl stamped her feet, clenched her teeth, and followed him.

Lin Ming really was going to class, but what he was attending wasn’t one of the important courses concerning martial arts, but one of the minor classes created by the Lin Academy so that students could increase their knowledge in other areas.

Every teacher had class on fixed days, but they didn’t have fixed times.

This class was set outside on this sunny day. It taught the history of the Sky Spill Continent. It taught about the 100,000 year riddle of the Sea of Miracles, the Demon Emperor’s appearance, the rise of the four Divine Kingdoms, and even Yang Yun’s treachery and defeat.

Lin Ming came to this class because the one teaching it was special.

Her name… was Lan Yunyue.

Wearing a dress the color of moonlight, a woman looking around 30 years of age walked up to the podium. Her bearing was graceful and elegant and she seemed like a remarkable person. She looked down from her platform, staring at the students that sat in groups of two and three.

After Lin Ming killed Yang Yun, Lan Yunyue had also gone to the Vermilion Bird Divine Kingdom. She lived with the Lin Family, and afterwards when the Lin Academy was founded, she joined as a teacher.

Her cultivation was at the Xiantian realm. Of course, she had relied on pills to forcefully raise herself to this level. She didn’t wish to teach martial arts, thus she chose to teach history instead.

As Lan Yanyue’s gaze swept over the class, her eyes finally fell upon a youth that was sitting beneath a tree.

Seeing this youth, Lan Yunyue didn’t know just what to feel.

Every time she came to teach class, she would subconsciously search for this youth. And, this youth had never missed a single day of her class.

They really did look alike… in particular, those eyes and that uncertain something that seemed to come from somewhere deep in his blood…

How could there be such a wonderful coincidence in this world?

Lan Yunyue shook her head. Then, she took out a thick history book from her spatial ring…

…

In the summer, there would be a survival course in the wilderness. The students of the Lin Academy would go into a forest filled with vicious beasts where they would temper themselves for a month.

In this forest, while the teacher responsible for watching over the students wasn’t paying attention, Lin Ming slipped away.

Moreover, when he ran away, he ran far indeed.

He left the Sky Spill Continent and arrived at the Holy Demon Continent.

The Holy Demon Continent was on the other side of the Sky Spill Planet. Many Divine Sea powerhouses now knew this secret and there was even a transmission array established between the two continents.

As Lin Ming went he brought the small black wolf with him.

His destination was the Eternal Demon Abyss.

“Little Black, today I’m going to bring you somewhere. I already told you about it, do you remember…?”

Lin Ming’s voice suddenly took on a serious tone.

Before, as he was dying, or when he had just completed his reincarnation, or even when he hadn’t grown up, he simply didn’t possess the ability to bring the small black dragon to the Eternal Demon Abyss.

Now during his first new life, a considerable portion of his strength had returned and he now possessed the ability to do so.

Although Lin Ming’s cultivation wasn’t high, his true strength couldn’t be decided by cultivation alone. Even the greatest Divine Sea powerhouses of the Sky Spill Continent weren’t able to see through the mysteries within him.

This was because Lin Ming’s dantian was not a dantian but the inner world of a peak Holy Lord master who was soon about to enter into the World King realm. This far exceeded the understanding of the martial artists of the Sky Spill Continent.

Thus it was now that Lin Ming brought the small black dragon to revisit the Eternal Demon Abyss. Here, he would answer to the Dragon Sovereign.

Chapter 1946 - A Single Life (3)

Lin Ming didn’t know what the Dragon Sovereign’s present situation was like. After he was chased by Tian Mingzi into the Eternal Demon Abyss and when he left, the Dragon Sovereign had already been in a precarious state.

In just the blink of an eye, over a hundred years had passed. How was the Dragon Sovereign doing now?

When Empyrean Primordius left, he seemed to have severed all connections with the Dragon Sovereign. Then, if Empyrean Primordius had perished, it was likely the Dragon Sovereign hadn’t felt it at all.

The little black dragon was extremely intelligent. It already understood the entire situation, and at this time, it lay quietly on Lin Ming’s back, not even making a single noise.

In its eyes, there was nothing but a boundless black wilderness. And at the end of this wilderness there was a terrifyingly giant abyss that revealed a dreadful aura.

In the little black dragon’s eyes, a trace of confusion appeared.

Within its memories, it seemed to faintly recall this place.

As if it had seen it before in a dream.

“Let’s go…”

Lin Ming said. He flushed forwards like a shot arrow, rapidly crossing thousands of miles. He headed towards that massive abyss and leapt down into it.

Darkness rapidly passed over them. With familiar ease, Lin Ming avoided the ancient life forms in the demon abyss and swiftly passed through the tombs of the martial artists until he arrived at the deepest depths of the Eternal Demon Abyss.

Faintly, Lin Ming could feel an incredibly horrifying aura transmitting from deep within the Eternal Demon Abyss.

The small black dragon was a bit nervous. Its large black eyes blinked. There was anticipation in its eyes but also a hint of fear.

One person, one dragon, the two of them slowed down. Then they felt a boundless vigor that carried with it faint and warm threads of a dragon’s majesty.

A planet-sized ancient black dragon slowly appeared in the dark void. As Lin Ming and the little black dragon flew in front of it, they seemed as small as motes of dust.

And on this giant ancient black dragon’s body, nine chains wrapped around it. Each chain was thick enough that not even a hundred people together could wrap their arms around it. At the end of these chains were massive metal hooks that plunged into the black dragon’s flesh, binding it in place.

Where these metal hooks came into contact with the black dragon, the area would be stained with black dragon blood and pieces of meat. After 100,000 years, this blood had solidified into thick layers of black and brown that alarmed the mind.

Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath. Although he had seen this before, seeing it again still left him depressed and filled with sorrow.

As for the little black dragon, as it saw this sight its eyes began to fill with pain and sadness. Its large and bright eyes started to turn wet with tears.

“Senior, junior has returned…”

Lin Ming bowed. The silent black dragon slowly opened its eyes. The dragon’s pupils were like lakes of amber that emitted a quiet light. In the darkness they were especially noticeable.

When the black dragon opened its eyes, the little black dragon also held its breath.

At this time, the little black dragon was in an extremely complex mood. There was fear, there was sorrow, and from deep within its bloodline, there was an inerasable love…

“200 years…” The black dragon slowly said. It looked at the small life in front of it. The growth of a dragon was a long process. This little black dragon only appeared to be a dozen or so years old. When converted to the age of a human, this little black dragon was nothing more than a newborn baby.

Then, it looked at Lin Ming. Lin Ming’s changed appearance and his lowered cultivation left the black dragon surprised.

From Lin Ming’s inner world, from Lin Ming’s potent vitality, from Lin Ming’s deep soul force, it could feel a terrifying potential!

“You… seem to have obtained a new life?”

The black dragon asked, unsure.

Lin Ming nodded. He let out a sigh in his heart. He could tell from the black dragon’s voice that it had become far, far older than before. Its fires of life were nearing their end and it was doomed to never be able to return to the heaven-shaking grandeur it once possessed in the past.

Lin Ming thought for a moment and then decided to tell the black dragon everything about Empyrean Primordius.

“Lord Dragon Sovereign, junior went to the Primeval Universe and met the primal god race. There, I also discovered the whereabouts of Senior Primordius…”

The black dragon was stunned upon hearing this. “Primordius! You saw him, he…”

Seeing Lin Ming’s expression, the black dragon had a foreboding feeling deep in his heart. He didn’t continue speaking but instead waited for Lin Ming’s explanation.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and explained everything that occurred to Primordius from start to finish, even describing what Primordius’ final moments were like.

After hearing this, the black dragon was wordless for a long time.

Perhaps what happened was the best possible result for Primordius. It might have been what Primordius hoped to see…

A hundred different emotions passed through the black dragon’s heart. It looked at Lin Ming, looked at its descendant, and fell into silence.

Suddenly, light began gathering between its eyebrows.

Within the Eternal Demon Abyss, the surrounding heaven and earth origin energy started gathering towards the black dragon’s single horn.

Seeing this, Lin Ming was bewildered. “Senior black dragon, you…!”

From the black dragon’s body, Lin Ming could feel all of its essence energy and flesh and blood essence gathering towards the point between its eyebrows.

Lin Ming seemed to faintly realize what was occurring. He asked, “Senior, just what are you planning to do?”

And at this time, a beam of light shot out from between the black dragon’s eyebrows. It shot directly onto the small black dragon that was beside Lin Ming. As the little black dragon was bathed in this light, it cried out in alarm and surprise.

It only felt that the energy within this light was warm beyond possibility, so comfortable that it wanted to sleep. But it also felt that something wasn’t right. However, it inevitably wasn’t able to withstand the increasing heaviness of its eyelids and it slowly shut its eyes, nearly falling asleep.

“Lord Dragon Sovereign, did you just give your life essence to Little Black?”

Lin Ming was worried. The black dragon’s life force had originally been greatly diminished to begin with. If it lost any more life essence then it would perish that much sooner.

In fact, the black dragon might not be able to wait for Lin Ming to grow and gain enough strength to shatter apart the nine dragon trapping cables laid down by the saint race powerhouses in the past.

The black dragon remained silent as it continued passing life essence. Only when Little Black was no longer able to absorb any more did it finally stop.

In the next moment, the little black dragon was wrapped in a black brilliance. It sank into the void and began sleeping.

After doing all of this, the black dragon seemed to age, becoming much older. Its eyes became bleaker and more clouded. It looked at Lin Ming and the corners of its massive jaw seemed to lift up a little in a smile. “I know what you are thinking. You probably hope that I can wait long enough until you can fight with an ordinary Empyrean and then break open these dragon trapping cables to rescue me.

“The truth is… you don’t have to waste so much effort or thought. I, have already become used to staying here. These dragon trapping cables have deeply pierced into my organs and for the last 100,000 years they have grown together with my flesh and blood, becoming a part of my body. They even affect my essence energy and blood vessels. Once they are forcibly removed, I fear I will die immediately.

“But if they aren’t taken out, they will slowly eat away at my life, causing me to lose essence energy until the day I die…

“Right now, I am the same as Primordius in the past, living in constant pain, calmly awaiting my demise.

“If I must die, then I don’t want to die without meaning. What Primordius wished to do, what he wished to leave behind, I am also the same. To see my bloodline live on in the world, that is more than enough for me…”

As the black dragon spoke to here, it affectionately gazed at the small black dragon slumbering deep in the void. It said, “Help me take care of him. He is the continuation of my life…”

The black dragon’s last few words touched the deepest emotions within Lin Ming. Because, he had also said words like these…

When Soaring Feather hunted him down, when his life was in peril and death was almost certain, he had asked Xiao Moxian to look after the child in her belly, because that child was a continuation of his life…

This was the instinctive response of a person in desperate circumstances.

Man was always unwilling to die.

But man would die no matter what.

As a person approached the precipice of death, they would hope that they could leave behind something.

So that when they closed their eyes one last time, they could tell themselves that their bloodline continued flowing on in the world…

This intense desire, if traded for another name, could be called ‘fatherly love’ and ‘motherly love’.

The love of parents. In essence, that was one’s hope that one’s life would continue to exist onwards.

This was a selfish love, but also a selfless love.

A parent’s love never asked to be repaid, because to them, their children living well was the greatest repayment they could ever receive.

Looking at the sleeping little black dragon, looking at the utterly exhausted Dragon Sovereign, Lin Ming seemed to have become aware of something new.

He found another manifestation of the samsara of life and death. Children, parents, the love of parents, these three things revolved around life and death…

He fell silent.

The Dragon Sovereign told Lin Ming of his hope. He wished that every hundred years, Lin Ming would bring Little Black to the Eternal Demon Abyss. Lin Ming agreed. Although he knew that this would reduce the Dragon Sovereign’s remaining lifespan, this was also the Dragon Sovereign’s greatest desire…

The little black dragon slept for a full three days in the darkness. After three days, Lin Ming brought the little black dragon and left the Eternal Demon Abyss, returning to the Sky Spill Continent once more…

Chapter 1947 - A Single Life (4)

By the time Lin Ming had quietly returned to the Sky Spill Continent and arrived at the dark forest near the Lin Academy, 25 days had passed. There was still five more days until the conclusion of the forest survival course.

On this day, heavy rains washed down upon the forest. In the summer this sort of warm and humid forest often had pouring showers.

In the boundless waterfall of droplets, Lin Ming scratched his head. He was planning to sneak into the forest without being noticed and then make up an excuse to rejoin the group. But, he couldn’t come up with a good reason.

As he had a headache from thinking of a reason, he discovered that in the Lin Academy’s forest, there were a massive number of soldiers wandering about.

These soldiers all wore the same silver patterned war armor. Even in the heavy rain and in the thick underbrush, they still retained their strength and their movements were as flexible as a leopard’s; they were a well-trained elite unit.

These soldiers each had a cultivation at the Xiantian realm or above.

It had to be known that if a Xiantian realm martial artist was placed in a small sect they would be considered an Elder. Yet in Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom, they were nothing but soldiers.

These soldiers weren’t part of the common military corps, but were part of the Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom’s Silver Armor Legion. Many graduates of the Lin Academy entered the Silver Armor Legion to adventure and gain experience, and the Silver Armor Legion also produced many famous powerhouses.

This legion was under the direct control of the Lin Family, and was considered one of the Lin Family’s sharpest blades.

Normally, they weren’t easily used. But now these people had launched a massive search through the heavily raining forest, combing every inch of the land. They shouted out for ‘Prince An’; it was clear they had been searching for Lin Ming for several days already.

Seeing this, Lin Ming was a bit dazed.

This matter seemed to have gotten a bit out of control… in truth, there was still five more days until the survival course ended. He never thought that the Lin Family would use the Silver Armor Legion to search for him. This was likely because they thought he had been captured or even eaten by some vicious beast in the forest…

And to mobilize the Silver Armor Legion, it was certainly his parents who had commanded this. They were worried for his safety and thus sent out the Silver Armor Legion.

Lin Ming braced himself and walked out from the woods.

“Prince An! Prince An is over there!”

As a silver-armored soldier saw Lin Ming, he was immediately overjoyed and began to shout out as loudly as he could. In a moment, many silver-armored soldiers rushed towards Lin Ming, gathering around him in a circle.

A man wearing golden armor and with a great red cape thrown over his shoulders strode forwards. He had thick eyebrows and was towering with broad shoulders.

This man was the leader of the Silver Armor Legion – Zhou Yutian.

Zhou Yutian was the Lin Family’s son-in-law.

He possessed a variation bloodline and was considered one of the top talents of the Sky Spill Continent. He came from a small family background, but afterwards he was admitted into the Lin Academy due to his amazing talent and obtained extraordinary results there. Later, he was even crowned champion of the grand martial artist meeting and was finally taken in by the Lin Family as their son-in-law.

After Lin Ming and Lin Xiaoge ascended, Lin Ming’s parents had three more children. The one who married Zhou Yutian was Lin Ming’s second sister, Lin Ping.

“Prince An, you’ve been deliberately stirring up trouble…”

Seeing Lin Ming safely return, Zhou Yutian didn’t know just what to say. “Prince An, do you know how worried Madame was in these past days? She’s been too worried over you to even drink or eat, afraid that something might have happened to you. Do you know how dangerous the forests around Lin Academy are, just how many perils lurk in the dark? In the depths of this forest there are ferocious vicious beasts that even Destiny Decree masters are unable to deal with. You can’t do something like this again!”

Zhou Yutian sternly admonished.

Lin Ming was a bit ashamed of himself. Normally, the character he displayed was that of a boy who loved to play around. He feared that his parents probably thought he ran deep into the dark forest because he was being mischievous.

Lin Ming could only apologize.

He was escorted back by the Silver Armor Legion. As for Lin Mu, she had obtained the news and stood at the entrance of the dark forest. She didn’t sit in her carriage but stood beneath it, anxiously looking around while a maid held up an umbrella for her.

The heavy rain came down, crashing onto the umbrella with ringing sounds. Lin Mu’s bangs were already matted to her forehead; she was too worried.

As Zhou Yutian had said, in these past days Lin Mu wasn’t able to sleep at all.

All mothers of the world were like this. The more they worried over their children the easier they thought something bad had happened.

Seeing his mother wait in the rain, Lin Ming felt his heart ache a little. He had truly been anxious to see the Dragon Sovereign but he was too young and it was impossible for him to be allowed to go adventuring. He had to take advantage of this opportunity to head out once, but he never thought his mother would be so worried about him.

He ran forwards to help support the umbrella for his mother.

“Little An, you’ve caused too much trouble this time…” Lin Mu scolded. But although she had a harsh expression, her eyes were filled with kindness and worry.

“Little An, are you hurt anywhere?”

Lin Ming shook his head. He resolved his heart that for this life, he would accompany his parents until they reached the end of their road. He would take care of them until old age, until the end of their natural lives…

…..

Like this, the stormy commotion ended. Lin Ming thought that this minor matter would quickly be forgotten.

But, reality turned out differently.

Because of this matter, rumors began to appear within Lin Academy and the Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom.

The approximate content of these rumors was that the Lin couple had spoiled Lin An too much. Lin An himself was nothing but a useless black sheep, a wastrel who ruined his family’s good name. He had a pitiful background and possessed no good points, and what was most disgusting was that he skipped all his classes and caused trouble all day long.

During the survival course in the dark forest he had caused a mess, completely ruining the survival course for everyone else!

If an ordinary student of Lin Academy were to have some problem during the survival course, the academy simply wouldn’t do anything at all and would sum it up as a death due to training. This sort of thing happened every year at Lin Academy and several students would die.

But, Lin An had only been missing for 20 some days and this was enough to cause the Lin Family to mobilize the Silver Armor Legion to search for him. This used up military resources and was simply making a massive fuss over nothing. Even the academy survival course was terminated early.

The survival course had only gone on for ten days. As for the missions assigned by the academy, only a very small number of people were able to complete them. This made it so that 99% of the students weren’t able to obtain any good results.

The students of Lin Academy were incredibly unhappy with such an ending. Just who did Lin An think he was? He wasn’t even related to the Lin Family to begin with; he was nothing but a bastard abandoned by his birth parents!

His talent and cultivation were the same as an average person’s. In normal times, he would be nothing but a punk with no good points, a street rat wandering the city.

The Lin couple not only took in such a bastard child but even allowed him to arrogantly do whatever he wished, doing all sorts of evil and nasty things. Not only was he not discipled but the Lin couple even dragged in others to search for him.

This was a clear case of injustice. It caused the Lin couple’s prestige to be greatly affected.

Some people even privately said that the Lin couple were nothing more than common citizens who had never seen the wider world before. If they hadn’t luckily given birth to their amazing son Lin Ming, then they would have already died and turned into white bones.

Even now, people were filled with thoughts that the reason they occupied their seat was only because of Lin Ming. They felt that the Lin couple shouldn’t interfere with the Vermilion Bird Divine Kingdom and that they shouldn’t have the right to mobilize the forces of Vermilion Bird Divine Kingdom. They should just look for some nice and quiet place to retire.

These discussions, either intentionally or unintentionally, passed to Lin Ming’s ears.

Lin Ming frowned. During this life, his original intentions were to accompany his parents. While he honored his parents, he wanted to experience their fatherly love and motherly love, becoming more aware of the samsara of life and death.

He didn’t think that his careless actions would cause his parents to be criticized.

“Really, wherever there are people, there will be struggles. I just wanted to be a prince that didn’t try to seize power, but it seems that someone has targeted me…”

Lin Ming didn’t care what others said about him, but he wouldn’t tolerate his parents being harmed.

Perhaps he should consider giving suitable honor to his parents so that they wouldn’t be criticized.

He went to look at the Lin Academy’s rankings. In order to encourage students and push them harder, an array formation stone tablet was set up in the academy’s back mountains. The most outstanding students of every class had their names engraved into the stone.

In addition, the Lin Academy had done something similar to the Seven Profound Martial House and had created many examinations. The record holders of these examinations would also be written in the rankings.

These rankings were looked upon by many students every day. Motivated students would even come over a dozen times a month.

As for Lin Ming, he had never looked before.

Today, he came to take a look. A name caught his eye. This person was called Situ Mingyue.

This name seemed to be a girl’s and it often appeared on the rankings. This was because she maintained several current rankings and even had a record high.

“Situ Mingyue?”

Lin Ming was curious. Another person named Situ. Those of the Situ surname often possessed a variation dantian and extremely high levels of talent. Could it be…

Lin Ming casually asked one of the students standing in front of the ranking list. “Who is this Situ Mingyue?"

The student looked a bit unhappy to be asked this question by Lin Ming, but he didn’t dare to not reply. He said, “You haven’t even heard of Situ Mingyue? ...She is the most splendid student from the third class and is Situ Yaoyao’s little sister, Situ Yaoyue’s niece!”

This student’s words confirmed Lin Ming’s guess. It seems he wasn’t wrong.

Situ Yaoyue was a genius from the Asura Divine Kingdom. She possessed an Extreme Violet Dantian and was skilled in the Darkness Laws. She was crowned the most talented junior of the Asura Divine Kingdom’s younger generation.

When the Asura Divine Kingdom chased Lin Ming into the Forsaken God Clan and forced Lin Ming into a continuous battle, Lin Ming had faced opponent after opponent until he encountered Situ Yaoyue.

Although Situ Yaoyue was a woman, she grasped the Great Desolate Blood Halberd and engaged Lin Ming in a fierce battle. They had fought to a near standstill but in the end Lin Ming had relied upon his body transformation technique to defeat her.

Although Situ Yaoyue at the time was older than Lin Ming by many years, it was still amazing for her to accomplish what she did.

As for Situ Yaoyao, she was Situ Yaoyue’s little sister and also possessed an Extreme Violet Dantian. When Lin Ming returned to the lower realms in the past, he had seen Lin Xiaoge battle against her. In truth, Lin Xiaoge wasn’t able to suppress Situ Yaoyao, but Lin Xiaoge was finally able to win due to the foundation she established because of all the precious medicines used on her. Only through a competition of endurance did she win. From this point, it could be said that Lin Xiaoge had actually lost to Situ Yaoyao.

Now, Situ Yaoyao actually gave birth to a daughter. And it was clear that this daughter also possessed an Extreme Violet Dantian. This Situ Family really possessed far too many talents and the Extreme Violet Dantian was passed down like this.

As for himself, he seemed to have a fate with the Situ Family.

Chapter 1948 - A Single Life (5)

As Lin Ming studied in Lin Academy, the rumors continued to spread.

If Lin Ming let loose his divine sense he could easily hear many people criticizing him.

Others said that the Lin couple condoned the overbearingly cruel and domineering acts of their adopted son. These discussions became increasingly fierce, even rising to the level of the Vermilion Bird Divine Kingdom’s ruling class.

This surprised Lin Ming. A matter that he didn’t think was important to begin with seemed to have been purposefully stirred up and controlled by someone behind the scenes in order to guide public opinion.

Was someone targeting him?

Lin Ming immediately thought this. After living for several generations of mortal lives, he would think more about everything, even things like this. Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom was after all the number one Divine Kingdom of the Sky Spill Continent, and those in power enjoyed the greatest authority of the entire continent as well as control of rich resources. If someone appeared that touched upon the benefits of these people, it was reasonable for these kinds of scenarios to appear.

The situation became increasingly complex.

But at this time, from the ruling class, someone stepped forwards to control the rumors. They started from several different points until the rumors began to gradually die down.

Although some people were dissatisfied with Lin Ming, they had never been so blatant in their actions.

The one helping Lin Ming was Vermilion Bird Divine Kingdom’s Eastern King, Lin Xiaodong.

Lin Xiaodong was one of Lin Ming’s good brothers from his youth. When Lin Ming parted from Lan Yunyue, Lin Xiaodong had looked after him.

After Vermilion Bird Divine Kingdom was founded, everyone that was close to Lin Ming, including his parents, Lan Yunyue, and Lin Xiaodong, all came here.

Lin Xiaodong was given the title of King. During his youth he often accompanied his parents in business and possessed some skill in politics and communication. In addition to him being brothers with Lin Ming and their close relationship, very few people in court dared to offend him or speak out against him.

While Lin Xiaodong wasn’t too strong himself, he had raised some guests that were masters. They were at the Life Destruction realm and some of them even ranked on the Destiny Decree. Thus, Lin Xiaodong became someone that was able to summon storms and rains in court and possessed a considerable amount of clout.

“You little brat, why don’t you try to fight to give your parents a little face!”

Lin Xiaodong saw Lin Ming in his own palace and punched him in the chest.

In these 200 past years, Lin Xiaodong had put on a great deal of weight. He wasn’t tall to begin with and with his large elephant-like legs, he resembled an egg. Because of his stomach he couldn’t even see his own toes.

He maintained his health well and married three wives and had dozens of concubines. These concubines all had good cultivation backgrounds.

In addition, he also had many maids serving him. This caused him to have droves of descendants. Currently, he had over 40 sons and over 30 daughters.

He whacked Lin Ming’s chest and ruffled his hair, looking like an elder teaching a junior. His eyes weren’t large to begin with and in addition to his fat stature, his eyes disappeared into slits when he smiled. He looked like a shady 30-40 year old businessman.

This left Lin Ming utterly speechless. He couldn’t help but recall that in the past, Lin Xiaodong had been a little brother that followed his rump wherever he went. Now, Lin Xiaodong had become Lin Ming’s elder and Lin Ming even had to call him ‘Uncle Dong’.

Of course, Lin Xiaodong called Lin Ming’s parents aunty and uncle, thus the generational rankings between them had gotten a little chaotic. But Lin Xiaodong didn’t care much about this. No matter what, he didn’t want a hairless little baby boy like Lin Ming to call him big brother.

In these past years, Lin Xiaodong had taken good care of Lin Ming. This was because Lin Xiaodong always felt that Lin An bore an uncanny resemblance to Lin Ming from the past.

After Lin Ming was lectured by Lin Xiaodong he left the Eastern Palace. He naturally didn’t want his parents to be sucked into the vortex that was the struggle for power, thus he restrained himself a little and started to attend classes in earnest.

On this day, the survival course in the dark forest was to begin once more. Because Lin Ming went missing last time the survival course was cancelled and many people weren’t able to obtain any results.

This survival course was considered a make-up exam.

After the tempering in the forest began, many people entered into the dark forest in groups of two or three. However, Lin Ming went in by himself.

He aimlessly walked through the dark forest, casually killing some small vicious beasts.

The edges of the dark forest had many low level vicious beasts and these vicious beasts were all divided into further ranks. Hunting and killing vicious beasts of different ranks corresponded to different scores. In 30 days when the survival course ended, if one could obtain a high enough score, then they would be assessed as having passed the survival course.

If one’s performance was outstanding then their results would be graded from good to great to excellent depending on their score.

Every year in the dark forest, those that passed only amounted to half the number of students. Most were good, several were great, and there was often only a single excellent student score.

Lin Ming’s plan was to obtain a score that was somewhere between good and excellent. He wanted to give his parents some face but didn’t want his results to be too world-shocking.

But at this time, he heard a loud cry in the forest.

He looked deep into the forests and saw a young girl fighting with a blue-eye poison toad.

This blue-eyed poison toad was one of the deadliest vicious beasts in the dark forest. By killing one, a student could obtain one of the necessary conditions to earn an ‘excellent’ score.

Lin Ming recognized this young girl. She was Situ Mingyue.

During this year’s survival course, the only one who could reach the ‘excellent’ rank would be Situ Mingue.

She was extremely similar to a young Situ Yaoyue. She wore purple clothes and her stature was high. Her legs were long and slender and her skin seemed as luminescent as pearls, creamy and flawless. Although her expression was cold, she didn’t give off the feeling of an unapproachable icy woman. Instead, she emitted the light demonic charm of an enchantress, making others feel strange upon looking at her.

Even when fighting the blue-eyed poison toad, Situ Mingye was calm, as if she were completely blended into her surrounding environment.

Lin Ming and the Situ bloodline shared considerable karmic bonds. He had completely destroyed Situ Minyue’s nation – the Asura Divine Kingdom, and even several elders of Situ Mingyue had died in that catastrophe.

Situ Mingyue’s aunt and mother were Situ Yaoyue and Situ Yaoyao. These two women were originally the proudest heavenly daughters of the Asura Divine Kingdom. With the support of a Divine Kingdom behind them, their futures should have been limitless.

But because the Asura Divine Kingdom was destroyed, Situ Yaoyue and her sister were left to fend for themselves.

From being proud daughters of heaven they had fallen from their high perch in the clouds, becoming miserable royal daughters of a defeated kingdom. The difference in status had been too great.

The Asura Divine Kingdom could be said to have offended many people. Situ Yaoyue and Situ Yaoyao were beautiful in appearance and possessed an abundance of talent, thus they were desired by some Divine Sea powerhouses. Some people wanted to receive them together and because of this they struggled for a long time.

From this aspect, it wasn’t too far off to say that the Lin Family had a grudge with the Situ Family.

After rounds of violent combat, Situ Mingyue finally killed the blue-eyed poison toad.

In the dark forest, her entire body was matted with blood and green mucus. Her chest lightly heaved up and down. It was clear that striking down such a powerful vicious beast had exhausted a good portion of her strength.

Ca!

Situ Mingyue thrust out her sword once more, piercing through the blue-eyed poison toad’s heart to ensure its demise.

After she confirmed that the blue-eyed poison toad was truly dead, she turned around and coldly stared at Lin Ming. She had long ago discovered Lin Ming but didn’t care much about it. She squatted down and quietly sliced open the blue-eyed poison toad’s pustule-covered skin. She reached into it and plucked out a fist-sized monster core. This was a token proving she had killed the beast.

Then, she looked at Lin Ming.

Lin Ming could see a hint of hostility and contempt in her eyes.

Although the Situ Family had fallen in these past years and had atoned for their mistakes in the past, everyone had to admit that the Situ Family produced amazing geniuses in every generation and that their bloodline was amazing!

Lin Ming didn’t know that Situ Mingyue had always had an obsession in her heart. Because of Lin Ming, her nation had been destroyed. So, while she naturally hated the Lin Family, she was well aware that it was impossible to overthrow them. Thus she was hoping to frontally defeat a disciple from the Lin Family’s direct descendants and earn back some pride for the Situ Family.

It had to be known that in the past, Situ Yaoyue had lost to Lin Ming and Situ Yaoyao had lost to Lin Xiaoge.

They were suppressed by the Lin Family.

But when Situ Mingyue was finally born into the world, when she wanted to defeat the juniors of the Lin Family and gain some honor for her mother, the talents of the Lin Family were actually on the decline, as if they would fall apart at the first blow.

Besides Lin Ming and Lin Xiaoge, the Lin Family didn’t produce any more extraordinarily talented individuals. Even with the support of resources, the disciples of the Lin Family often only had ordinary achievements.

Because Situ Mingyue couldn’t find battles she could fight, she felt as if she were punching against empty air.

She had hopes that Lin An would be a little bit fiercer. This fellow looked alike to the Lin Ming that had ascended to the Divine Realm, so their natural talents should be at least a little bit similar.

While defeating Lin Ming was impossible, defeating Lin An would be more than enough. There were even some people that said Lin An was Lin Ming’s reincarnation.

However, she was left disappointed once more. Lin An was simply nothing more than a playboy young master, a bag of trash. She couldn’t summon even the slightest bit of interest to fight him.

Situ Mingyue put away the monster core in her hands and turned to leave. But at this time, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. He looked far off into the distant depths of the dark forest.

Situ Mingyue couldn’t feel it, but Lin Ming had discovered something strange in the air.

A high level vicious beast was approaching!

For such a high level vicious beast to appear in the dark forest, this was absolutely a disaster to the students of Lin Academy!

How could this be?

By any reasoning, Lin Academy should never have made such a mistake, allowing such a terrifying vicious beast to kill its way into the forest.

Moreover, there was something off about this…

This vicious beast was extremely fast. At this distance, the teacher sent to secretly protect him should have already discovered the change in situation. But how come there wasn’t any response?

Could it be…

Lin Ming frowned. He swept out his sense and discovered something else. This something else caused his face to darken completely.

Lin Ming’s mental strength was incredibly formidable. It was so powerful that he could easily pierce through this high level vicious beast’s spiritual sea. There, within the vicious beast’s spiritual sea, he discovered a martial artist’s spirit mark!

In other words, this high level vicious beast was being controlled by someone else. It was a high level martial artist’s contract beast!

There was someone controlling this vicious beast to enter the dark forest and kill people.

And now, looking at the direction the vicious beast was headed in, it was sent to kill either him or Situ Mingyue. As for who it was sent to kill, Lin Ming could easily guess this when he recalled the matters with the rumors earlier.

“So there is someone who wants to harm me. They worry that my parents favor me too much and will give more precious resources of the Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom to me. Are they afraid that even supreme authority will be passed down to me?”

Chapter 1955 – Lin Ming’s World

Energy grew stronger. Lin Ming’s body burned like a sun. The rays of light constantly transformed around him, finally forming a rainbow-colored sphere of light behind him.

This sphere of light gradually evolved, becoming a massive phantom.

The phantom was extremely blurry, as if it were formed from gathered fog. But even in the violent and crazy space storms it didn’t scatter at all.

Lin Ming’s closed his eyes. His clothes flapped around him and his hair flew upwards.

The phantom behind him continued to change, finally becoming a giant cuboid.

This was a thick and ancient book.

This ancient book slowly opened, revealing a completely blank interior.

But in the next moment, an invisible character began to emerge from nowhere, as if an invisible pen were writing on the paper.

Then, the second character, the third, fourth, fifth, more and more characters were written at an increasingly quick pace…

All of these writings appeared in either black or gold. If Sheng Mei were here, she would discover that these words contained the Concepts of the golden pages and the black book, but there were faint differences between them.

Lin Ming’s books of life and death had been born from the Holy Scripture, but he had added in his own comprehensions.

The phantom of this ancient book became increasingly clear. More and more words appeared within it.

These words starkly contrasted gold and black, simple and plain and yet containing a meaning that was difficult to name. They were simply impossible to understand.

Rather, it should be said that these words had no definite meaning at all. They only contained different kinds of Concepts. When different people read these words they would each come away with a different understanding.

Even Lin Ming was unable to accurately explain these words.

This was equal to the total comprehensions of his 400 some years of life. The same life, but different feelings, this invisible pen was the unknowable fate of life…

The ancient book was slowly written. This process continued for several days. Finally, the pen of fate fell one final time.

In that moment, this ancient book bloomed with the brilliance of a world, as if all the light in the universe was being gathered towards this ancient book!

This was an ancient book that belonged to Lin Ming, a self-created Great Dao book that would allow him to climb to the peak of martial arts!

For a time, a horrifying vortex of energy formed. A massive amount of interstellar matter was sucked into this vortex. With the ancient book as the central point, the Great Dao aura in the surrounding space was condensed to the peak.

A universe’s physical matter, heaven and earth origin energy, Heavenly Dao Laws, when these three things were joined together they were in truth the essence, energy, and divine of a universe!

Lin Ming used his strength to gather them, purifying them, leaving only their essence behind!

He had already comprehended the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra and understood how the Great Dao rules of many worlds revolved. He knew that when a universe’s matter, energy, and Laws were completely gathered and essence, energy, and divine were gathered, one could breed a brand new world!

When the Asura Road Master and the Holy Scripture creator established their own world, they had laid down their own world Laws and had used their transcendent methods to gather material and energy and then manifest their own world!

Currently, Lin Ming was walking down the same path as the Asura Road Master and the Holy Scripture creator!

This was a bold move. Rather, one should call it a crazy attempt!

This was because the Asura Road Master and Holy Scripture creator had only created their own world when they had become renowned throughout the universe and their strengths had reached incomparably powerful levels.

As for Lin Ming, he wanted to walk down this road as he broke into the World King realm.

In the dimension of the lower realms where the power of the Laws was weak and small, where matter was lacking, where energy was barren, to accomplish this here was already Lin Ming’s limit!

Slowly, beads of sweat formed on Lin Ming’s face. Blue veins popped up on his forehead.

He stared blankly on as right in front of him, a world began to slowly appear in its elementary form.

In the past when the Asura Road Master and Holy Scripture creator created their own worlds, these worlds were stable to the point where they were could exist for billions of years or even hundreds of billions of years, able to stand side-by-side with the universes of the 33 Heavens!

Lin Ming naturally couldn’t achieve this. Even if he created his own world, it would collapse in a few dozen or a hundred some years.

But that didn’t matter. The world he created now was only in its elementary form. Through the increasing influx of power and his own rising boundary, he could have this world continue to evolve and consolidate without end.

In the future, if Lin Ming became an Empyrean or even a True Divinity, it was impossible to estimate just how large this world would grow to.

This was a world that was constantly evolving, constantly developing.

And at this time, Lin Ming’s strength had already reached a limit. If he relaxed the energy flow even just a little bit, it would cause the essence, energy, and divine of a universe that he gathered to falter and collapse, completely disintegrating.

If this were to happen then Lin Ming would likely suffer a backlash from the energy and be heavily wounded.

He let out a deep bellow and summoned the power of Asura blood within him!

Black scales covered Lin Ming’s body. His blood vitality billowed like beams of light, boiling without end!

Behind him, a tall and overwhelming black Asura phantom appeared. This Asura phantom was 1000 feet high with thick chains that twined about its body, its entire being wrapped in dragon-thick muscles!

A phoenix danced above its right arm and a True Dragon wrapped around its left arm!

It stepped on nine stars. Together with Lin Ming, it held onto this newborn elementary world.

This Asura phantom was the power that Lin Ming cultivated, formed from pouring in the power of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, the strength of the Heavenly Sutra, and the blood of a True Dragon and Phoenix!

This giant Asura pushed forwards with the momentum of a grinding pan. It slowly pushed against this newly born world, causing the essence, energy, and divine of this world to condense and condense again.

With his own comprehensions of the books of life and death as the foundation of this world, with the Asura Laws stabilizing and restraining it, Lin Ming had done everything he could to their limits.

When his strength began to reach the point of exhaustion once more, he started to burn blood essence through the Gate of Life.

Then, this world finally began to slowly condense.

It was too small – a mere several miles in radius.

Moreover, the structure of the world was highly unstable. Even an attack from a Divine Sea powerhouse could cause the system of essence, energy, and divine within this world to collapse and be destroyed in an avalanche of failure.

After completing the creation of this world, Lin Ming had used up every ounce of energy in his body. His gaze was absorbed as he looked at this world, as if he were looking at this own child.

At this moment, Lin Ming was fervently excited. He had done it!

This was a world that belonged to himself, the beginning of a brand new start!

From this day on, a new epoch had begun in his road of martial arts.

At this time, the Asura phantom pushed this world and thrust it directly into Lin Ming’s body.

The world rapidly shrunk. It overlapped with Lin Ming’s inner world.

In that instant, within Lin Ming, this newly created world’s essence, energy, and divine superimposed with his own essence, energy, and divine. This world slowly fused together with Lin Ming’s inner world!

For a time, red clouds tumbled throughout space. Paths of life and death, the sound of the Great Dao, all of it swirled in the starry space, creating a strange image that continued to change…

And Lin Ming, in that moment, had finally broken into the World King realm!

His World King realm had an essential difference from the World King realm of other martial artists!

He had created a world which could grow and evolve.

Currently, because the world Lin Ming had fused into himself was too small and weak, the strength that he had gained from breaking into the World King realm wasn’t some drastic leap upwards. But as time passed, the world Lin Ming contained within himself would continue to expand. It would hold planets, galaxies, and eventually become a universe of its own. At that time, the strength Lin Ming possessed would be unimaginable.

Lin Ming sat cross-legged in the void, meditating for several hours of time. After he restored a part of his strength, he took a single step out into the void and vanished.

Lin Ming continued to tear through space, using void shift after void shift.

Three days later, a blood red planet appeared in front of Lin Ming.

This planet didn’t have the least bit of life; it was a lifeless dead planet. But, this planet itself contained a massive amount of precious materials and also possessed an incredible trove of world essence energy.

The volume of this star was nearly ten times that of the Sky Spill Planet. Its diameter surpassed 200 million miles.

In the past 100 some years as Lin Ming wandered through this lower realm, he occasionally saw this planet and had noted its position.

Originally, Lin Ming had worried about needing to refine a world when he broke into the World King realm. He thought of searching for an upper level world to refine.

But finally, Lin Ming had dropped this idea. This was because there wasn’t a single world that could truly satisfy Lin Ming.

Now, Lin Ming had created a world of his own. Although he couldn’t refine this massive planet before him, he could actually draw in its essence energy and use it to reinforce and strengthen his own world.

Lin Ming flew towards this planet. He broke into the atmosphere like a rapidly falling meteor.

Bang!

With a terrifying explosion, Lin Ming crashed into the planet!

Lin Ming continued to drill inwards, sinking further and further into the depths of the planet. From the outer layers of the planet where it was dirt and rock, the surroundings became increasingly hot the further in he went.

Rock turned into billowing magma.

Lin Ming didn’t care about this degree of heat. He continued to pierce through. At this time, the pressure also increased.

This pressure pushed down on Lin Ming’s mortal body, causing explosive popping sounds to occur.

Lin Ming didn’t seem to care at all. He raced all the way into the deepest parts of the earth – that was, the core of this planet!

Here was no longer magma. Rather, it was a giant core formed from rare minerals and metals.

These metals and minerals were extremely good materials for forging weapons. They were formed in the massive natural furnace that was this massive planet and had been tempered under high temperature and pressure for billions of years. This was a massive trove of treasure.

It was extremely solid and had been melted into a near liquid form by the high temperature. Lin Ming plunged in, continuing to race towards the deepest part, withstanding everything to get there!

Lin Ming took a deep breath. Even If his mortal body was incredibly powerful, it still wasn’t easy for him to resist such an environment.

He let loose his mind and sat in meditation. Slowly, he began drawing in the planet’s essence energy. All of the essence energy converged into Lin Ming, nourishing the true world he had created…

The growth of a world was a long, long process. So for a long time, Lin Ming could absorb essence energy from this planet to nourish his world.

Chapter 1956 – The End of the First Life

50 years.

100 years.

200 years…

Looking at the boundless universe above the planets, one could see the changing stars. But, the truth was that they never changed. They simply traveled along trajectories that cycled with the mystical rules of the Heavenly Dao.

In the evolution of a planet, several hundred years was far too short, to the point that there wouldn’t be any changes at all.

However, in this universe, there was a giant red planet that had been experiencing world-shaking changes in the last hundred years.

In the beginning, it was a young and hot planet. Its surface was covered with active volcanoes and it had an atmosphere rich in pure heaven and earth origin energy.

However, as time passed, its heaven and earth origin energy began to thin. The volcanoes that dotted its surface began to erupt one last time or gradually die down.

As if the energy of the star had started to dry up.

In the following 50 years, this planet experienced numerous earthquakes. Massive fissures started ripping through its surface and from these deep valleys that were hundreds and thousands of miles deep, lava slowly flowed out.

After another 50 years, even the lava leaking out from these cracks started to cool. Fewer and fewer volcanoes erupted and the landscape of the planet started to dry up.

This was the sign of an aging planet.

Such a silence was maintained for another 50 years. On this day, the planet began to violently shake!

This trembling surpassed any previous earthquake and any previous volcanic eruption.

Rumble rumble rumble!

The earth tore open and an alarmingly titanic fissure appeared. It was like a divine god was using a pair of hands to break apart the planet!

Beneath this great pressure, burning hot magma and rare liquid minerals and metals gushed out, forming several hundred mile high waves that impacted into the heavens.

Beneath these rough waves, a person’s shadow rushed out.

From the raging sea of fire, his muscles reflected a dim red light and metallic luster. His dark long hair hung to his ankles, wrapping around his body like a silk cocoon.

Besides his hair, his entire body was naked. His figure could be called perfect. His torso, his arms, his legs, his neck, all were formed in beautiful and powerful symmetry.

Each muscle, each line of his body, was perfect, as if it were a work of art sculpted by some master.

This person was Lin Ming.

Over 200 years ago, Lin Ming had entered this planet to quietly cultivate. He breathed in the energy of the planet, nourishing himself.

As Lin Ming calmly cultivated, the evolutionary history of the planet that should have lasted for billions of years was quickly reduced to a mere few hundred years.

From young, it became old.

In exchange for the planet’s decline, Lin Ming’s inner world became more stable and developed further.

As the massive amount of world essence energy gathered into Lin Ming’s body, his inner world grew to over 20 miles in size. He had reached the standard of most World Kings, and if his inner world grew any more, he would grow increasingly strong.

Lin Ming didn’t stop. His figure flashed through the void and he tore open space, rapidly flying away.

After this period of journeying, Lin Ming reentered the Sky Spill Planet and spent 10 more years beside his parents.

After that, in the tearful eyes of his mother, Lin Ming set out once more, flying into the depths of the universe.

On the road of cultivation he didn’t stand still.

He recalled the position of another planet. This planet was smaller but the grade was higher.

And most importantly, there were no living beings on this planet; it was a dead star. Otherwise, if Lin Ming drew out all the essence energy from such a planet then all life living on it would die.

Lin Ming arrived at his destination in another 10 days.

This was a metal planet. It wasn’t too large and was almost entirely made of different metals and minerals.

Because this planet was too close to a sun, it was extremely hot. Even some metals melted away, forming molten streams, rivers, lakes, and even oceans.

Lin Ming’s figure flickered and he rushed into the metal planet.

He began to absorb the essence energy of this world once more.

From a World King to an Empyrean, this was originally a long, long process.

Even a top genius like Emperor Shakya had to use a full 10,000 years to complete this step.

Lin Ming was already over 600 years old.

And his cultivation at the World King realm had just begun. The road of martial artist he chose was countless times harder than any other martial artist’s road of cultivation!

A self-created fusion of the real world and inner world, to cultivate the universe of the world and the universe of the body, to meld together the Heavenly Sutra and the Holy Scripture!

No matter how profound Lin Ming’s comprehensions were, no matter how solid his foundation was, it would require an incomparably long time for him to break into the Empyrean realm.

He would even be slower than most Divine Realm geniuses.

Currently, he had yet to complete his full book of life and death. If he wanted to fuse in the Asura Heavenly Dao, the difficulty of this was unimaginable. From the overlords of the ancient era to now, no one had ever managed to complete such a magnificent feat.

Cultivation passed without sense of time.

The road of martial arts was incredibly lonely. During long periods of seclusion, one had to withstand this loneliness. One had to make their heart and mind as calm as placid water…

Although this sounded simple, people weren’t rocks after all. If a mortal were to be shut into a small black room without light, without sound, without anyone else, then they would feel as if they were going crazy in two or three days. If they were locked in for two or three months, then their mind would shatter and they would thoroughly fall into insanity.

Martial artists weren’t like this. Their minds communed with the heavens and earth, with the universe, taking the Heavenly Dao Laws as a companion.

Lin Ming absorbed the essence energy of the planet for a long time.

He completely let loose his sense, pondering on this life without any distractions, reviewing the roads he had walked down…

Over a hundred years later, the energy of this planet also began to dry up.

This time, Lin Ming didn’t take as long. This was because his inner world had grown larger and he was able to absorb the energy of the world at a faster pace.

Then, Lin Ming roamed the universe. He used the world energy of the universe to nourish his own inner world.

And after he absorbed the essence energy of a planet, Lin Ming would return to the Sky Spill Planet and accompany his parents for some time.

Like this, time passed…

Every time Lin Ming returned, it would be after dozens of years or even a hundred years of absence.

He saw his parents grow older.

Wrinkles slowly appeared and climbed up their faces. The wear and tear of time quietly carved itself upon their appearances.

Each time Lin Ming returned, they wouldn’t have changed too much. But after so many times, Lin Ming’s parents had already turned from the appearance of a young couple in their thirties to a middle aged couple in their fifties.

Lin Ming suddenly felt that even though he returned here for this life, he hadn’t spent much time with his parents.

As if this was the fate of a wanderer.

Even if his parents lived lives much longer than a mortal, at the same time, the gaps of time between Lin Ming’s return were also much longer than the lifespans of a common mortal.

If so, then the truth was that this was essentially the same.

If his parents could live to 1600-1700 years of age and he returned only every 60 years, then in the future the number of times he would return to see them could be counted on his two hands. But, Lin Ming had no other choice. Every time he absorbed the essence energy of a planet he couldn’t stop halfway, and he had far too many things he had to shoulder.

In a brightly lit room, the windows and lattices were painted with red lacquer and the wooden bed and furniture emitted a fragrant scent.

This seemed a bit similar to the arrangement of the Lin Family’s restaurant in the past, but the materials used to form everything were far more precious.

This was his parents’ bedroom.

And to the side of this bedroom, there was an old willow tree. When Lin Ming first established the Vermilion Bird Divine Kingdom and Lin Fu and Lin Mu moved there, they had personally planted this tree.

Now, this old willow tree had grown from a small seedling to a towering tree over a hundred feet in height. Its roots were as thick and tangled as dragon claws and the bark was aged and thick.

In a cool spring breeze, the branches and leaves swayed in the wind. Leaves fluttered down from time to time, falling onto a stone table set beneath the tree.

Here, Lin Ming was playing chess with his father.

Every time Lin Ming returned he would join his father in playing chess and drinking wine. As for Lin Mu, she would make a few simple dishes and the three people would eat a family reunion dinner.

This time was also the same.

In the Divine Realm, Lin Ming had eaten up countless heavenly materials, and many of these materials and medicines possessed the most outstanding tastes in the world.

Even within the lower realms, within the Vermilion Bird Divine Kingdom, there could be food made from all sorts of peak materials. Great chefs of the imperial palace would use true essence as the stove fire and use spiritual spring water to cook, making precious dishes that overflowed with drool-worthy fragrance.

But, there was no food that possessed the special flavor that of the dishes that his mother cooked.

This wasn’t just taste, but a kind of taste, a kind of memory. These were traces left behind from Lin Ming’s past.

Almost a thousand years ago when Lin Ming was a child, he loved eating these dishes at the Lin Family restaurant.

Even now, he was the same.

Even across such a long time, Lin Mu didn’t forget the types of food that her son liked to eat. Similarly, Lin Ming didn’t forget the flavors of these dishes.

“Little An, when do you plan on bringing back a wife? Your mother has no other wishes in life…”

Lin Mu often rambled on. Suddenly, Lin Ming felt sad.

He could feel that his parents’ fires of life had begun to weaken.

His parents were not martial artists and it was impossible for them to cultivate to the Divine Sea realm where they could live for 10,000 years. They had prolonged their lives with all sorts of heavenly materials, and now they would soon reach their limits.

After that, they would grow old and die of old age.

This was a Heavenly Dao rule that no one could change.

……

Time flowed by. Another 400 years passed.

Lin Ming’s parents had grown even older.

If compared to ordinary mortals, they would be around 70 years of age.

Their backs had begun to bend over and more wrinkles appeared on their faces. Their eyes became dirty as they stepped into the twilight of their lives.

Seeing that his parents didn’t have much time remaining, after Lin Ming returned, he didn’t plan to leave anymore.

He wanted to accompany his parents and spend the final years of their lives with them.

This was also to bring this first new life of his to a full completion.

Although the Grand Reincarnation Art could allow a person to live nine new lives, it didn’t have the heaven-defying ability to lengthen a person’s life by nine times.

It could reforge a person and give them the light of a new life. But, it couldn’t extend the total lifespan of a martial artist. Ultimately speaking, it wasn’t the Law of Eternal Life, but only a cultivation method created by the Holy Scripture creator after he comprehended the Concept of Life and the Concept of Death to their limits, created in order to draw out one’s potential to its maximum.

Thus, Lin Ming didn’t think about how long he could live out this life. He needed to complete his reincarnation as soon as possible.

Chapter 1957 – Returning Home

Sky Fortune Kingdom, Green Mulberry City –

Aged architecture, pedestrians of all kinds, sweet and savory candied fruits, fragrant teas…

This was a city that had been unchanged for a thousand years, a constant scene of peace and tranquility.

Today, Green Mulberry City welcomed several unusual strangers.

They were Lin Ming and his parents.

After a thousand and several hundred years, dozens of generations of people had already passed in Green Mulberry City.

No one recognized Lin Ming and no one recognized his parents, but they had still heard of Lin Ming’s legends.

This name would be passed down for several hundreds of thousands of years…

Lin Ming entered Green Mulberry City like common folk. They walked down new streets that had been renovated many times already, and these still familiar streets left Lin Ming’s parents filled with emotion.

They arrived at the Lin Family restaurant. This was a historical landmark that had been sealed away for over a thousand years, and was the true home of Lin Ming and his parents.

Because this building had been carefully maintained by others, it still remained completely intact.

However, after the glazed tiles withstood the wind and rain of over a thousand years, they were no longer bright.

The red lacquered columns and doors, even if washed and repainted several times, began to slowly turn mottled, revealing the flavor of passing years.

Creak –

The front door opened. What greeted one’s sight was the lobby of the restaurant.

The marbled blue stone ground was old, but the cleaned furniture was exactly the same as in the past…

Lin Ming was able to recall the scene of him jumping about this lobby when he was a child.

All sorts of people would come to this restaurant. Some would be here to drink wine, some would be here to drink tea, some would come and tell stories, some would come and play cards, some would play the zither, some would play chess…

Lin Ming remembered many of those old regulars. When he ran through this lobby as a child, these people would give Lin Ming some candies to eat.

“Even through the years, it's still the same…”

Lin Mu’s old eyes filled with tears. She traced the counter of the old tables as she recalled the past. Lin Fu used to stand here, wearing a loose gray cotton robe and a small felt hat. He would hold an abacus in his hands, recording numbers in the ledger as noises filled the air.

As for Lin Mu, she would help in the kitchen. After every dish was finished the waiter would bring it back and shout out with a voice full of charm, “The dish is ready!” Then, with a towel on his shoulder, the waiter would set down the dish, wiping clean the table and helping brew some tea.

Lin Mu, Lin Fu, as well as Lin Ming, the three of them lived in this restaurant.

This was their family home. The two old parents wished to pass the final years of their life here…

This restaurant was no longer open for business, but every day, Lin Mu would prepare food in the kitchen and Lin Ming would help at her side.

This three person family was happy and warm. But, Lin Mu still carried a single worry with her, and that was that Lin Ming remained unmarried…

Although Lin Ming could see the thoughts of his parents, he always kept his silence.

On this day, a visitor came to the Lin Family restaurant. A woman in a black dress looking just over 20 years old arrived. Her cultivation was unexpectedly at the late Divine Sea realm.

This woman was Situ Mingyue.

In the Sky Spill Continent, it was incredibly difficult for a martial artist to reach the late Divine Sea realm before a thousand years of age.

“Oh? You want to ascend?”

Lin Ming looked at Situ Mingyue with surprise. In truth, this was a reasonable desire. A martial artist who had climbed to the peak of the lower realms would not be satisfied with dwelling there. They would want to fly into the Divine Realm, seeing a broader world where they could freely spread their wings.

“Yes!”

Situ Mingyue was well aware of Lin Ming’s identity. She wanted to consult with him before preparing to ascend.

However, Lin Ming shook his head, “You… cannot ascend.”

“Why?”

Situ Mingyue’s heart skipped a beat. She could sense in Lin Ming’s eyes a type of deep and sorrow-filled emotion, one that caused her heart to shrink.

“The Divine Realm…has changed. Moreover… this world was once sealed by a woman. With your strength, you cannot break through…”

Lin Ming sighed. Situ Mingyue was left puzzled.

The Divine Realm had changed? The world of the Sky Spill Planet was sealed?

She suddenly remembered. If Lin Ming decided to reincarnate on the Sky Spill Planet, was this involved with the so-called changing of the Divine Realm?

She didn’t know what it was but she could feel instinctually that this ‘change’ must have been some heaven-shaking calamity.

“What happened in the Divine Realm?” Situ Mingyue couldn’t help but ask.

“The invasion of an outside race.” Lin Ming succinctly replied. He looked up to the skies, as if his eyes could see through the starry space and into the Divine Realm. “Humanity… is on the brink of disaster…”

“This…”

Situ Mingyue’s eyes widened. She thought that the great change that occurred in the Divine Realm might be some inner strife amongst humans, but she never imagined it would be because of the invasion of some alien race. And for humanity to already be in a precarious situation…

“If Senior has returned to the Sky Spill Planet from the Divine Realm, and has cultivated all over from a new rebirth, is this also related to that disaster?” Situ Mingyue asked. Lin Ming nodded.

“Sage Lin, your parents, they don’t seem to know of your identity. Have you never mentioned it?” Situ Mingyue asked again.

Lin Ming shook his head. “They don’t know nor does it matter. What they feel towards me is a connection that comes from the depths of their bloodline; it isn’t something that can be mistaken. I am their son and I cannot mention what I have experienced in life, otherwise I will have to tell them why I returned to the Sky Spill Planet, why my wives and Lin Xiaoge weren’t able to return, why I returned to being a baby…

“If my parents know the real situation of what is occurring, they will not be able to rest peacefully.”

Lin Ming quietly said. Situ Mingyue was left disappointed.

After a long period of silence, Situ Mingyue unwillingly asked, “Then… is there nothing that can be done?”

“I don’t know.” Lin Ming said. “I will return, perhaps in 10,000 years…”

10,000 years was the deadline that Lin Ming had set for himself.

To comprehend and fuse the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra, to grow his inner world, to dual cultivate the universe of the body and the world, all of this couldn’t be done rapidly but required an extremely long period of time.

10,000 years was already far too little time.

He wanted to grasp as much time as he could to accomplish all that he could. Only like this could he return to the Divine Realm and have a chance to struggle with the saints and the even more terrifying Soul Emperor.

“10,000 years…”

Hearing this, Situ Mingyue sucked in a deep breath, her expression a bit bitter and pained.

For a Divine Sea powerhouse, living to 10,000 years was their limit. Yet, this was a time period that Lin Ming casually tossed out. His words left her wallowing in despair.

If she was unable to surpass the Divine Sea realm, then by that time she would already be on the verge of death or she would have even become nothing more than bones.

Lin Ming could see Situ Mingyue’s thoughts. He said, “You can wander to travel. This lower realm dimension consists of more than the Sky Spill Planet. I can give you a spirit ship and a star chart so that you can visit other planets. Although you cannot ascend to the Divine Realm, freely wandering this world will still be helpful to you. At least, breaking through the Divine Sea won’t be difficult.”

Lin Ming casually said. But, Situ Mingyue still held unwillingness in her heart. She knew that if she couldn’t ascend to the Divine Realm and was only able to wander the lower realms, then no matter what she tried she wouldn’t be able to accomplish anything great. To barely surpass the Divine Sea realm would be her limit.

She bit her lips and looked at Lin Ming. Summoning every ounce of courage she had, she deeply bowed towards him, “Senior, I wonder if… you can take me as your apprentice?”

Lin Ming was stunned. He looked at her and slowly shook his head. “No. I have never taken in an apprentice and I have far too many matters I have yet to complete. I don’t wish to form any new karmic ties here.”

The destiny of a world, cause and effect, all of these were ephemeral and unpredictable things that Lin Ming didn’t want to be touched by. If he accepted an apprentice then he would have to take on the responsibility of a master.

Currently, Lin Ming didn’t have the time or energy to do all of this.

Listening to Lin Ming’s words, deep disappointment flashed in Situ Mingyue’s eyes.

In truth, she didn’t hold much hope that this was possible either. She was self-aware that even though her talent was at the peak of the lower realms, in Lin Ming’s eyes, it was probably nothing more than ordinary.

Even if Lin Ming accepted an apprentice, he would never accept her.

“I’m sorry for disturbing Senior.”

Situ Mingyue ruefully smiled. She deeply bowed towards Lin Ming once more and then turned to leave.

But at this time, faint footsteps sounded out from behind them. Lin Mu walked down the stairs and was immediately overjoyed to see Situ Mingyue. She called out, “Miss Situ? How come Miss Situ is here?”

When Lin Ming and his parents returned to Green Mulberry City to live in seclusion, this was information that not even many high-level figures of the four Divine Kingdoms were aware of. Lin Mu never thought that Situ Mingyue would actually find this place. This caused her to make some exciting associations.

Situ Mingyue hurriedly bowed as she saw Lin Mu. But by now, Lin Mu had already gently grasped Situ Mingyue’s hand and was pulling her down to sit, saying that she had to stay and eat a meal.

Situ Mingyue was helpless. She looked towards Lin Ming. Lin Ming hesitated for a moment and then slowly nodded.

Like this, the family dinner started.

Fresh and fragrant rice, six simple dishes, four pairs of chopsticks. Lin Fu even heated a pot of wine, pouring two cups to celebrate.

Although the old couple had returned to their past home and their mood was very good, they always held onto some regrets. This was from the monotony and loneliness brought about by such peaceful silence.

They hoped for quiet and peace even as they wished to see a lively family. Of course, if it was someone that could make their family lively, it also had to be someone that they liked and hoped to see…

Situ Mingyue was exactly such a person.

A simple meal, a simple happiness. Lin Mu constantly picked up dishes to place in Situ Mingyue’s bowl, her smile both gentle and kind.

“Eat some more. This is the sweet and sour fish that he loved to eat the most when he was a child. Only the sweet and sour fish of our hometown is the best. From Green Mulberry River, you need to fish up a big carp that is at least three jins heavy. Of course, it has to be fresh, and the ingredients also need to include the finest rock sugar…”

Lin Mu proudly said. Situ Mingyue knew that the ‘he’ Lin Mu spoke of referred to Lin Ming and also Lin An.

Lin Mu might not know that Lin An was Lin Ming, but what she knew was that the dishes they loved to eat were the exact same…

“Miss Situ, this is wine that I made myself. Here, try a little…”

Lin Fu laughed as he spoke.

Lin Ming saw the wonderful mood his parents were in. Although they had been happy these years, it had never been like today where they revealed smiles from the depths of their heart.

Lin Ming’s heart stirred. He let out a light sigh and came to a decision.

His lips moved as he sent out a true essence sound transmission. “Situ Mingyue, you and I can be master and apprentice for 100 years, but we will normally not refer to ourselves as master and apprentice. I only need you to accompany my parents, and I will teach you cultivation methods and give you a blessing of good fortune. After a hundred years pass, I will reincarnate and cultivate from nothing again, and as for you, that is when you and I part.”

As Situ Mingyue was eating, her chopsticks shook. She looked at Lin Ming, at a loss for words…

Chapter 1958 – The Second Reincarnation

Situ Mingyue stayed behind. Although her relationship with Lin Ming was only that of a master and apprentice, and one that was temporary at that, this was something Lin Ming’s parents didn’t know about.

In fact, in the eyes of Lin Mu and Lin Fu, there was a profound significance for Situ Mingyue to stay behind.

The old couple hoped that there would be people accompanying them in their old age, but they also wished that their son would marry and live a happy and bliss-filled life.

Lin Ming didn’t give an explanation for this misunderstanding. The reason he asked Situ Mingyue to stay behind to accompany his parents was because he wished to have his parents live peacefully in their old age.

Most of the time he didn’t speak with Situ Mingyue. He would only pass down cultivation methods to her that were suitable for her to practice and allow her to perceive them on her own.

As for pills, Lin Ming had more than enough. Every pill would be melted by her into spring water, and she would slowly drink this spring water and refine the medicine.

The effects were remarkable.

Situ Mingyue used a mere 10 years to approach the Divine Transformation realm.

The truth was that her talent wasn’t too bad even when placed in the Divine Realm. The problem was that she lacked skilled teachers in the lower realms which had delayed her cultivation. However, this was all made up for now. Although it was impossible for her to have any monumental achievements, with Lin Ming’s guidance it wouldn’t be difficult for her to cultivate to the Divine Lord realm.

Sometimes, Lin Ming would go out together with Situ Mingyue. They would venture deep into the starry space, and here Lin Ming would teach Situ Mingyue some Laws and advanced cultivation methods.

Lin Ming even passed Situ Mingyue an incomplete portion of a transcendent divine might. Although he didn’t have much hope that she would be able to perceive anything from it, she could at least come into contact with the Great Dao Laws, expanding her horizons as she obtained more inspirations.

Whenever these times came, Situ Mingyue’s eyebrows would bunch together as she simply wasn’t able to find any clue on what to do.

She was worried that Lin Ming would think she was too stupid and she desperately hoped that she could perceive something to satisfy him. However, these Great Dao traces were too complex and varied. No matter how hard she tried, it was difficult for her to become aware of anything.

Lin Ming didn’t say anything. He simply asked her what progress she had made and then would silently leave.

Like this, 50 years passed.

Lin Fu and Lin Mu grew older. But at the same time, they smiled more and more.

When she wasn’t cultivating, Situ Mingyue would spend the rest of her time accompanying Lin Ming’s parents. She frequently went to the kitchen to help Lin Mu prepare food and would take out a chess board to play with Lin Fu.

Everything was warm and harmonious. The happiness of a whole family made up for the final regrets that the old couple felt in life.

This was also what Lin Ming wanted.

In this life, he wanted to give his parents peace and happiness in their twilight. For this reason, even if he had to contaminate himself with some karma, it didn’t matter at all.

Spring went and fall came. Another 20 years passed. Lin Fu and Lin Mu both leant on walking sticks. It became a little difficult even to walk down the street.

Even so, there were no servants in their family. Every time they went to buy groceries, Situ Mingyue would help Lin Mu out of the Lin Family restaurant where they slowly walked down the familiar streets.

During these times, Lin Mu would walk slowly. She would take a stroll, feeling the sun on her face, feeling the joys of life.

Lin Fu and Lin Mu, the two of them had tasted poverty, and lived in opulence, had experienced the supreme life of being worshipped by millions and billions of people. Now in their old age, with Situ Mingyue and Lin Ming accompanying them, they felt warmth and happiness.

This was their life, a blessed life.

They had no regrets.

Two years later, just as summer began, on a sunny day Lin Fu and Lin Mu passed away one after another.

Just before they left, their faces were filled with smiles and their expressions were at peace. They had died in bed of old age.

The death of his parents also marked the end of Lin Ming’s first reincarnation, one that had lasted for over 1600 years.

It marked a complete ending to this time.

According to his parents’ will, Lin Ming buried them in the mountains around Green Mulberry City.

After death, become dust and return to the earth. This was the simple wish of most mortals.

According to custom, Lin Ming set up grass houses up in the mountainside. He wore simple mourning clothes and mourned for his parents for three years.

Situ Mingyue also followed Lin Ming. She wore white clothes, observing the mourning period together with him.

They lived in two separate grass houses. Every day they would sweep the graves of the old couple, burning incense for them and praying for them.

These days were slow and tepid. But whether it was Lin Ming or Situ Mingyue, they found an inner peace and quiet in these slow and tepid days.

Three years quickly passed.

With the end of the mourning period, Lin Ming had to leave.

Early one morning, the bright sun rose. The morning haze of Green Mulberry Mountain scattered and the dewdrops hanging on the grass also slowly evaporated.

Lin Ming lit incense for his parents and deeply knelt on his knees, bowing down, his forehead reaching the ground. This was also his final bow.

He stood up and said to Situ Mingyue behind him, “According to our agreement, our relation as master and apprentice has come to an end. You can now begin walking your own road.”

Lin Ming calmly said. But as these words fell into Situ Mingyue’s ears, she felt infinite desolateness, infinite melancholy.

There was an unspeakable feeling in her heart. She had known this day would come and she had mentally prepared for it. But when it truly came, she was at an inexplicable loss.

But, she was well aware that she and Lin Ming were originally two straight lines that never crossed. It was only because of Lin Ming’s parents that they approached for a brief period of time – and that was only approaching.

Then, as these straight lines continued on, they would slowly separate, gradually growing further and further apart.

This was a destiny that was already decided.

Regardless of what she did, it wouldn’t change.

Thus, she slowly nodded.

“Then, farewell. If we are fated to meet again…”

As Lin Ming spoke he casually stepped into the void. He simply didn’t need to tear open the void, but entered directly into it, vanishing from sight.

Situ Mingyue stood in a daze where she was, silent for a long time.

The year before Lin Fu and Lin Mu passed, Situ Mingyue had broken into the Divine Transformation realm. Moreover, with Lin Ming’s teachings and the support of the resources he left her, she had formed a solid foundation. It wouldn’t be a problem for her to reach the Divine Lord realm in the future.

But none of this, including the peak of martial arts that she had longed for in her dreams, brought her any joy right now. She quietly turned around, entering the grass house she had lived in for three years and gently closed the door…

…………..

Another 20 years passed.

In a lower dimension of this universe, within an imperial city on an unknown planet, at some unknown time, a young beggar appeared at a city corner.

He was short and his entire body was covered in dirt, but his eyes were amazingly bright.

Although he was a beggar, he never begged people. He only wandered about, and this wandering continued for dozens of years.

This young beggar grew extremely slowly, but because he was a beggar, no one noticed him.

Until one day, he disappeared from the city…

He broke into space, flying deep into the universe.

This was the second reincarnation of Lin Ming. During these years, Lin Ming’s mood and cultivation had become increasingly perfect. His cultivation didn’t increase quickly, but his comprehensions in the Heavenly Dao grew at an alarming pace.

He quickly sped through the universe. Soon he reached a massive black planet. Like a meteor, he plunged deep into its core…

Chapter 1959 – Return to the Divine Realm

The universe was profound and endless, an existence far too mysterious. It contained infinite rules of the Heavenly Dao. Since ages long lost, innumerable ancient powerhouses had searched high and low, tirelessly chasing down the elusive road of martial arts.

But up until now, there had yet to be a single person who completely understood all the mysteries of the universe.

Not only was the universe mysterious, but it was eternal.

Even when great worlds collapsed and returned to nothing, the universe as a whole would continue to exist.

No one knew where these eternal skies started or where they would end…

Time, was the most terrifying reaper of all life. But to the Heavenly Dao of the universe this concept held no meaning at all.

A thousand years was only a flash of time, so short that there would be almost no change in the universe.

However, when it came to mortal society and their nations, in several thousand years there would be hundreds of generations of people. Dynasties would fall and others would rise in their place. The great families, sects, countless lives were born and returned to nothing. Their convoluted history would be buried in the sands of time as they were slowly lost forever.

In the end, the only thing these people would leave behind in the world was ‘nothing’.

To the vicissitudes of time things remained the same, but people always changed.

One wintry afternoon, a person and a large black vicious beast appeared outside an ancient city.

This city had been renovated countless times, but many edges and corners of it were still engraved with the wearing of the years…

Outside the city, people were bustling. These people came and went, fear in their hearts as none of them dared to approach. Even so, they stretched out their necks, curiously looking on.

This man wore black clothes and his body was as straight as a spear. His looks seemed carved by a saber, containing an indescribable flavor.

As for the vicious beast beside him, that was what attracted the most attention.

It looked like a giant wolf, but there was a single black horn that thrust out from its head, making it look like a mythical dragon.

This man and beast were Lin Ming and the small black dragon.

After a thousand years, Lin Ming had completed his third reincarnation and had stepped into his fourth. As for the black dragon, it had grown and its appearance was restored to its original state. If it desired, its body could grow to thousands of feet high, towering like a mountain peak.

During his fourth reincarnation Lin Ming returned to the Sky Spill Planet and came to Green Mulberry City once more.

Green Mulberry City still existed, but its name had changed. It was no longer called Green Mulberry City but was now called Sky Province.

The walls here had developed further outwards and the roads had been expanded. In the center of the city a grand imperial palace had been erected, emblazoned in gold and jade.

Green Mulberry City had long become the capital city of Sky Fortune Kingdom.

In fact, Sky Fortune Kingdom had already changed dynasties, and this was not the first or second time either.

The deterrence of Lin Ming’s name made many countries not dare to invade the Sky Fortune Kingdom. But, this didn’t mean that the royal family of the Sky Fortune Kingdom wouldn’t be changed.

A coup, a cruel and witless ruler, all of this could cause the downfall of a dynasty.

Now, the royal family of the Sky Fortune Kingdom was no longer surnamed Yang, but was surnamed Zhou.

The Sky Fortune Kingdom was no longer called that either, but was now referred to as the Great Zhou Dynasty.

In order to stabilize the destiny of their nation, the royal family of the Great Zhou Dynasty decided to move the capital city to Green Mulberry City and change its name to Sky Province. The royal family believed that since Lin Ming once lived in the city, it would surely have a glorious destiny and would shelter the foundation of the Great Zhou Dynasty for 10,000 years.

Towards this, Lin Ming no longer cared at all.

He now had no more worries. He constantly journeyed out, refining his inner world. He grew stronger and stronger.

But during his fourth reincarnation, Lin Ming felt his cultivation reach a bottleneck.

This was the transition from an ordinary World King to a Great World King.

The truth was that if Lin Ming desired, it wouldn’t be difficult for him to forcefully break past this transitionary phase.

But, he wanted everything to be done perfectly. Thus he made a decision. That was to go to the Asura Road and complete the final trial!

He had wandered through the lower realms long enough. It was time to leave.

However, in order to break out from the world that the Sky Spill Planet was located in and go to the Divine Realm, he would have to take a great risk. Moreover, he had to break through the barrier that Sheng Mei left behind.

In the past, Sheng Mei had left her barrier above the skies of the Sky Spill Planet. The array eye was naturally located here too.

This array formation blocked out the space channel in the lower realm dimension that connected the Sky Spill Planet to the Divine Realm.

“Let’s go, Little Black…”

As Lin Ming spoke, he soared upwards. His body turned into a keen blade that pierced through the deep blue skies. As for the black dragon, it also followed Lin Ming. Like this, man and beast turned into two beams of divine light that broke past the atmosphere of the Sky Spill Planet and arrived in space.

This part of the void didn’t seem unusual at all. But as Lin Ming lightly touched it, it rippled like a rock thrown into a lake. Then, a giant array formation appeared. This array formation was similar in appearance to a giant yin yang diagram. One half was gold and the other half was black, representing the Concepts of Life and Death.

In the samsara of life and death, Lin Ming already had his own comprehensions.

After a moment of silence he faced the giant array diagram. He thrust out his finger again and again, each thrust causing ripples to spread through space. With each thrust, an invisible pen seemed to paint images atop this giant array diagram.

This process continued for a quarter hour of time. Then, the array diagram trembled, becoming increasingly bright and transparent, as if it were turning to mist.

Seeing this, Lin Ming took in a deep breath. The array formation had been unraveled.

He stared at the void behind the array formation and slowly opened a space channel. His appearance gradually changed and his temperament and aura became completely different.

Lin Ming used the Bodily Rebirth Technique. After comprehending the Concept of Life, when he used this secret technique he could change his life aura, becoming an entirely different person.

Not just that, but in the past Sheng Mei had drawn out most of Lin Ming’s soul source, and because Lin Ming’s soul had gone through the Grand Reincarnation Art and had gained a new life, during this process of rebirth his soul fluctuations had also faintly changed. He could truly have been said to have been reborn both inside and out.

This was also the reason he dared to return to the Divine Realm before his strength had fully matured.

After finishing, Lin Ming stepped forwards, passing through the array formation as if walking through a screen of blue smoke. The array formation that Sheng Mei left behind wasn’t moved at all…

The Sky Spill Planet’s upper space channel was filled with all sorts of chaotic energies. But to the current Lin Ming, these chaotic energies were no different than a calm breeze.

It was just that as he rapidly shuttled through the space storms, his heart wasn’t calm.

He knew that once he reached the end of this space tunnel he would finally see everything that had happened in the Divine Realm after thousands of years.

This was something he had always wished to know, but also something he was afraid to find out…

……….

Space transformed. Lin Ming felt as if he passed through a thin membrane of water.

As he stepped into these familiar yet strange starry skies, all sorts of emotions bloomed in his heart.

This starry space, it was this starry space again. But, the aura of it seemed to have changed…

He knew that what he would see were likely scenes that would leave him feeling sad…

He couldn’t restrain the feelings in his heart. He tore open space and began using the great void shift. First, he wanted to go see Divine Dream Heavenly Palace.

Although he knew what had likely happened, he wanted to lay witness to it with his own eyes.

He didn’t know what happened to Mu Qianyu, Qin Xingxuan, Xiao Moxian, his child, Mo Eversnow, Empyrean Divine Dream, Empyrean Vast Universe… they, were they safe?

After ascending to the Divine Realm, Lin Ming could complete the journey to Divine Dream Heavenly Palace using less than 20 days.

But, Lin Ming actually spent a full two months.

During these two months, he swept his sense over many places.

He saw many planets that had been destroyed. Their bodies had collapsed, turned into nothing but countless fragments. Beneath the gravitational pull of the remaining mass they turned into a belt of ring-like fragments that aimlessly floated through the cosmos.

Besides these planets, the sects that had been destroyed were even higher in number.

Many sects were annihilated along with their spirit mountains and celestial islands.

From cold and tragic ruins, Lin Ming could imagine just what it was like when the saints invaded.

With a True Divinity leading them, humanity was no match for the saints.

Those top elites that managed to escape were barely able to flee in time. But as for general Holy Lands, they were undoubtedly instantly destroyed by the saint Empyreans.

For an Empyrean, eliminating an ordinary Holy Land was the same as kicking down a sand castle.

Countless elites of humanity had died tragically in this catastrophe.

As for those that were left behind, they were only ordinary human citizens.

There were far too many of these people. They numbered in the trillions of quadrillions and were spread through the 3000 great worlds of the Divine Realm as well as the countless small worlds and medium worlds. It was impossible for the saints to kill all of them.

But as long as they severed the martial arts inheritances of humanity then these mortals would have no strength to resist, just like common domesticated animals. They would be reared in cages and enslaved.

Finally, Lin Ming arrived in the part of the universe where Divine Dream Heavenly Palace was.

Although he had already been mentally prepared, as Lin Ming saw the place where Divine Dream Heavenly Palace had been, he still fiercely shook. The scene before him left him moved, but in his emotions was also a trace of sadness.

Divine Dream Heavenly Palace was no longer here. This was also within reason. If Empyrean Divine Dream were still alive, she would definitely bring Divine Dream Heavenly Palace away with her.

But in the former site of Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, all of those grand and glorious mountains that were full of spiritual energy and exquisite planets were now completely taken over by the saints. This was a land that contained a tremendous amount of resources and heavenly materials and was a treasure trove rich in heaven and earth origin energy. The saints naturally wouldn’t destroy it.

A sect of the saints was established here and saint disciples entered in and out. This sect was prosperous and had inherited the millions of years of accumulations of Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, and was now using it to nourish itself.

They had enslaved the spirit beasts that were raised on the celestial mountains of Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, forcefully taming them into mounts and contract beasts.

The mineral mines and medicinal fields were also wildly developed by the saint sect. All sorts of heavenly materials were plundered from the ground.

As for the human martial artists, they were either slain or taken in as slaves. They were used as miners, servants, janitors, or even taken in as living furnaces…

A million miles away, Lin Ming watched all of this.

He stood there for a long time and then quietly left, leaving not a single trace of himself behind.

In the vast and boundless starry space, Lin Ming turned into a beam of light that fled full speed into the universe. He gripped his fists so hard that his nails dug into his flesh.

He told himself –

Everything that had been lost would be returned two-fold…

Chapter 1960 – Reentering the Asura Road

Regardless of what calamity occurred in the 33 Heavens, the Asura Road hadn’t changed.

As for the human, saints, and spiritas here, they seemed to live independently from their kin in the 33 Heavens, without much overlap or contact between them.

Lin Ming’s Asura Command had already shattered so he was unable to use it anymore. He found the spatial entrance into the Asura Road that Empyrean Divine Dream had led him to in the past, and used his own strength to sink into the Asura Road.

When Lin Ming reentered the Asura Road he discovered that amongst its trial challengers, the saints had rapidly increased in number.

In the outer Asura Road, Lin Ming observed that many young saint elites passed in and out of the large cities. It seemed that during the time he was gone, the great influences of the saints had dispatched their disciples en masse into the Asura Road.

The saints had revealed their ambitiousness.

Lin Ming didn’t bother with any of this. Currently, the Asura Road’s final trial had yet to open. Lin Ming quietly waited in the Great Desolate.

He sank deep into the Great Desolate. Here, he felt the power of the world of the Asura Road.

Deep underground, Lin Ming could feel that the Asura Road world was actually somewhat similar to his own inner world.

Could it be that the Asura Road world that the Asura Road Master had created in the past was also his own inner world?

This thought immediately flashed through Lin Ming’s mind. Just how difficult would it be to accomplish something like this? However, he also believed that in the distant future, he would be able to take this step too.

The world power within the Asura Road was potent and vigorous. However, because it was locked in by the constraints of the Asura Heavenly Dao, it was incredibly difficult for Lin Ming to absorb any.

Lin Ming composed himself and began to quietly perceive the composition of the Asura Road world. With the guidance of the Asura Heavenly Dao, it wasn’t difficult for Lin Ming to accomplish all of this.

Perceiving all of this was a slow process. Lin Ming focused himself, becoming enraptured with the process. In the blink of an eye, dozens of years passed.

Lin Ming obtained many new enlightenments. He fused all of these comprehensions into his growing inner world.

And at this time, the opening of the final trial also approached.

Lin Ming left the Great Desolate and ventured into the inner Asura Road.

In order to attend the final trial one needed a qualification token. The last time Lin Ming entered the final trial, he had obtained a qualification token from Mo Brightmoon.

If one wished to obtain a qualification token, the process would require a tremendous amount of energy and time. Although it wasn’t too difficult to the current him, Lin Ming didn’t want to waste this time.

His strength was already great enough that he could blatantly storm into a sect and recklessly wrest away a qualification token.

Late at night, Lin Ming floated high in the air, letting his sense spread out in all directions. He covered a large region of the inner Asura Road and soon discovered an influence that was located near the Asura Sea. This was a group that belonged to the saints!

And they were the saints of the 33 Heavens!

Among them was someone that possessed a qualification token. Even though they had carefully hidden away the token, they still couldn’t escape Lin Ming’s sense.

Lin Ming sneered. He silently descended like a dark ghost of the night.

This group of saint martial artists was still meditating in their holy palace. But outside of the holy palace, there were some people standing guard.

Those standing guard had spread out their divine sense, completely covering a surrounding area of a hundred miles. But when Lin Ming arrived, he didn’t alert them at all.

Pa!

With a faint sound, one of the sentries wobbled and slumped to the ground.

The other saint martial artists were alarmed. They rapidly rolled up from their sleep and were about to draw weapons from their spatial rings. But at this time, there was a loud explosion. The defensive barrier of the holy palace had been smashed apart!

Soon after, one of the people amongst them felt a strong breeze rush against him. A black beast rushed forwards like a demonic hellhound, crashing into his chest!

Peng!

This person flew backwards, smashing against a wall and vomiting a mouthful of blood.

His organs had all been crushed apart in this single strike!

“D-damnit!”

Amongst the group of people, a Great World King roared out. He was clearly able to see the vicious beast that had attacked them. This unknown vicious beast looked like a black wolf with a single long horn jutting out from its head.

But, what was most terrifying was the master of this vicious beast. Of the ten plus people present, no one was able to clearly see his appearance or catch his position. He was like a death reaper, mercilessly harvesting lives.

Every time he flickered he didn’t leave behind any fluctuations of the Space Laws. Even so, he floated in the air and disappeared into space, vanishing without a sign. This degree of Law comprehensions had reached an unimaginable level.

Moreover, this other party had a terrifying strength capable of ripping apart the holy palace’s protective barrier. This left the saints drowning in despair.

“Scatter and flee! Inform the sect and request backup…!”

The Great World King sent out sound transmissions. However, halfway through his sound transmission came to a halting stop.

He was the last saint martial artist to die.

This saint race squad consisted of 12 people, and all of them were killed off by Lin Ming.

Looking at the corpses around him, Lin Ming was silent. Before, he would never kill innocents. Those he had killed had already stepped onto the road of death.

But this time he killed 12 saint martial artists in a single breath, all so no news would be leaked out. Even though his identity wouldn’t be revealed even if news of him had leaked out, Lin Ming had to guard against all possibilities, no matter how small they were.

Lin Ming felt no psychological burden in killing these people. This was because when it came to a war between races, there were no innocents.

Lin Ming flicked his finger and shot out a fireball. All of the corpses burned away, and with the breeze of the night, their ashes faded.

He found the token he wanted. The other useless things were all destroyed. The holy palace was also taken away by Lin Ming and all other traces of his appearance destroyed.

After finishing all of this, Lin Ming flew up, disappearing into the night like a bat…

……

The final trial’s location was deep in the inner Asura Road. This was a boundless sea called the Asura Sea.

The Asura Sea was limitless and fathomless. Even if a massive planet like the Sky Spill Planet were to sink into the Asura Sea, it would be completely submerged!

In such a deep sea, the pressure at the seabed was unimaginable!

By any common reasoning there was no seabed that could withstand such tremendous pressure. The reason the Asura Sea could still exist was because of the power of the Asura Laws.

At those terrifying depths, innumerable horrifying sea beasts were bred. Among them were many sea beasts equivalent to an Empyrean in strength. In the rumors it was said that deep in the Asura Sea, there were one or two True Divinity level super sea beasts that had been bred. They were the king of all sea beasts!

Because of these stories, very few people dared to enter the Asura Sea.

The only exception was if… the final trial was beginning.

On this day, the usually lonely Asura Sea began to greet many guests.

Many influences gathered at the Asura Sea.

On the surface of the Asura Sea, many great figures spread out viewing platforms that floated above sea level. Many martial artists rushed here from all over the Asura Road, gathering to bear witness to such a grand occasion of the Asura Road.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Deep within the sea, the waters separated. A blue whale as large as a mountain emerged from the sea waters. As it rose up, countless streams of water fell down from its titanic body like waterfalls.

For a time, the viewing platforms on the sea surface were wildly swept up by the waves created by the blue whale. Many young martial artists on the viewing platforms stumbled around, unable to stand steady.

“Hey, that’s Northheaven Palace’s Deepnorth Leviathan… that is Northheaven Palace’s destiny-stabilizing God Beast. Although its bloodline is a bit flawed, it is still a fortress that is much stronger than a half-step Empyrean. I never thought that Northheaven Palace would send the Deepnorth Leviathan here to shake up the scene.”

Someone said from the viewing platforms. As they spoke, the giant blue whale called the Deepnorth Leviathan opened its huge mouth. From its mouth, a blue curtain of light appeared. The disciples of Northheaven Palace were shrouded in this blue light.

They all wore the uniform of a sect and bloomed with heroic dashing. From their dignified appearance, one could see that they were the elites of their sect.

In truth, most of these people only came to see the world and broaden their horizons; they wouldn’t truly be entering the final trial. After all, there was a limited number of qualification tokens.

“Northheaven Palace really laid out their capital this time, but they can’t be blamed for doing so. During these past years, the saints from the 33 Heavens outside the Asura Road have sent far too many elites in here. It sort of feels as if they are trying to make a show of some kind. Because of this, competition for the final trial has also become more intense.”

“This time, I heard that the 33 Heavens’ saints have sent many high level figures here. Many of those people come from the Good Fortune Saint Palace!”

Upon mentioning the name of the Good Fortune Saint Palace, dread flashed across the faces of the martial artists from the Asura Road. Many great figures who rushed here from all over the Asura Road also frowned.

The master of Good Fortune Saint Palace was also the supreme leader of the saints – the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was simply too terrifying. According to rumors, he might have become the number one master of the 33 Heavens. He had fused together with some strange and horrible monster, obtaining unparalleled power in exchange!

As everyone spoke, a resonant phoenix cry echoed out in the skies.

A bird that resembled a phoenix flew towards this area. On the back of this bird sat an old woman dressed in a phoenix robe and wearing a golden crown. She leaned on a golden walking stick and exuded a rich and opulent aura. Her eyes seemed to contain a great pressure, making it difficult for others to feel at ease.

And behind this woman were several beautiful young women. Each one had a face covered by a thin veil, looking like goddesses that descended to the mortal plane.

“Grandma Goldwind! An inner Asura Road Empyrean!”

After seeing this old woman, many people were stunned. The Asura Road’s final trial was a grand occasion, but it was still a tempering experience for juniors. Most of the time Empyrean level characters wouldn’t attend, but would send their direct disciples to manage the situation.

With the arrival of Empyreans, that signified just how valuable this final trial now was.

“Grandma Goldwind personally led her disciples to the final trial. It looks like the limelight of the 33 Heavens’ saints has been too bright these past years. The native influences of the Asura Road are unwilling to fall behind them and are willing to fight more.”

“I fear this final trial will also be set atop the winds and waves. I wonder if anyone will be able to achieve an 80% completion rate…”

“It’s not impossible. Amongst the young elites that the Good Fortune Saint Palace dispatched this time, there might be some people capable of this…”

As everyone was speaking, no one noticed a black-clothed, common-seeming youth quietly standing atop a viewing platform.

He was like a gray brushstroke amongst this world, completely out of sync.

At some time, he suddenly turned his head and looked into the horizon of the Asura Sea.

He felt that someone he recognized had arrived…

Chapter 1961 – Famine’s Avatar

In the distant horizon of the Asura Sea, a young man in golden armor slowly flew forwards. This gold-armored youth was tall and broad. A fire red cloak was thrown over his back, his momentum spirited and daring!

His cultivation had reached the peak of the Great World King realm, approaching the half-step Empyrean realm.

This cultivation, when placed in the grand scene of the final trial’s opening, wasn’t considered much at all. Moreover, there were more than Great World Kings but even true Empyreans.

But as this youth appeared, the eyes of those in the audience shrank. It was clear that they were extremely afraid of this gold-armored youth.

“It’s really him…”

Lin Ming muttered. This gold-armored youth was someone he was familiar with – the Good Fortune Saint Son!

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s cultivation speed was far higher than Lin Ming’s. But, this was also within reason. First, the Good Fortune Saint Son had lived longer than Lin Ming, and secondly, the Laws that the Good Fortune Saint Son cultivated were infinitely simpler than Lin Ming’s.

With Lin Ming having reincarnated also, although he didn’t experience any bottlenecks returning to his previous cultivation realm, it still delayed him by a great deal of time.

“The Good Fortune Saint Son, he actually came…”

Lin Ming thought. In truth, he also wanted to find an opportunity to kill off the Good Fortune Saint Son, but now was not the right moment.

At this time, Lin Ming’s complexion changed. From beneath the Good Fortune Saint Son the sea began to stir, a storm rising up!

Violent fluctuations of energy emanated outwards. Dreadful waves swept over the world. A giant spherical blood red life form rose up from the sea, its appearance like a scarlet sun!

From all over this bloody sun, the sea water boiled away. Water vapor evaporated all over, massive layers of clouds forming in the skies.

Following this, a horrifying momentum rushed out. Even the God Beast that had arrived at the Asura Sea felt fear. It shrank backwards, filled with dread for this bloody sun.

“This is…”

Many Asura Road martial artists were stunned. Most of them had never felt such a terrifying aura before.

And amongst these people, even the originally silent Lin Ming felt a cold sweat seep out of his forehead. He almost tore through space to run away.

No one was more aware than him of just what this blood red ball was. It was the abyssal demon – Famine!

“How is this possible?”

Lin Ming was panic-stricken. Why would Famine appear here? Did the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign also come?

Lin Ming held his breath. If the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign arrived, then his Bodily Rebirth Technique would truly be challenged!

After all, Lin Ming had once fought against the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. He didn’t have any hopes that a newly reborn body would be able to deceive the sense of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

“Mm? Something’s wrong!”

Immediately, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. Over half of that blood red ball had appeared above the horizon. From the radius of the blood red ball, the total volume was clearly far smaller than Famine had been before.

Famine’s true body was over 10 thousand miles in diameter, as large as a planet.

But this blood red sphere was only several hundred miles in diameter.

Moreover, although the aura of this blood red sphere was similar to Famine’s, it was much, much weaker. It was clearly not the true Famine.

And, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign wasn’t atop this blood red sphere. The one controlling it seemed to be the Good Fortune Saint Son.

“This small crimson sphere, could it actually be… Famine’s descendant?”

Lin Ming immediately thought. His heart chilled. Famine was already an incredibly terrifying existence. If it was able to produce descendants… he simply didn’t want to imagine that.

Famine’s attribute was to swallow all. If it were to continue without end, then even the entire universe would be swallowed up by it!

“What is that thing?”

On the Asura Sea, many people wondered with trembling hearts.

For many of them this was the first time they had lain eyes upon such a terrifying life form.

In their original opinion, God Beasts were already the supreme vicious beasts of the entire universe. Although legends said that deep within the Asura Sea there were one or two super beasts that could compare with True Divinities, legends were only legends; no one had seen them before.

But currently, this terrifying thing could even cause a God Beast to draw back in fear. Was this a terrifying existence on the level of a True Divinity?

“It is Famine!”

On a luxurious sea platform, Grandma Goldwind slowly spoke. As she looked at Famine, a strange light glittered in her eyes.

Lin Ming turned his head and listened. For all these years, he had been absent from the Divine Realm for far too long and didn’t know what state the saints were in. He also didn’t know how strong the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had become.

“Famine? From the legends, the avatar of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign?”

A small number of martial artists from the Asura Road had also heard about the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. The destruction of the Divine Realm, the defeat and withdrawal of the human race, these were events that reverberated through the 33 Heavens.

In addition, many saint martial artists had recently come to the Asura Road. Thus, many of them knew just what kind of character the leader of the saints was. They also knew of his avatar – Famine, who came from the Dark Abyss.

“It is! But, it is more accurate to say that what is before us is only Famine’s avatar. In the last thousand years, Famine has swallowed far too many things. It has swallowed massive amounts of resources, life essence, soul essence, and has begun to breed its own avatars. With this, it can swallow things even faster, growing even faster...

Grandma Goldwind muttered.

Lin Ming’s face darkened. Swallowed many things!? Resources? Life essence? Soul essence?

These things could only have been from the Divine Realm!

When the God Lamenting Wall began to weaken and the great calamity approached, it was even possible that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had raised up a great war that swept through the Divine Realm and ancient races all in order to provide food for Famine.

Where would the saints have found so many things to feed Famine? It was naturally impossible for the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign to ruin his own race, thus he could only choose to invade other universes.

After understanding this, Lin Ming gripped his fists and clenched his teeth.

In this calamity, countless people had died in battle within the Divine Realm. Innumerable sects had been turned to dust, their inheritances lost to time.

Many people had been swallowed and their souls absorbed, forced to become a part of Famine. This was a truly tragic way to die.

It was even likely that those humans who survived would be raised by the saints and used as fodder to feed Famine.

With the saints suppressing humanity, the human race would suffer the fate of eventually degenerating into farm animals.

Understanding this, Lin Ming’s eyes suddenly became icy cold. He looked towards the Good Fortune Saint Son who was flying in from the distance, and hid the murderous intent bubbling in his heart.

At this time, the Good Fortune Saint Son stood tall above Famine’s back, a light grin on his face.

In that peak battle against Lin Ming in the past, the Good Fortune Saint Son had suffered an excruciating defeat, ending in the greatest frustration of his life.

But afterwards, when the saints invaded the Divine Realm, the Good Fortune Saint Son had commanded the armies to trample over the 3000 great worlds of the Divine Realm. Most Empyreans had either fled or died. The Good Fortune Saint Son could be called invincible, knowing no loss. He recklessly galloped over the universe, overbearing, as if no one in the world could topple him. His confidence that was shattered by Lin Ming was also restored as he found the thrill of revenge.

His cultivation would need at most 2000 more years to break into the Empyrean realm.

Moreover, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had even let him control one of Famine’s avatars!

As long as he could raise this avatar and fuse together with it, then his strength would reach an unimaginable boundary.

At that time, besides a few people in the entire 33 Heavens, who could stop him?

In this situation, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s thoughts were incomparably smooth. He had been ordered to preside over the smelting trial of the Good Fortune Saint Palace’s junior disciples. He stepped onto the Asura Sea stage with cocky vigor, using Famine’s avatar to make a high-profile appearance that deterred all present!

The Good Fortune Saint Son was satisfied with the effect he created. In his opinion, those who possessed absolutely formidable strength should expose that strength and awe everyone, making them submit!

The saints already possessed such capital.

The high-spirited Good Fortune Saint Son didn’t notice that on one of the viewing platforms, a black-clothed youth was gazing at him.

Although this black-clothed youth’s eyes contained a horrifying killing intent, what was unusual was that no one sensed him.

This was because the boundary of his soul force had far surpassed all others’ present. No one was able to sense him.

“Let’s begin… today is the stage of my race. Only my race will be the main lead of this final trial!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son raucously laughed.

Many native influences of the Asura Road saw the Good Fortune Saint Son’s rampant behavior and wanted to refute him, but they couldn’t summon the energy to do so.

Their influences truly couldn’t compare with the Good Fortune Saint Palace.

At this time, from beneath the Good Fortune Saint Son’s feet, the flesh and blood of Famine began to slowly split up like a pomegranate being torn apart. From within it, a group of young saint elites appeared!

These young saint elites had been sent from the Good Fortune Saint Palace. They were a special squad of disciples sent to participate in the final trial.

As for the Good Fortune Saint Son himself, he would not be attending the final trial. This time he was only a host.

Chapter 1964 – Change in the Spatial Gate

As the disciples from the Good Fortune Saint Palace and Soaring Feather God Mountain approached, Lin Ming stepped back and hid himself in a space distortion, completely vanishing from sight.

In the final trial, wanting to distort space wasn’t easy. Lin Ming relied on his understandings of the Asura Laws to do so.

“Elder Senior-apprentice Brother, we’ve arrived first.”

A young disciple from the Good Fortune Saint Palace looked at the empty scene in front of the Gate of Laws, chuckling as he spoke. The elder senior-apprentice brother he spoke of was naturally the fat man leading them.

The fat man patted his belly. He drawled, “This isn’t anything to be overly proud about. We come from the Good Fortune Saint Palace and we have the most people here. With so many of us working together, if we aren’t the first group to arrive then we might as well go home and cry. Moreover, those from Soaring Feather God Mountain have also arrived.

As the fat man spoke, his eyes peered into the horizon. He could see a deep blue spirit boat slowly but solidly flying towards them. That was the transportation device of Soaring Feather God Mountain’s disciples.

After the disciples from Soaring Feather God Mountain arrived, they only spared a glance at the Good Fortune Saint Palace disciples before gathering off on another side on their own where they began to meditate.

As time passed, more and more trial challengers reached the Gate of Laws.

As for Lin Ming, he chose a time when most of the trial challengers had arrived to quietly appear. No one noticed an extra person amongst the throngs.

After Lin Ming appeared, the Gate of Laws began to shine with an even more dazzling light!

Rumble rumble rumble!

The earth shook. The Gate of Laws opened just a sliver and a horrifying aura gushed out like a tsunami!

The hearts of those present quaked. The trial of the Gate of Laws was finally about to start!

This was an extremely vital part of the Asura Road’s final trial. The rewards dispensed at the Gate of Laws were incredibly rich.

Moreover, from this point on, the results of the trial challengers would rapidly be pulled apart. The powerhouses would go higher and the weak ones would drop lower.

Beneath the shroud of divine light, the gate completely opened.

Within the gate was an incomparably vast starry space. Four spatial gates were lined up in the starry space.

These four spatial gates represented four difficulties. From largest to smallest, from easiest to hardest, they were the mortal-step difficulty, earth-step difficulty, heaven-step difficulty, and also the Asura difficulty!

The difficulty of the Gate of Laws was disgustingly abnormal. In the past, even the sixth revolution Sheng Mei was barely able to perfectly complete the heaven-step difficulty.

“Hahaha! It’s finally opened!”

“It’s begun. The smaller the spatial gate, the more difficult it will be. This is one of our life’s most important chances. Everyone, be a bit more cautious and give it everything you have!”

A sect disciple with some experience began to introduce the details of the Gate of Laws.

The gazes of many trial challengers invariably drifted over to the rightmost spatial gate, the one that was also the smallest.

This spatial gate was blood red, like a spinning vortex of blood. The aura it emitted caused one’s heart to shake with fear and dread.

Many martial artists felt a terrifying pressure just looking at it. They couldn’t keep their eyes on this gate for a long period of time.

“Don’t look, if you look too long then you’ll suffer a soul wound. That gate isn’t something that people can enter.”

An Asura Road disciple grimly said to several of his junior-apprentice brothers.

“No one can enter? Thousands of years ago, wasn’t there that monstrous genius Lin Ming who managed to perfectly pass the Asura difficulty? Is that legend true?”

Upon mentioning Lin Ming’s name, the complexions of many martial artists changed.

Lin Ming was a fabled existence within the Asura Road. In billions of years, he was the only final trial challenger who had managed to obtain a completion rate above 90%.

This was a completion percentage so high it strained the neck. There were even many people that weren’t willing to believe this rumor.

“That legend… is true.”

Someone slowly said.

The atmosphere of the field fell silent for a moment. Amongst those present, no one dared to choose the Asura difficulty. Even the heaven-step difficulty caused people to shrink back.

As for Lin Ming, not only had he chosen the Asura difficulty but he had perfectly passed it. This disparity was greater than clouds and mud.

“Elder Senior-apprentice Brother, some people mentioned that boy…”

A disciple of the Good Fortune Saint Palace said in a hushed whisper. To the saints, especially talents of the saints, Lin Ming was a nauseating name.

Their senior, the Good Fortune Saint Son, had originally been brutally beaten down by Lin Ming.

“Heh, who cares if the legend is true or not? He’s already dead.”

The fat elder senior-apprentice brother loudly spoke up. Everyone turned their heads towards him.

The fat man was casually lying back on his flying rug. He unhurriedly took out a bag of fruits from his spatial ring. These fruits were the size of longans and seemed to drip with jade green juices, seeping with fragrance. Just by looking at them one could see that they were precious heavenly materials.

The fat man began speaking as he popped these fruits into his mouth. His voice was a bit slurred, “A dead genius is no longer a genius. Who cares how talented Lin Ming was when he was alive? It was bad enough he was born in the wrong race, but he was truly an idiot. A mere Holy Lord thought that he could save the Divine Realm, really, I want to laugh myself to death.

“For my saint race, killing him was easy. The only problem was that he hid behind the protection of peak Empyreans so we had to use a True Divinity. To die by a True Divinity’s hands, he should be honored.”

The fat man lazily spoke, his words careless. As everyone heard these words, they felt various emotions in their hearts. Some felt pity for Lin Ming, but there were even more people gloating in his downfall.

Where there were people, there was bound to be jealousy. In particular, geniuses hated being surpassed by others. When someone was so terrifying that no one could see their back, these people naturally hoped that something bad would happen to them.

“Enough with the chit chat. Choose your gate!”

The fat elder senior-apprentice brother waved his hand and the disciples of the Good Fortune Saint Palace began making their choice.

What they chose was the earth-step difficulty level.

This difficulty level was already extraordinary. Of the many Asura Road disciples, most could only choose the mortal-step difficulty.

But then, the fat man also made his choice. He chose the heaven-step difficulty!

This was the same difficulty that Sheng Mei and Xiao Moxian chose in the past. From this alone it could be seen how hard it was!

Of course, Sheng Mei had perfectly completed the heaven-step difficulty in the past, moreover she had done so calmly. It was impossible for the fat man to do the same, but he might be able to partially complete it.

After making his choice, the fat man looked towards the disciples of Soaring Feather God Mountain.

Finally, the gray-clothed woman from Soaring Feather God Mountain decided not to weaken her momentum at all; she also chose the heaven-step difficulty.

“Interesting!”

The fat man’s lips curved up in a happy and thoughtful smile.

Following that, the others made their choice. No one could summon the courage to follow in the footsteps of the fat man and the gray-clothed woman; they only chose the easier difficulties.

And by this time, Lin Ming still hadn’t made his choice.

He looked towards these four spatial gates and frowned. His divine sense repeatedly scanned the Asura difficulty spatial gate but he didn’t detect anything strange. This spatial gate was exactly the same as the one he chose in the past.

After seeing that 99% of the people had chosen and the Gate of Laws trial would soon begin, Lin Ming finally started to move. But, he still couldn’t make a choice.

However at this time, the Gate of Laws suddenly shined with a divine brilliance once more!

The earth wobbled and quaked, even fiercer than before. Everyone was panic-stricken; they had no idea what had occurred.

Ka ka ka ka!

With a great cracking sound, the void to the right of the red Asura gate suddenly split open!

A vortex of energy emerged from thin air, revolving without end, stabilizing that shattered space and turning it into another spatial gate.

This spatial gate was a deep blood red, and even smaller, only a fifth of the Asura level gate’s diameter.

For a time, everyone was shocked.

What was going on here?

There were supposed to be four spatial gates – why had another appeared?

Moreover, this spatial gate was smaller than all the other ones present. If so, this meant it was even more difficult than the Asura level gate?

Just as people thought this, someone suddenly paled as he began shivering.

This new smallest spatial gate emitted a horrifying aura, one that affected his soul and nearly ruptured his spiritual sea.

He quickly turned his head. Only then was he able to let out a breath of relief.

Everyone looked away, no longer daring to look at the new spatial gate.

How terrifying!

It was like this gate contained demons.

It seemed that their previous guess had been true!

Then, was there anyone that could actually enter such a gate?

Everyone glanced at each other in dismay. No one knew what to say.

Then, a breathlessly angry voice resounded in the air –

“Fuck, this is such a damn tease!”

Everyone turned their heads. All they saw was the fat man who was eating his fruit suddenly throw the remaining fruits he had on the ground.

“There already isn’t anyone capable of entering that damned red Asura gate, and now one with an even higher difficulty popped up out of nowhere. The brains of the final trial creator are really…”

As the fat man was cursing, he suddenly forcefully swallowed his last words just before he was about to say them.

This was because the reputation of the Asura Road Master was too dazzling. The fat man didn’t dare to violate this final taboo lest he incur the wrath of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws.

As the fat man spoke, the light of the final spatial gate grew increasingly bright. This blinding blood red color made everyone feel as if they were about to tumble into hell, so suffocating that they couldn’t breathe.

As the luminescence reached its peak, they ever feared that glancing at the final spatial gate would cause their souls to fall into chaos.

And in this situation, a person’s blurry figure slowly approached this final spatial gate. However… because of the shroud of blood red light, no one was able to clearly see him.

“I think… someone walked in…”

An Asura Road martial artist hesitantly said with doubt, his eyes leaking tears.

His foundation was solid, his soul force was formidable, and he was also extremely curious. He persisted in looking at the new spatial gate for a little bit longer and seemed to have seen someone’s figure vanish into it.

“Are your eyes blind? You can die in this Gate of Laws trial, so who would dare enter that gate!”

“Don’t joke around. Those who enter that gate are either idiots are they are trying to kill themselves!”

Everyone began arguing with each other. But at this time, a powerful suction force reached out from every spatial gate.

These suction forces contained the power of the Asura Heavenly Dao. All of the trial challengers were sucked into the spatial gates they chose. Then, after they entered, the Gate of Laws slammed tight behind them.

The trial of the Gate of Laws had officially begun.

Chapter 1965 – The Final Gate

After thousands of years, because Lin Ming had chosen an intensely difficult and steep road of martial arts and he had perceived the world of the universe and the world of the body to the peak, his strength hadn’t risen too quickly. One could say he had done everything in perfect order.

Now, facing this Gate of Laws that had never been revealed before, an unusual mood brewed in his heart.

Thousands of years ago, what he had seen in the Asura level gate was also the same.

A dark blue ancient plank road stretched to the horizon, vanishing into a boundless sea of clouds.

Lin Ming stepped onto this ancient plank road.

On the plank road existed the remnant pressure of the Asura Road Master. The deeper one ventured, the greater the pressure.

Lin Ming summoned the power of divinity of the 33 Heavens. Within his body, his self-created universe slowly revolved. The terrifying aura of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws barraged Lin Ming’s mortal body without end.

This strength and this pressure was absorbed into Lin Ming’s inner world. As for what Lin Ming himself had to bear, it wasn’t much at all.

However, the further he walked down this plank road the greater the pressure was.

Slowly, Lin Ming realized that beneath the exertion of this pressure, all of his flesh and blood was being grinded down and his footsteps and even his breath became labored.

This strength was as deep as a sea. Beads of sweat formed on Lin Ming’s forehead.

Lin Ming sat atop the plank road, withstanding the pressure on his body and drawing it into his self-created universe.

Cracking sounds filled the air. Under this pressure, Lin Ming’s inner universe began to emit the sound of breaking.

He frowned. Focusing his mind, the Laws of the Holy Scripture also revolved. A power of endlessness merged into Lin Ming’s inner universe.

Lin Ming closed his eyes, feeling the hundred tastes of a thousand mortal generations. The Great Dao of Life and Death, the samsara of the world, all of these feelings passed through his spiritual sea. Slowly, Lin Ming felt his inner universe not only withstand this pressure but also become constantly compacted beneath it.

Originally, Lin Ming’s inner universe had expanded to 3000 miles.

But in this short period just now, his inner universe was forcefully compressed by a hundred miles, reduced to 2900 miles.

This sort of change left Lin Ming overjoyed. The more his inner universe shrank, the more compact it would become. Although this wouldn’t increase Lin Ming’s strength, it would actually be a tremendous benefit to his future martial arts growth.

Slowly, Lin Ming adapted to this pressure. Then he stood up and continued forwards.

He didn’t worry. He moved forwards slowly. Whenever he felt that he couldn’t withstand the pressure, he would sit down and meditate.

Each time this would take him several hours.

Like this, Lin Ming’s inner world constantly compressed.

When Lin Ming completely passed through the plank road, his inner world had been compressed by 900 miles, making it 2100 miles in size. By this time, a full 12 days had passed in Lin Ming’s journey.

At the end of the plank road existed a vast and ancient continent. At the center of this continent, numerous golden gates stood tall.

These golden gates stretched to the horizon. They covered all the Laws of the 33 Heavens, and this was also the reason why the test from the second level to the third level was called the Gate of Laws.

In the past, Lin Ming had also come to this ancient continent. These golden gates had opened one after another and enemies who represented the Great Daos of the 33 Heavens had appeared.

When Lin Ming defeated all these enemies in turn, the golden gates had disappeared, leaving behind only a single final gate. When this final gate opened, the Black Asura had appeared.

The Black Asura he had ridden a great black dragon and he had also worn deep ruby red armor. His arms and his waist had been wrapped with thick chains.

When Lin Ming first came to the final trial, he had to withstand three spears from this opponent in order to perfectly pass the Asura level difficulty.

But this time, the Gate of Laws that Lin Ming stepped into was clearly far more difficult than the Asura level gate. He had no idea just what sights would greet him.

Because of the Grand Reincarnation Art, Lin Ming’s skeletal age was actually much less than his true age. This also gave him an overwhelming superiority in the final trial.

The endless golden gates shivered. But, none of them opened. They shivered so hard that even the entire ancient continent started to quake. Lin Ming tensed himself and raised his guard, revolving his energy to the limit. He waited for the fierce battle to begin!

With all of the golden gates shaking, Lin Ming even suspected that all the enemies would rush out at him together. If that occurred then this would truly be a brutally frigid battle.

However, he didn’t think that a moment later, all of those golden gates would suddenly quiet down and vanish, without a single enemy appearing.

“Mm?”

Lin Ming was surprised. He gazed around and noticed that there was only a single gate left in the entire continent.

This was extremely similar to the last time Lin Ming had come to the Gate of Laws.

But, what was different was that Lin Ming had leapt over the test of the 33 Heavens’ Laws, passing directly to the end!

Then, what would appear from this final sealed gate?

Lin Ming slowly approached the gate.

This gate was a thousand feet high and as heavy as the earth.

It was engraved with ancient reliefs. As Lin Ming saw these reliefs, he could no longer move his eyes away.

These reliefs contained a beguiling demonic charm that that was indescribable. The 1000 foot square of reliefs seemed to contain a great universe. As Lin Ming looked upon this relief, he felt as he were gazing into a real world.

The surface was engraved with daunting warriors, heaven-destroying magic tools, disintegrating worlds, and also… countless demons.

Some of the demons were as large as planets and some were as small as gravel. They were all perfectly presented on this relief, making it feel unbelievable.

Looking at these demons, Lin Ming felt something strange tickling his mind. This relief should be depicting a great war in ancient times between fierce demons and the rest of the intelligent life that existed.

At this time, the gate suddenly opened!

A horrifying divine light shot out from the slit of the opening gates, cutting through the world like the sword of a divine god!

Lin Ming subconsciously narrowed his eyes. With his sense, he vigilantly prepared to begin this test at any time.

When the gate opened, Lin Ming opened his eyes to see that the world around him had fallen away.

He had arrived in a pure white space.

This feeling was as if a world was sealed into that great gate, and after opening, this world had descended and Lin Ming had been drawn in.

In the endless white was a man’s back.

He quietly stood there, as if he were the only one to exist in the heavens and earth.

This back didn’t seem like that of a phantom, but like that of a real person.

Like this, with his back to Lin Ming, the man slowly stepped backwards.

The moment Lin Ming saw this man he gasped. His blood began to boil and seethe. Facing this man felt as if he were facing the entire universe.

For a time, an unstoppable thought swelled up within Lin Ming’s mind.

He immediately understood that this person was likely… the Asura Road Master!

He was a mere 100 feet away from Lin Ming. Lin Ming could clearly feel the waves of aura that washed off his body.

The man turned around. As he did so, a bright halo of light wrapped around him, blurring his face and making it impossible to clearly see his appearance.

The man raised his right hand. What floated above it was a slowly spinning galaxy.

This galaxy seemed ethereal and unreal, as if it contained the infinite mysterious changes of the universe.

At this time, the man gave off a feeling as if he were the source of the universe’s Laws, the singular epicenter of the 33 Heavenly Daos.

The Asura Road Master, was he the Asura Road Master?

Lin Ming was left dazed for a moment. His heart began to race. The legendary Asura Road Master that was said to possess unparalleled strength now stood in front of him. It was like this was all a dream.

Could it be… the Asura Road Master was planning on giving him the final test?

In the past when Lin Ming passed through the Asura level difficulty, his final test had been to face the Black Asura. Lin Ming had speculated that the Black Asura was the Asura Road Master’s avatar or an incarnation.

And where he was now was a difficulty far higher than the Asura level; it could even be said to be a Gate of Laws that was specifically opened for Lin Ming.

The examiner of this Gate of Laws was actually the Asura Road Master himself!

In the past, the Asura Road Master’s incarnation had been at the True Divinity level! As for the Asura Road Master’s true self, he had likely surpassed the realm of True Divinity…

“Senior!”

Lin Ming took a deep breath and respectfully bowed.

In truth, he had already guessed that the man in front of him was not the true Asura Road Master, but a wisp of will that he had left behind in the past!

Just what kind of test would he hand down?

Lin Ming didn’t know what it would be, but he knew it would be difficult beyond imagination!

Chapter 1966 – Debate In the Void

In the past when Lin Ming faced the Black Asura examiner, he had to withstand three attacks.

Then, if the Asura Road Master had come to personally conduct this test, would it also be a battle? If he were to fight with the Asura Road Master’s true self, what sort of scene would that be?

All sorts of thoughts raced through Lin Ming’s mind. But, what he knew was that regardless of what the result of the test was, the test itself was a great lucky chance.

At this time, the Asura Road Master slowly walked towards Lin Ming.

He gazed at Lin Ming. Even when wrapped in dreamy threads of fog, his profoundly deep eyes were still incomparably clear.

Through these eyes, Lin Ming seemed to see dimensions of universes being born and destroyed within them.

And now, within these eyes, what was actually reflected was Lin Ming.

This clear image was like a mirror, perfectly reflecting Lin Ming’s demeanor and appearance.

Then, the Asura Road Master arrived in front of him.

By this time the Asura Road Master was only a hundred feet away from Lin Ming. He didn’t say a single word but quietly looked on.

The Asura Road Master didn’t emit any aura. In fact he seemed the same as an average mortal person. However, Lin Ming could actually feel a mind-boggling depth of strength from his body.

He knew that this shock came from the Asura Road Master’s body, from the inner universe he possessed.

Like a mortal suddenly arrived in the boundless sea of stars, even when facing the starry space they wouldn’t feel any pressure nor would they feel the aura of the stars, but just by facing it, they would be shocked by how vast and beautiful it was!

Lin Ming held his breath, quietly waiting for the Asura Road Master to give him his test.

At this time, the Asura Road Master raised a hand. With his hand in the air, he used his finger as a pen and began to draw an arc in the void.

This winding line was like a small snake. From start to finish, it formed a perfect circle. Then, the Asura Road Master lowered his finger and started to trace a new line.

Then, the third and fourth. The Asura Road Master continued to draw marks. These marks floated in the void, pale and light, like ripples of water in the air.

Slowly, these marks seemed to blend together with the world, becoming intangible and invisible. If the average person were to come here they wouldn’t even be able to see the Asura Road Master’s finger.

But Lin Ming was able to revolve the Asura Heavenly Dao within him to the limit and see these ripple-like marks. In truth, they were forming runes!

These were Asura Heavenly Dao runes!

The Asura Road Master was drawing runes, and the clear purpose was that he was preparing them for Lin Ming.

Then, Lin Ming understood.

These runes could be called his own exam page. The test that the Asura Road Master was giving him was not a battle of strength but a debate of the Laws!

To debate with the Asura Road Master?

Lin Ming took a deep breath, feeling this a bit inconceivable.

He never thought the test method would be like this…

He was well aware that this would be a tremendous challenge for him but at the same time a rare opportunity.

These were runes personally drawn by the Asura Road Master, the most essential manifestation of the Asura Heavenly Dao!

At this time, the Asura Road Master had stopped drawing. He held his hands behind his back and looked at Lin Ming, waiting for his reply.

Lin Ming took a deep breath, completely bringing his mind to tranquility.

He carefully observed these Heavenly Dao runes. They were relatively simple amongst the Asura Heavenly Dao.

It seemed that at the very start, the Asura Road Master didn’t raise too difficult a problem.

Or, in the eyes of the Asura Road Master, a junior like Lin Ming could be sufficiently proud in comprehending the Laws to such a degree at such an age.

Lin Ming pondered for a moment. Within his eyes, these runes branded themselves in his spiritual sea where they were rapidly analyzed.

After several reincarnations, Lin Ming had tempered himself in the bustle of the mortal plane and his state of mind had reached near perfection. He had even partially fused the Concepts of the Holy Scripture into the Asura Scripture. Now, Lin Ming’s understanding of the Asura Sutra had in truth begun to gradually separate from the Asura Laws created by the Asura Road Master, as he stepped onto a different path.

In this sort of situation, Lin Ming no longer simply accepted and studied the Asura Sutra, but was comprehending a version that belonged to himself.

After sitting in meditation for half an hour, Lin Ming finally moved!

Rays of energy gathered on his fingertip. Using his finger as a pen, Lin Ming began to portray his own Asura Heavenly Dao lines.

One stroke after another, the lines drawn by Lin Ming began to intersect with those left behind by the Asura Road Master.

Compared to a heaven-shaking and world-destroying scene that would occur when top supreme elders fought, this confrontation of writing could be called simple and mediocre with nothing wonderful or dazzling about it.

However, reality was different. When the lines of the Asura Heavenly Dao that Lin Ming drew connected with those drawn by the Asura Road Master, a brilliant burst of light flashed out, impacting into the heavens like a divine pillar of light!

A martial artist’s cultivation method was in truth a manifestation of the Laws.

As for drawing runes, they were the condensation of the Laws. They contained a terrifying momentum, in no way weaker than the cultivation method itself.

When two martial artists who had reached extremely high attainments in the comprehension of Laws began to engage in a vigorous debate using Law lines, although the eruption wouldn’t sweep through the world with energy that could shatter planets, it would still emit a horrifying aura and momentum that was similar to a martial artist’s billowing blood vitality during the heat of battle. As it lit up the skies, its glory could compete with the sun and moon!

Ka ka ka!

Lin Ming’s drawing speed became increasingly fast. The void of the final trial unexpectedly seemed as if it couldn’t withstand the pressure of Lin Ming’s strokes connecting with the Asura Road Master’s. With a crisp sound, it seemed to crack open.

Then, the Asura Road Master’s complexion changed!

He never thought that the Law lines he casually drew up would arouse such an intense fighting momentum from a junior.

It seemed… that he had underestimated this junior!

Seeing the lines he drew being slowly swallowed up, the Asura Road Master’s lips curved up.

He smiled, and this was also a smile of appreciation and admiration.

To have the Asura Road Master, a man who once stood at the peak of the 33 Heavens and ruled over the ancient era, show appreciation towards someone else, this was enough to leave behind a legend!

At this time, the Asura Road Master took a step forwards. He took out a spear from his spatial ring!

He began to use this spear as a pen to draw the lines of the Asura Heavenly Dao!

This time, the Asura Road Master’s drawn lines were much denser. Every line tore through the void, galloping like horses, filled with endlessly daring spirit and majesty.

Lin Ming began to heat up with excitement. He also drew out the Black Dragon Spear and engaged in a vigorous debate with the Asura Road Master!

Lin Ming’s drawings were soft and supple, continuous and without end.

As the two fought, it was like the sun and moon battling for supremacy!

This was a fierce confrontation. If an outsider were to see it they would be dumbfounded. In their opinion, it was unimaginable for people to be able to engage in such an incredible debate of the Laws.

It should be said that they would never imagine fighting could occur in such a way!

Only peak Laws like the Asura Heavenly Dao, and only with someone who understood the Asura Heavenly Dao to such a deep degree like Lin Ming, would be able to engage in such a splendid duel of Laws!

As time passed, Lin Ming noticed that he was slowly starting to fall behind.

But at the same time, the appreciative smile on the Asura Road Master’s face became increasingly wide and vibrant.

The truth was that the Asura Road Master had only been using an infinitesimally portion of his strength. He had probed Lin Ming and after discovering that Lin Ming was much stronger than he had anticipated, he had then begun to slowly increase the strength behind the Laws he drew. Like this, Lin Ming was naturally worn down the longer they went.

Ka ka ka!

A connection of lines!

Beads of sweat poured down Lin Ming’s forehead. The lines he drew were swallowed up in massive amounts. Some strokes he drew shattered, turning into Law fragments that scattered away in the void.

After all of Lin Ming’s drawings exploded, the Asura Road Master faintly chuckled and put away his long spear.

And at this time, Lin Ming’s body had reached exhaustion and he nearly slumped to the ground. A battle of Laws didn’t use energy, but it was an enormous consumption of one’s soul force and mental strength. After Lin Ming had gone through several incarnations, his spiritual sea had been tempered enough that he could last until now.

He held himself up with the Black Dragon Spear, taking great heaving breaths.

And at this time, in front of him, the Asura Road Master lifted his finger and began to draw once more in the void.

This time, the Asura Road Master’s drawing speed was extremely slow.

His writing had become pale again. But the things he drew up were entirely different from what he drew just awhile ago.

Originally, the Asura Road Master’s writings had contained a deep and profound buddha-killing intent, swift and fierce, aggressive beyond belief.

But now, the things the Asura Road Master drew up were soft and restrained, but also contained the Great Dao of the world. They were things that were hard to feel, that were elusive to the mind.

Without a doubt, the depth of the Laws that the Asura Road Master drew this time were on a higher level than those he drew just then!

Lin Ming gazed upon these Law runes. Although he didn’t immediately understand them, he could feel that these runes were all incomplete!

Incomplete rune after incomplete rune was drawn up by the Asura Road Master.

As if he were waiting for someone to fill them, make them whole again.

“Could this be… my test question?”

Lin Ming suddenly understood. The Asura Road Master was waiting for him to complete these runes. If he could accomplish this, that was the same as passing the test.

Perhaps this was also the final topic.

Lin Ming wasn’t in a hurry to complete these runes. He sat down where he was and entered the fused martial intent state, meditating.

He completely entered the ethereal state. After several hours of meditation, his soul force had slowly restored to its peak.

Then, Lin Ming finally opened his eyes and began to perceive these runes.

In front of Lin Ming hung a total of 33 runes, just enough to represent the Laws of the 33 Heavens.

Slowly, Lin Ming forgot the passage of time, forgot himself, forgot all else. He completely sunk his mind into these mysterious Law runes.

Within each rune seemed to be a phantom of the Asura Road Master. Lin Ming could faintly feel that these phantoms were incarnations left behind by the Asura Road Master in the past.

And these runes contained the complete summarized understandings of the Asura Road Master’s knowledge of the Asura Heavenly Dao.

Chapter 1967 – Completing the Laws

Every rune that the Asura Road Master drew up was only missing a very small part. Even so, making up this tiny part was as difficult as ascending to heaven.

As Lin Ming was intoxicated in his enlightened state, the Asura Road Master slowly stepped back.

He gently waved his hand and an energy enchantment fell over the world. This enchantment changed the flow of time.

The Asura Road Master’s understandings of the Time Laws had reached an incomprehensible degree. When he changed the flow of time he could even avoid the distortion of Laws that occurred in the enchantment, allowing Lin Ming to perceive the Laws as he practiced his cultivation method.

Tragic Death Valley had been such a situation. The flow of time within Tragic Death Valley had been at a 10:1 ratio compared to the outside world.

Currently, this time enchantment sped up time to an even more incredible degree, achieving a ratio of 30:1. Three days outside represented three months within the time enchantment.

This was a time extension given to Lin Ming by the Asura Road Master. In order to make up the missing parts of these runes, that was something that required more than a few days and nights. But, the final trial actually had a time limit, and once that time limit was reached, everyone within would be transmitted outside.

As Lin Ming was diligently perceiving the Laws, within the space of the final trial, other people were slowly passing the Gate of Laws.

The Gate of Laws was the tunnel that connected the second level to the third level. After the Gate of Laws was the third level, and the third level had no dangers, only rewards.

If some people didn’t have full faith they could overcome the fourth level then they could withdraw to the third level until the final trial was over.

More and more people arrived at the third level. The first martial artists that appeared were those who had chosen the mortal step difficulty. Afterwards, more and more trial challengers appeared.

They gathered at the end of the Gate of Laws, discussing their harvests and experiences during their trials.

Many of them beamed with joy. With so many juniors gathered together, it was natural for them to begin comparing who was better and worse.

And as all of these people were discussing, the heaven step level Gate of Laws began to tremble.

All of the martial artists looked over. As they saw the heaven-step Gate of Laws begin vibrating, their eyes started to shine with awe.

They faintly guessed just what was occurring.

Ka ka ka!

As the Gate of Laws opened, a woman rushed out.

She seemed a bit distressed, her clothes were torn in many areas and there was even a trail of blood flowing from the corners of her lips.

This person was the gray-clothed woman from Soaring Feather God Mountain. She had succeeded in passing the heaven-step Gate of Laws!

This was the same difficulty that Sheng Mei had chosen in the past. Although it was impossible for the gray-clothed woman to perfectly pass it, she could be more than proud of her current accomplishments.

Then, the heaven-step Gate of Laws began to shake once more!

Another figure rushed out from the Gate of Laws. This time, it was the fat elder senior-apprentice brother from the Good Fortune Saint Palace.

There were many marks on his body and his face was a bit purple. Even so, the fat man’s face was shining with a smile and his mood was excellent.

“Elder Senior-apprentice Brother came out!”

Seeing the fat man come out, the Good Fortune Saint Palace’s disciples hurriedly stepped forwards. “How much did Senior-apprentice Brother complete?”

Seeing the fat man’s good mood, some people quickly asked.

“Not much, just around 80%.”

The fat man casually said. But, as these words fell into the ears of others, this left them dumbfounded.

An 80% completion rate of the heaven-step difficulty; this result left everyone feeling flabbergasted.

In the world of martial artists, power was worshipped above all. This fat man might not be pleasing to look at or listen to, but he came from the Good Fortune Saint Palace and his strength was extraordinary, naturally powerful.

The fat man chuckled. In this final trial, he could be called the leading player.

He looked at the gray-clothed woman standing not too far away. She frowned. Her result was somewhat worse than the fat man’s.

And, the results of her subordinates were faintly inferior to the other disciples of the Good Fortune Saint Palace.

There simply wasn’t anything that could be done about this. Soaring Feather God Mountain was a hidden sect and couldn’t compare to the Good Fortune Saint Palace that held absolute control over all resources of the saints.

“Let’s begin and choose our rewards!”

The fat man said with high spirits. The third level of the final trial was completely covered with immortal palaces. Every immortal palace held treasures and the trial challengers could enter them according to the total completion percentage they had obtained so far.

The moment he chose his reward, the fat man had a strange tingling feeling at the back of his mind. He turned around at looked at the blood red gate on the right side of the Asura level gate; the one that was smallest.

This spatial gate emitted fluctuations of energy that shook the heart, as if something earth-shaking was occurring within.

If one had to forcefully describe this new fifth Gate of Laws that had appeared, then calling it the Gate of Hell would be the most appropriate.

After Asura was Hell. For some unknown reason, the fat man was a bit uneasy as he stared at this spatial gate…

……

Time passed, day after day.

Within the Gate of Laws, Lin Ming continued to feel out the runes that the Asura Road Master had left behind.

After three months, Lin Ming still hadn’t attempted filling in these 33 runes.

He had drawn countless deductions in the air, but all of them had dissipated in failure.

These deductions consumed a tremendous amount of mental strength. Even though Lin Ming’s soul force had been tempered for such a long time, he still had to regularly stop and meditate to restore himself.

A fourth month, fifth month, soon, half a year passed. From deep in his trance, Lin Ming’s eyes suddenly popped open. His two pupils gleamed like bright stars.

He lifted his hand and finally drew in a key part on the first rune. And after he drew this, he felt the entire rune come to life, slowly starting to change. It turned into a burning flame. This flame began to beat with an unusual tempo; this was the fire of the universe’s most source Great Dao.

Although it wasn’t too blazing, every flame that Lin Ming had ever experienced in his life, whether it was fires of the forests, fires beneath the earth, fires of the sun, the fires of jealousy or the fires of hate, every fire had their shadow within this beating flame.

Lin Ming pondered for a moment and then drew another stroke.

As this stroke went down, the feeling of the rune changed again. In this rune, Lin Ming could see flashing thunder.

This was a vast sea covered with dark skies, with violent winds rising from all over. A terrifying sword of thunder cut through the skies like the spear of a divine god, destroying all things in its way.

The thunder changed without end. From time to time it was brutal, from time to time it was quick. Lin Ming even saw Thunder Souls and Thunder Sources amongst them, the most essential force of the power of thunder.

Even the different types of thunder that he absorbed with the Heretical God Tree began to flash before him.

As if struck with inspiration, Lin Ming drew a third stroke…

With this stroke, thunder and flame seemed to fuse as one.

This was the core of Lin Ming’s Heretical God Force – the fusion of thunder and flame.

When Lin Ming first stepped on the road of martial arts, he had relied on Thunderfire Annihilation to recklessly sweep his way through the South Horizon Region.

Now, Lin Ming had become aware of the highest Asura Heavenly Dao Laws, opening up his own road of martial arts. He smoothed out and paved the Laws he comprehended.

Lin Ming fell quiet. Then, he added several more strokes to this rune, making it even more perfect.

Next, Lin Ming turned to a second rune.

This time he didn’t take too long. After a mere hour, he moved.

His fingertip was filled with the power of divinity from the 33 Heavens. He drew out a trace of blue.

As this line appeared the surrounding space twisted up. Light was swallowed, vanishing without a trace.

This simple stroke had caused a mutation in the Space Laws. He continued without stopping. With a turn of his pen, he drew out another stroke. This stroke was purple and gave off an extremely strange feeling, as if it weren’t a marking but the endless vicissitudes of time itself…

These two markings were respectively the manifestations of space and time. Lin Ming drew all his comprehensions of space and time into this rune.

Lin Ming’s pen didn’t stop there. He drew line after line, causing space and time to be muddled and distorted, making it impossible to distinguish its size, making it impossible to distinguish whether it came from the past or future.

Within Lin Ming’s writing time and space also fused as one.

In truth, the Asura Road Master’s incomplete runes had no singular answer. As long as Lin Ming could fuse the Laws he learned into the 33 Heavens Asura Laws and complete the runes, then he would pass.

Lin Ming started to draw upon the third rune.

This time, countless starlight seemed to fall with the stroke of his pen. Every movement seemed to depict a star.

These stars became more and more realistic. As they floated in the void, seven were bright and two were dark. Faintly, Dao Palaces lay atop these stars. These were the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace that Lin Ming had comprehended.

In the past, the Asura Road Master’s 33 incarnations had comprehended the Great Daos of the 33 Heavens. The Nine Stars of the Dao Palace was one of these.

Lin Ming’s understandings of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace were fused into the Asura rune.

Stroke after stroke, Lin Ming tirelessly and diligently drew. Every drawing Lin Ming made resonated with the Laws around him.

As his inner world sympathetically resonated with the surrounding Laws, it was also baptized!

The Great Dao was boundless and the Laws were infinite.

Lin Ming’s inner world compressed once more, and this compression was even more thorough than before. His inner world was now only a thousand miles. Compared to the 3000 miles it was when he first entered the Gate of Laws, it was three times smaller!

Even the gaps that had been left over in Lin Ming’s self-created world began to be eliminated during this compression!

Lin Ming’s condition became increasingly vivid. The pen he wielded seemed to fly as the power of divinity wildly gushed out. His mental strength also entered an impassioned state.

He even fused in the awareness he had gained after reincarnating several times, the enlightenment of the samsara of life and death, of the changes and emotions of mortals. All of these things were fused into the runes.

The Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra were originally top cultivation methods that lay at the peak of martial arts. In so many billions of years, Lin Ming was the only one able to achieve such high attainments in both cultivation methods. Even so, it was extremely difficult for him to fuse them together!

But today, after Lin Ming entered this utterly entranced state, he had forcefully added the charm of the Concepts of Life and Death into these Asura Heavenly Dao runes!

Under these actions, the Holy Scripture and Heavenly Sutra began to subtly unify, becoming increasingly close.

Rune after rune was completed. Yet Lin Ming didn’t complete the runes in order but was wildly drawing where his instinct brought him, as if he were drawing some splendid yet incomprehensible work of art.

Suddenly, Lin Ming felt that the Laws he wrote down had neared perfection. In the final moment, his beautiful writings swerved like dragons and snakes, completing the final stroke.

In that instant Lin Ming fell to his knees in exhaustion. But in front of him, the aura of the Heavenly Dao that had been suppressed for so long suddenly shot into the skies like a pillar of divine light!

Rumble rumble rumble!

Thunder flashed and flames billowed. The void shook.

The 33 Asura Heavenly Dao runes that dangled in the air began shining together, their divine light pouring into the world as if a spiritual god was being born. The world filled with the most mystical brilliance of the Great Dao…

Lin Ming had finally completed all 33 Asura runes!

Shua!

The time enchantment opened. The Asura Road Master looked at the utterly exhausted Lin Ming and also the 33 Asura runes that shimmered in front of him. A look of praise filled his eyes.

The Law runes that Lin Ming filled in might not be perfect, but to the Asura Road Master, his work had completely surpassed the limitations of a World King level martial artist.

Even a True Divinity might not be able to accomplish this!

This wasn’t because Lin Ming’s strength had reached the level of a True Divinity, but because during his last several reincarnations his understands of the Laws had reached an unbelievable degree. In addition to all the lucky chances he had ever obtained working in tandem with him, he had been able to complete all of this!

Chapter 1970 – The Secret Treasure in the Swamp

This blackwater swamp was extremely broad, thousands of miles in diameter. The disciples of the Good Fortune Saint Palace had searched for six or seven days on end, but they had only managed to search 60% of it.

By this time, many trial challengers had gathered at the entrance towards the fifth level. They had passed the fourth level’s test and were waiting for the entrance to the fifth level to open.

This situation left the Good Fortune Saint Palace disciples somewhat worried. They didn’t have much time remaining. If they weren’t able to smoothly fulfill their mission then their fates would be miserable indeed.

This wasn’t a punishment that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had deliberately passed down to them. In a sense, this was a path they had chosen on their own. In order to obtain great power, they had to take an equally dangerous risk.

“Continue searching. We still have three days. Once the fifth level opens, no one is allowed to stay on the fourth level. You can either return to the third level or enter the fifth level… in other words, we have to find that thing before then.”

The fat man gloomily said. Everyone’s expressions became earnest.

The truth was that they were afraid they had missed something in the 60% of the land they had just searched. If they did that, then the consequences would be unimaginable.

Time passed. Every now and then, trial challengers would pass close by and see that the disciples of the Good Fortune Saint Palace were searching the swamp, and guessed that they were seeking out some sort of peerless treasure. But because the Good Fortune Saint Palace was too strong, they didn’t dare to have any wild ambitions and left beneath the threat of the fat man and the others.

Nightfall. The disciples of the Good Fortune Saint Palace tirelessly worked away.

The dark swamp was filled with perils. They had killed dozens and hundreds of poisonous insects and snakes without stopping.

And as the sun dawned, one of the disciples suddenly felt their arm stiffen. Within his palm the red ball of meat was gently trembling.

“Elder… Elder Senior-apprentice Brother!”

The disciple cried out.

“What is it?!”

The fat man’s mind had been incredibly taut these past several days. When someone called out to him, he reflexively turned his head.

As for his beady eyes, they didn’t look towards the man’s face but towards his hand, where the red meat ball was wriggling about, faintly distorting.

“Quick! Search over there!”

The fat man hurriedly instructed. Immediately, all of the Good Fortune Saint Palace disciples that were spread out within 10 miles began arriving at this area.

The truth was that the balls of meat in their hands were the flesh and blood of Famine!

The thing they searched for was buried deep in the earth, and its Laws were extremely high. With their strength they were unable to sense it at all. This was the reason this thing had been buried in the fourth level of the final trial for such a long time and yet no one had obtained it before.

But by using Famine’s flesh and blood, they could form a connection to this thing. By relying on this connection, they could locate the final position of this thing.

“It’s close! Yes, it must be that thing!”

The fat man’s breathing quickened, his entire mental state extremely tight. If he could bring back this thing then his future path would be unimaginable!

At this time, the Good Fortune Saint Palace disciples felt the flesh and blood of Famine in their hands become increasingly soft and viscous. From a solid state, it dissolved into bloody water.

“It turned watery…”

One disciple muttered. The flesh and blood of Famine in his hand completely melted away, streaming down from between the seams of his fingers and down into the black swamp.

Then, something amazing occurred.

The melted flesh turned into little red meat worms that gradually sank into the swampy ground and drilled deep into it.

“Start digging!”

The fat man decisively said.

“This…” Someone hesitated as they heard the fat man’s order. “When a rare treasure is born it will definitely send out a terrifying aura. At that time, many trial challengers will be drawn.”

Hearing the junior-apprentice brother’s words, the fat man diabolically grinned. “If they come then they come. It won’t be easy to dig this thing out. It has a demonic nature and there needs to be a blood sacrifice…”

As the fat man spoke, a faint killing intent exuded from him. Even the disciples of the Good Fortune Saint Palace felt their hearts quaking.

If this were normal times, then no matter how strong the disciples of the Good Fortune Saint Palace were, they wouldn’t be able to use their 20 some numbers to defend against the onslaught of all the other trial challengers.

Unless, they were to use a forbidden power…

However, they didn’t want to use this power. “When a rare treasure is born it needs a blood sacrifice? Is this accurate news that Senior-apprentice Brother obtained?”

“It is what the God Sovereign has speculated; it shouldn’t be wrong. Alright, enough with the chatter, let’s start digging!”

This swamp was formed from mud. To the martial artists here, wanting to dig into it was as simple as cutting into tofu.

The black-clothed martial artists thrust out their weapons, stabbing a pit hundreds and thousands of feet deep. However, they weren’t digging long before they discovered that the ground resistance began to increase.

This change left the fat man disgruntled yet overjoyed. He knew that they were digging closer and closer to the rare treasure!

…….

“I have to say… are you planning to enter the fifth level?”

In a corner of the fourth level, several trial challengers were rummaging through a pile of junk-like scraps of magic tools that they had unearthed from an ancient ruin.

However, as time passed they bitterly found out that these magic tool fragments weren’t left behind from the era of the Asura Road Master. At most, these fragments were around a hundred million years old. In other words, a hundred million years ago, there were some trial challengers that entered the final trial and experienced dangers that caused them to all perish here.

This left everyone frustrated. They had spent so much effort in finding these things but they had turned out to be garbage.

They had spent a great deal of time in the fourth level and had overcome many dangers, but the harvests they obtained were very few. They could only blame their bad luck and poor destinies.

As for the even more dangerous fifth level, they couldn’t help but mull over whether or not they actually had the ability to enter that area.

As they were stuck in this dilemma, they felt a horrifying aura, one that rushed over them like an overwhelming tide.

As they were covered by this aura, they immediately felt as if they had fallen into hell. A dreadful killing intent covered them, causing them to drip with cold sweat and nearly vomit blood.

They turned their heads and saw that in the far off horizon, an astonishing scene was occurring!

A mass of terrifying black aura hurtled into the skies, forming a massive ghostly phantom head!

This phantom head was incomparably ferocious. It transformed again and again in the skies, seeming to swallow up everyone!

And this terrifying aura was undoubtedly from that ghostly phantom!

“Heavens! What is that!?”

“Was some supreme treasure born?”

“Supreme treasure?” Everyone glanced at each other. If such a rare treasure were born and it also possessed such a strong demonic strength…

If they were to recklessly rush over then they might experience some great danger.

But with the opportunity placed in front of them, they weren’t willing to give up without a struggle!

“Look! Some people are headed over!”

Several people looked up to see black spots moving in the skies, hurtling towards that ghost head phantom at an extremely fast speed!

With others flying over, although the competition would become even more difficult, it also gave a sense of security.

People believed that if so many went over, with so many other people there the chances of them dying wouldn’t be high… right?

“Let’s go take a look!”

With this, everyone launched their movement techniques and hurtled towards the location at full speed.

And not too far away, Lin Ming also saw all this occur. He frowned. This aura… somehow, for some unknown reason that he couldn’t place a finger on, felt somewhat familiar.

He thought for a moment. Then, he slowly closed his eyes and opened them again. When he did, a strange sight occurred.

Lin Ming’s pupils had changed. His pupils had become like a small needle, and around this small needle were many strange patterns.

These patterns stretched out, emitting a sense of mystery.

For a time, beneath Lin Ming’s eyes, all the Laws in the surrounding space were unable to hide from him.

This arcane skill was Three Lives Old Man’s Three Lives Pupils!

In the past when the Divine Realm was invaded by the saints, humanity was in peril. Three Lives Old Man had decided to end his life in a fleeting moment of glory. But before he left, he had used some time to pass on the Three Lives Pupils technique to Lin Ming.

Lin Ming had originally opened the Daevic Eye Dao Palace. When combined with the Three Lives Pupils, both abilities complemented each other!

And beneath the gaze of the Three Lives Pupils, what Lin Ming saw was completely different. He saw a monstrous flame seething into the skies, burning pitch black. And in this black flame one could faintly see countless pained souls caged within. There were also the skeletons of kings, floating amidst it…

“This is…”

Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath, his heart shaking!

Chapter 1973 – Artificial Demon

“Famine? How is this…” Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with shock. This was absolutely not the saints’ body metamorphosis, but a strength that came directly from Famine!

And at this time, the clothes on the fat man’s back had already been blown apart. Massive bloody pustules rose up from his back.

Gurgle gurgle!

These pustules violently wriggled and crept, growing larger and larger until they exploded open. As blood and plasma flew into the air, several python-like tentacles rose out from these pustules, dancing all about.

“This is…”

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. There was no way he would mistake these tentacles for something else; they were Famine’s blood dragon tentacles! The only difference was that on the fat man’s body, they had shrunk countless times over.

At this time, the fat man was already completely unrecognizable from his past appearance. He had become a 20 foot tall blood red demon with fierce bone spikes that jutted out and thickly corded muscles wrapped around him. Eight tentacles flapped about from behind him.

Seeing the fat man, everyone was bewildered. This blood red life form didn’t seem like a person at all, but a manmade demon!

“This is strength that comes from Famine… I understand now.” Lin Ming recalled Empyrean Primordius from thousands of years ago.

At that time, when Lin Ming saw Empyrean Primordius, Empyrean Primordius’ appearance had been that of a demon. But he didn’t have Famine’s tentacles. Instead, what he had were sharp bone blades.

Empyrean Primordius had seized the body of an abyssal and had turned into that appearance. This fat man was likely in a similar situation.

Someone had artificially implanted Famine’s flesh and blood within his body!

The body of an abyssal demon was nearly impossible to seize. After Empyrean Primordius seized the body of an abyssal, he had lost his sense of self.

And the fat man’s strength was clearly far inferior to that of Empyrean Primordius. To have him attempt to seize the body of an abyssal was the same as delivering food to it instead. However, if his body was implanted with the flesh and blood of Famine then that was different.

This was because Famine’s flesh and blood was under the control of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign.

This flesh and blood would obey the orders of others and as a result, it wouldn’t swallow the fat man.

“So that’s what is happening… as Famine becomes more powerful and as the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s control over it becomes increasingly tight, he can split off parts of Famine’s flesh and blood and plant it into the bodies of high level martial artists to compose artificial demons. If the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s controlling ability is powerful enough then he can even form a legion of demons!”

It could be imagined that this demon legion would possess a terrifying battle efficiency. At the same time, they were also completely controlled by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. This was because due to their bodies being fused with Famine’s flesh and blood, a mere thought from the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and they wouldn’t even have their bones remaining!

As Lin Ming realized all of this, he could sense that the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign’s ambitions were becoming increasingly great. Through Famine, there were far, far too many matters he could deal with. Slowly he would be able to extend his control over the entire 33 Heavens. Of course, this was all based on the premise that he could defeat the equally ambitious Soul Emperor.

“What is that monster!?”

As the trial challengers saw this fat man’s change, all of them felt weak at heart. This came from Famine’s aura. As a once incomparably terrifying existence, once Famine’s flesh and blood was fused into the fat man’s body, the aura it carried with it caused all the trial challengers present to feel fear and dread.

“That should be the saint race’s body metamorphosis! It’s just that we’ve never seen this version before!” Some people said to comfort themselves and also raise their morale. However, at this time, the fat man chuckled.

“You… do you all really think this is the saint race’s body metamorphosis…?”

As the fat man spoke, blue veins pulsated over his body like worms. It was like every syllable he spoke was incredibly difficult to get out.

His voice had completely changed. It was hoarse, low, and deep. The change of his body had caused his voice to seem not like a person’s at all.

At this time, every change within the fat man’s body was caught in Lin Ming’s eyes.

“His blood vitality… is burning away. Famine’s flesh and blood is swallowing his cells! If he tries to maintain this kind of body metamorphosis for too long then he will die. It seems this body metamorphosis has a tremendous limitation placed on it. Using it a single time will cause one to lose a great part of their life force and also affect their future boundary. There is even a chance that they will be swallowed up by Famine instead.”

Lin Ming thought as he sensed the blood vitality within the fat man. Famine was an abyssal demon and its attribute was to swallow all. This was the ‘instinct’ that was carved into every inch of Famine’s flesh and blood.

Even with the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign restraining it, it was difficult to completely write off this sort of instinct.

“Ever since this forbidden strength was planted within me… this is my first time using it. You should all feel honored!”

As the fat man spoke he roared and hurled himself towards an inner Asura Road disciple!

That inner Asura Road disciple came from Divine Void Divine Kingdom. Amongst the trial challengers here, his strength was in the upper echelons.

“Be careful!”

Someone cried out in alarm.

But, the fat man was too fast; his speed surpassed the reaction ability of those present.

The Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciple had been tempered through numerous tests of life and death. Although his brain didn’t respond his body already started to reflexively move, independently acting in this critical moment.

He leapt backwards. At the same time, he took out a thick saber and chopped downwards. A thick and sticky darkness spilled out from his saber like ink. This darkness contained a powerful divine soul attack!

Hu –

The thick darkness roared, forming a death god phantom. The death god phantom grasped a scythe as it rushed towards the fat man’s spiritual sea!

This was a transcendent divine might of Divine Void Divine Kingdom, an arcane skill specifically used to strike the spiritual sea. This Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciple was smart enough; seeing that he couldn’t dodge the fat man’s attack, he decided to use offense as defense instead!

The fat man’s body metamorphosis could immediately be seen to augment the mortal body; it was the obvious choice to attack the opponent’s spiritual sea instead.

Kacha!

The Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciple’s saber was caught by the fat man. At the same time, the death god’s scythe came slashing down at the fat man’s head!

This fat man completely disregarded the death god’s scythe. Rather, he reached out, grasping towards the Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciple’s heart.

“You –”

The Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciple’s eyes flashed with deep disbelief. He stared helplessly on as the death god’s scythe cut into the fat man’s head. But at the same time, a cold feeling bloomed in his chest. The fat man’s sharp claws had thrust into his chest and grabbed onto his beating heart.

“No - !”

The feeling of having one’s heart held was indescribable. Fear and helplessness covered the Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciple’s eyes. Before he could finish speaking, the fat man cruelly grinned and twisted his right hand, twisting apart the Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciple’s blood vessels and ripping out his heart.

Puff!

Blood shot out. The Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciple’s expression stiffened and his body toppled over like a dead dog. As he tumbled away, he could see the fat man holding his beating, dripping, heart, and then directly swallowing it whole.

“Ahh!”

A trial challenger cried out in fear. This body-metamorphosized demonic fat man had actually eaten someone’s heart!

Moreover, what frightened these people the most was that the Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciple’s soul attack seemed to not injure the fat man at all. The Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciple clearly excelled in divine soul attacks, but such an attack was easily withstood by the fat man!

Could this fat man’s weakness be his body instead?

Looking at the fat man’s body that seemed cast with thick iron-hard muscles, the trial challengers couldn’t summon the courage to deal with him using material attacks.

If his mortal bodily defense was even stronger than his soul defense, then this was completely a monster!

“Famine’s flesh and blood swallowed up that disciple’s soul attack…” Lin Ming was able to see what had occurred. Famine was a terrifying existence. Its ability was to swallow all. It could even swallow the Heavenly Dao rules, so what was swallowing a divine soul attack?

After fusing with Famine, not to mention the increase in strength, but this defensive ability to swallow energy, material, and divine soul attacks made it so that all other martial artists at the same level would be helpless to do anything.

This was a truly terrifying monster!

Lin Ming closely observed the changes occurring in the fat man’s body. But at this time, the Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciple’s body started to shake. Beneath the gaze of all present, his entire body melted away.

The meat on his body and face seemed to melt away like fat under high heat. It flowed down in bloody water mixed with yellow goo, finally leaving behind nothing but bones.

As everyone saw this they were panic-stricken; they had no idea what had occurred.

Then, as if it was being summoned, this bloody water slowly gathered into a stream that flowed into the pit behind the fat man where it was completely absorbed by the pitch black bone column.

Seeing this, the fat man smiled. He revealed teeth that were dyed red with blood. “The demon relic is quite greedy… at such a close distance, it is even willing to swallow ordinary flesh and blood… if it is the flesh and blood of an abyssal then it would be even greater… after undergoing my body metamorphosis, even though I am able to consciously imprison the energy in my flesh and blood, I can still feel its demonic call!”

“Elder Senior-apprentice Brother, isn’t this something that His Majesty the Saint Sovereign values? Today, let us keep this crowd of garbage here and use their flesh and blood to feed the demon relic! This is the best use of waste!”

Behind the fat man, another disciple from the Good Fortune Saint Palace spoke up. His body also started to change. His flesh and blood wriggled about as if numerous insects were crawling beneath his skin.

He had a pained expression etched on his face, as if his body metamorphosis process was far more difficult than the fat man’s. It was obvious that his ability to control Famine’s flesh and blood was far inferior to the fat man’s.

“Another one!”

A trial challenger shouted out as he saw another Good Fortune Saint Palace disciple undergo that body metamorphosis. He felt his limbs turn cold and his heart drop into his stomach. He feared that there were several demons within the group of Good Fortune Saint Palace disciples. It was even possible that they were all like that!

“This feeling, is truly life-taking… I almost thought I would die, haha…”

After the second Good Fortune Saint Palace disciple completed his body metamorphosis, he began panting for breath, as if he had lost nearly half his life. This was the forbidden power they worried about when they were searching for the demon relic.

This power, while giving them formidable strength, would also take their life. It required constant conditioning from the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign in order to overcome the difficulties and successfully undergo body metamorphosis without dying. But, to have the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign waste time and energy to condition them, this proved their value. That value was to find the demon relic!

After completing this mission, one day they would be able to completely fuse with Famine’s flesh and blood, obtaining an undying body!

Chapter 1977A – Stirring Up Trouble

At this time, the only ones left alive were the two disciples from Soaring Feather God Mountain and the several dozen Asura Road disciples. When Lin Ming turned his eyes towards these Asura Road disciples, all of them held their breath.

Among these people, Lin Ming could see several youths wearing a uniform robe as well as having seven-colored feather crowns on their heads.

He recognized this clothing – these people came from Divine Void Divine Kingdom!

Divine Void Divine Kingdom was one of the two True Divinity level influences of the Asura Road. The one who established Divine Void Divine Kingdom, Soul Emperor Divine Void, was Empyrean Divine Mist’s brother. But at the same time, they shared a deep-seated blood hatred with each other.

“The lot of you, come over here!”

Lin Ming pointed towards the disciples from Divine Void Divine Kingdom. The group of them turned pale white.

However, they obediently followed Lin Ming’s orders and walked over.

“Use your soul attacks to severely wound these two. Don’t kill them.”

Lin Ming pointed towards the two Soaring Feather God Mountain disciples who were imprisoned by him.

The Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciples gulped. Just why did they need to use soul attacks?

Did this omnipotent human not know any soul attacks? However, this was also possible. After all, humans weren’t known to excel in the domain of the soul.

After a brief bout of doubts, the Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciples complied with the command.

Although Lin Ming had imprisoned the movements of the two Soaring Feather God Mountain disciples, he hadn’t locked down their spiritual sea. To break through spiritual sea defenses, not harming their lives while getting just the right amount of soul damage, this was a difficult task. The two Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciples that did so could be said to have given their everything to accomplish this.

Finally, they accomplished their task. The two disciples from Soaring Feather God Mountain fell into an unconscious state.

Lin Ming inspected the condition of these two disciples and was satisfied with the results.

“Very good. Then, it’s time to deal with the rest of you…”

As Lin Ming spoke these words, everyone’s complexions changed as if they had fallen into an icy lake. “You…”

Without waiting for these people to respond, black energy began surging up from Lin Ming, wildly erupting like a black volcano.

This black energy was Lin Ming’s soul force!

Such a terrifying soul force instantly shocked the Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciples!

Their jaws fell down and their eyes widened to full moons. “How is this even possible!?”

These disciples came from Divine Void Divine Kingdom and were also spiritas, thus they had a naturally deep understanding into the aspect of soul force. They originally thought that because Lin Ming was a human his attainments in the soul weren’t too amazing, and thus they were ordered to attack the Soaring Feather God Mountain disciples.

But now, seeing this human erupt with such a dreadful soul force, they were all frightened to death!

It had to be known that this was all occurring beneath the suppression of the final trial Laws. If this were outside, to what extent would his soul force reach? Perhaps even a spiritas Empyrean wouldn’t be able to compare!

A human, in the aspect of soul force, was able to surpass a spiritas Empyrean?

Such formidable strength and with such a terrifying soul force, could this man be the reincarnation of the Asura Road Master?

This was a ridiculous idea. But, what was occurring was so stunning that their frazzled minds couldn’t help but produce such a thought.

At this time, a black cube appeared in front of Lin Ming, slowly spinning around.

The black cube’s surface was engraved with mysterious patterns. As it appeared, it caused the surrounding space to collapse. Dim motes of divine light gathered in space, slowly floating towards the black cube, as if the black cube contained a real universe within.

This black cube was the Magic Cube.

During these years, Lin Ming had already fully restored his soul force. Moreover, because of the several reincarnations he underwent,  because he experienced the hundred tastes of life and death, because his mood and state of mind had been tempered, his soul force had broken past its previous boundaries to achieve an even more perfect Eternal Soul.

The Eternal Soul, ancient and unchanging.

Although this soul force might not be able to compare to those peak spiritas characters, in terms of quality, no one could compete!

As Lin Ming used his perfect Eternal Soul to galvanize the Magic Cube, he was truly able to command it!

For a time, the winds changed, whipping up. Massive dark clouds covered the surrounding space, and all of the Asura Road disciples suddenly saw illusions surround them as their spiritual seas fell into enemy hands.

The truth was that the moment these people saw the Magic Cube, their eyes were no longer able to leave it.

They forgot what danger they were in, they forgot everything. In their eyes all that existed was this divine object. Afterwards, because of the Magic Cube, their spiritual seas swung completely open.

Out of so many people, not a single one was able to resist Lin Ming.

What Lin Ming first wanted to do was erase all the memories of what had just occurred from the minds of these people.

Using Lin Ming’s evolved Eternal Soul and the divine tool that was the Magic Cube, he could perfectly accomplish this. He could do so with such skill that not even a True Divinity would be able to see through it.

Erasing memories was like a skilled criminal erasing all traces of his own crime from a crime scene. In order to be flawless, the criminal would have to remove every possible trace of his presence there, including every thread of hair or even mote of dust, all in order to make it seem that he had never been there at all, to the point that even the most intelligent detective would be at a loss of what to do, unable to argue against that criminal at all.

Lin Ming was such a criminal. This was because he knew that when these people returned, the ones investigating them would be Soul Emperor Divine Void and Soaring Feather God King.

Although Lin Ming’s strength was far inferior to these True Divinities’, his advantage was that he possessed the Magic Cube and Eternal Soul. When it came to erasing memories, if Lin Ming claimed he was second then no one in this universe could say they were number one.

After earnestly erasing all of these memories, Lin Ming repeatedly inspected them to make sure not a single trace of his presence was left behind. Then, he started to forge memories.

After erasing memories there would be an unexplainable void where they had been. One naturally had to craft new memories for the plan to be perfect.

However, while erasing memories was easy, forging memories was far, far more difficult.

If Lin Ming tried to forge memories from nothing, he couldn’t guarantee that he could hide the truth from a True Divinity.

But Lin Ming had another plan. That was, to manufacture ‘illusions’ that occurred in reality, and have these people experience what Lin Ming wanted them to.

Thus, they would believe everything that happened to them and would think that it was all real.

If they believed everything they saw was real, then these memories would truly be real.

No matter how sharp a True Divinity’s sense was, if they were to inspect memories that were real, what would they be able to find out?

Thus Lin Ming didn’t falsify memories. Rather, beneath his guidance, he had these Asura Road and Soaring Feather God Mountain disciples have real memories.

Under Lin Ming’s control, the Asura Road disciples’ minds were brought back to the moment they had seen the great ghost appear above the blackwater swamp.

In order to seize treasures they had rushed to the scene, where they engaged in a fierce battle with the disciples of the Good Fortune Saint Palace and Soaring Feather God Mountain.

Chapter 1978 – Fighting the Undying Polar Ice Once More

“I’ve awakened… it seems, I slept for another thousand years?”

“Mm. To be exact, you’ve slept for 1058 years…” Lin Ming smiled.

Over a thousand years ago, Empyrean Divine Mist had awoken for a short ten days. Then he fell asleep once more, resting until this moment.

The Magic Cube had the effect of stabilizing the soul. Empyrean Divine Mist wasn’t in a bad or good situation. As long he went through his period of slumber then his soul force wouldn’t weaken or increase.

“What you did this time could be called giving Divine Void a good deal of trouble.”

Empyrean Divine Mist lightly said. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign had done all of this in order to obtain the demon relic; he wouldn’t give up on it so easily. And in terms of strength, Divine Void Divine Kingdom was weaker than the Good Fortune Saint Palace. However, within the Asura Road and with the protection of the Asura Road’s Laws, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign shouldn’t dare to do anything reckless.

“Perhaps. Cause and effect runs in circles. Divine Void and Senior have a grudge with each other, and since I’ve received help from Senior, it’s normal for me to pay some interest back to Divine Void Divine Kingdom…”

Lin Ming’s response was calm. He was someone who remembered grudges and gratitude. When he attacked the disciples of the Good Fortune Saint Palace and Soaring Feather God Mountain, this was because they were on opposite sides to begin with, not to mention that they had already killed many Asura Road disciples when they took the treasure. If Lin Ming were to let them go, then in the next several thousand years, the number of young human elites they killed would only increase.

Regarding Divine Void Divine Kingdom, Lin Ming only wanted to deal with Soul Emperor Divine Void. As for the disciples of Divine Void Divine Kingdom, Lin Ming had no problems with them, thus he let them live.

“Is that so… the samsara of gratitude and grudge, the circle of karma…”

Upon mentioning his enmity with Divine Void, Empyrean Divine Mist had a strange feeling stir in his heart. Ever since he was sealed in the Magic Cube, Divine Void probably thought he had died…

“But, everything you’ve done today will only give Divine Void some trouble. It’s impossible to shake his foundation.”

Divine Mist quietly murmured. Lin Ming nodded. “I’m not hoping that this matter will provoke some great war. At most, it will divert the attention of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. And I also feel that I can’t hide the truth of this matter from the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. He will likely discover some questionable points…”

Lin Ming didn’t care whether or not his actions would provoke a war. His main goal was to conceal his whereabouts.

“Mm, making sure you are safe and ensuring no news that you are alive spreads is more important than anything else. You still have many days ahead for that…”

As Empyrean Divine Mist spoke, he fell into a deep slumber once more.

Lin Ming’s current strength was lacking. According to Empyrean Divine Mist’s earlier suggestion, he had to complete the seventh revolution of the Grand Reincarnation Art and raise his cultivation to the half-step Empyrean or even true Empyrean realm before he could fully reveal himself.

But Lin Ming could feel that the Empyrean realm was a long, long time away.

While he simultaneously studied two of the highest Laws and had to pay attention to the Grand Reincarnation Art, Lin Ming doubted he would be able to break into the Empyrean realm within 10,000 years.

This speed was far slower than Emperor Shakya.

And compared to the Good Fortune Saint Son, it was even slower than that.

This was the price of practicing the Grand Reincarnation Art.

At this time, Lin Ming entered the final trial’s fifth level.

Although the space within the final trial changed each time, the fifth level always stayed the same.

The one who guarded this floor was the Undying Inferno and the Undying Polar Ice.

In the past, Lin Ming and Sheng Mei had joined forces to bring down the Undying Polar Ice, causing their reputations to soar.

Now he arrived here by himself and would have to face the enemy alone.

Because he practiced the Grand Reincarnation Art, Lin Ming had a skeletal age advantage in the final trial. The Undying Inferno’s attacks weren’t able to pose any threat to him. He relied on his understandings of the Fire Laws to easily avoid every strike aimed his way.

Then, the Undying Inferno eventually exhausted itself of energy and turned into a phoenix egg. Lin Ming crossed his hands behind his back, looking at this happen.

He didn’t attack, but waited for the Undying Polar Ice that was hidden in the phoenix egg to hatch out.

Lin Ming had chosen to strike down the fifth level guardian while it was in its Undying Polar Ice form in order to obtain the highest completion percentage possible.

This was because the Undying Polar Ice was restrained by Lin Ming’s attributes.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Cold energy started to gather from the heavens and earth, condensing high in the air.

Horrifying Ice Laws locked down this space. One could see that in the center of this gathering cold energy, there was a flashing ice crystal. This ice crystal started to condense into a small ice phoenix.

As more cold energy gathered, the phoenix grew larger and larger. In an instant, an aura that could freeze the world suddenly and furiously whipped up!

Bang! Bang! Bang!

The earth quaked. Glacier after glacier drilled out from the ground, towering 100,000 feet high!

A lilting smile crossed Lin Ming’s lips.

Undying Polar Ice. After not seeing it for several thousand years, he was finally able to fight it again!

In the past, Lin Ming had to wait for Sheng Mei to use the Umbral Heaven Ice Array and pass through layers of dangers, blocking the Undying Polar Ice’s attacks in order to exhaust it of energy. When it had turned into an egg, Lin Ming then rushed out, using the Black Dragon Spear to kill the Undying Polar Ice in a single all-out strike!

But this time, Lin Ming didn’t plan on waiting. The moment the Undying Polar Ice appeared, Lin Ming rushed forwards!

He wanted to face the Undying Polar Ice while it was in its peak state. He planned to engage it in a brutal melee!

This was a crazy plan. If Sheng Mei saw this then even she would be understandably shocked.

Hu - !

With a keen whistling sound, the Black Dragon Spear flew out from Lin Ming’s spatial ring!

This spear hadn’t appeared for thousands of years. In these thousands of years, Lin Ming had also never fought with everything he had in his peak state.

Now, as the familiar weight of the Black Dragon Spear returned to its owner’s hand, it emitted a loud hum as if the soul of a Divine Dragon were awakening within the shaft!

Hum –

Hum –

Hum –

Threads of cold energy gathered, becoming increasingly thick and potent. Within the chilling icy winds, the Undying Polar Ice was enraged. It was angry that a mere human dared to challenge its endless might!

It turned towards Lin Ming and hurtled down at him, its speed soon reaching the extreme. In the legends, it was said that ancient Rocs could pass 90,000 miles with a single flap of the wings, without needing to use any Space Laws.

Although the ice phoenix was slower than an ancient Roc, it wasn’t much worse. Of course, this was in a situation where it didn’t utilize the Space Laws. Only this speed was true speed, a speed capable of surpassing the reaction time of others!

This was because its attack wouldn’t bring about fluctuations of the Laws, thus it became impossible for others to sense it.

Whoosh!

The Undying Polar Ice immediately appeared in front of Lin Ming. It stretched out a giant claw that radiated a freezing light, grasping down at him!

This claw was covered with a freezing ice force field. Any life form that was covered by this force field would have their mortal body and soul both frozen away.

So to avoid the Undying Polar Ice’s attack, speed alone was not enough. One needed the ability to deal with the force field that came along with the Undying Polar Ice’s attack!

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank and he drew backwards. His body started to burn with black flames. As these flames lit up all around him, they carried the true meaning of nirvanic rebirth, directly burning away that freezing ice force field.

Lin Ming stepped on the void and vanished like smoke. In terms of natural speed he was inferior to the Undying Polar Ice, thus he used the Space Laws without hesitation. And when it came to the Space Laws, he surpassed the Undying Polar Ice by countless miles. Even if he wildly used the Space Laws however he wished, it would be near impossible for the Undying Polar Ice to lock onto these Law fluctuations and locate Lin Ming’s position.

In an instant, Lin Ming had already appeared behind the Undying Polar Ice.

Nine great stars gleamed above Lin Ming’s head. Starlight poured down, pouring into his mortal body. From within him, the Purple Temple Dao Palace, Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace, Extreme Polar Dao Palace, Daevic Eye Dao Palace, all of them began to open one after another!

The Black Dragon Spear was infused with the power of nine stars. It crushed through space with overwhelming momentum as it savagely pounded down!

Kacha!

Like a bolt of divine lightning falling from the highest heavens, it smashed into the Undying Polar Ice’s back.

The phoenix’s back could even carry a mountain. But as Lin Ming’s spear smashed into it, not only did the freezing ice force field shatter apart but those beautiful ice feathers also cracked open, leaving bits and pieces of ice flying out.

Icy blue blood flowed out from these wounds. In truth, this wasn’t blood but liquid condensed from the purest ice energy in the world. If an ice-attribute martial artist could obtain but a single drop, it would be a treasure beyond compare.

The Undying Polar Ice was incensed. It had protected the final trial’s fifth level for billions of years, and during this period there had been people capable of shattering the egg it transformed into, but there had never been someone capable of wounding it in direct frontal combat!

It roared out once more as it hurtled towards Lin Ming!

Ka ka ka!

The void froze, cracking open! A deep blue beam of light shot out from the Undying Polar Ice’s mouth, straight towards Lin Ming’s chest!

This freezing cold beam of energy was horrifyingly powerful; it far exceeded Lin Ming with his suppressed cultivation.

After all, the Undying Polar Ice was in its peak state. When it was created in the past, it was formed in a default state so that no one would be able to defeat it in its peak condition.

Lin Ming didn’t defend. His two pupils suddenly contracted, turning as thin as pins. Around his pupils, mystical patterns appeared.

In that moment, he had opened the Three Lives Pupil.

Three Lives Pupil – All Existence to Void!

When combined with the Daevic Eye Dao Palace, in a mere moment, the complete method with which the Undying Polar Ice utilized the Ice Laws was seen through by Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s eyes no longer saw that blinding blue light. Rather, what he saw was a Law structure composed of endless cold energy essence.

The power of thunder and fire erupted from Lin Ming’s body. The phantom of the Heretical God Tree appeared behind him. The two strengths collided and a terrifying explosion of energy blew into the skies, causing the world to change and origin energy to gush out in violent waves.

Beneath the suppression of Laws, the disparity in cultivation was made up for. The Undying Polar Ice’s attack had been forcefully broken by Lin Ming!

The Undying Polar Ice became increasingly furious. It fought Lin Ming in close-range combat!

Its vorpal wings and sharp claws were dreadful weapons.

Bang!

With another frontal collision, Lin Ming was sent flying back. But, he didn’t fall into a disadvantage. He rushed out once more, engaging the Undying Polar Ice in brutal battle!

A battle of bodies, a showdown of energy. The Black Dragon Spear in Lin Ming’s hand seemed to turn into a black dragon that flew about in the air.

In the skies, a dragon and phoenix contended for supremacy!

The numerous 100,000 foot high glaciers were unable to withstand this terrifying storm of energy. All of them crashed down in rumbling avalanches.

Mountain-sized chunks of ice crashed into the ground and dissolved into icy rivers of water. This was an apocalyptic scene.

Chapter 1980 – Emperor Cemetery

The three emperor jades were placed into the grooves one at a time. The emperor jades lined up in the grooves, and then, the entire statue lit up with a dazzling divine light. At the same time, a vortex began forming in the void beneath the statue.

Lin Ming was sucked into the vortex. The scenery changed, and in the next moment, Lin Ming arrived in a dark gray world.

The first time Lin Ming entered the smelting trial he had already learned about the existence of the seventh level. When he discovered that the three emperor jades of fate were required to open it, he had always been thinking just what that place would look like.

Would this be a test with a heaven-defying difficulty, or would it purely be rewards?

Lin Ming’s imagination had become even more intense when he obtained the third emperor jade of fate. But because of all the tribulations he had suffered afterwards and everything else that had occurred to him, he had pushed those thoughts out of his head.

Today, Lin Ming would finally step into the seventh level and see everything there…

But the scene that appeared in front of him left him startled.

What he saw was… a vast cemetery.

This was a pure gray world. The sky was disorderly and the earth was barren. In this land, rows of graves were lined up, tens of thousands of them.

These graves occupied a square area of land. They were all of the same gray and black stone, a solemn and reverent atmosphere swirling around them.

Lin Ming didn’t know if they were protected by an array formation or if the tombstones were forged from some type of special rock. But, even after 10 billion years passed, these tombstones remained whole. The only difference was that one could feel the breath of endless years coming from the elegant writings carved into the stone.

Lin Ming walked to the front of a tombstone. This tombstone was carved with the words of the ancient god race.

“Extreme Emperor Heavens’ Reverent White Arc Xiu Kao’s Tomb.”

A mortal’s tombstone would also have an inscription; it would be carved with the names of their children and grandchildren.

As for this tombstone, it didn’t have anything besides the grave master’s name and title.

As for the words Extreme Emperor Heavens, it should be the name of a universe, in other words, one of the 33 Heavens.

Lin Ming had never heard the name of Extreme Emperor Heavens before. But, this wasn’t strange at all. Far too much time had passed and it wasn’t strange for the names of the 33 Heavens to change during this period. Moreover, this was a name that existed 10 billion years ago. In the ancient era, every one of the 33 Heavens was prosperous and glorious. But now, only 16 Heavens were developed; the other 17 Heavens had turned into wildernesses.

Reverent White Arc Xiu Kao, of these words, Xiu Kao was clearly a name. It was a strange surname and an even stranger first name, but perhaps in the ancient era 10 billion years ago, this might have been a normal or even popular name.

As for Reverent White Arc, that was naturally the title of the grave’s master.

What a Reverent was, Lin Ming had no idea, but it sounded like a title no worse than an Empyrean. If so, then in this cemetery where there were unknown tens of thousands of graves, was an Empyrean level or above powerhouse buried in each one?

Lin Ming found this hard to imagine. It had to be known that in the entire Divine Realm, there had only been a mere 200-300 Empyreans.

Even for the saints and spiritas, when their Empyreans were added together from each of their seven Heavens, they only had a thousand or so.

Compared to the cemetery in front of him that had tens of thousands of Empyreans buried here, Lin Ming simply felt this was too unbelievable.

The ancient era 10 billion years ago was a time when a hundred races strove for supremacy. It was a time when the primal god race and the celestials dominated the 33 Heavens. At that time, heroes rose up from the ranks and young elites were innumerable. However… if it were said that several tens of thousands of Empyreans were buried here so casually, Lin Ming would still think that it was quite odd.

As Lin Ming thought like this, he walked behind the tombstone. This part was similar to a mortal’s tombstone, and was carved with the epitaph of the grave’s master.

There were a few hundred words written into the stone. As Lin Ming read these words he was inwardly flabbergasted by what was written. The master of the grave was indeed an Empyrean level powerhouse, moreover, he hadn’t been an ordinary Empyrean. From the vague information given, Lin Ming speculated that if this person were placed in the current era, he would be similar to a middle or even upper Empyrean.

However, this proud son of heaven that existed 10 billion years ago had actually suffered such a fate: “Bones unfound, his sword is buried here.”

This grave was only the tomb of a sword; Xiu Kao’s body was not here.

Lin Ming sighed. He looked at the next grave – Sky Zenith Heavens’ Demon Concubine Yuan Chun’s Tomb.

Lin Ming had never heard of a Sky Zenith Heavens before. If there was a Heavens that dared to call itself by such a name, then perhaps 10 billion years ago, this Sky Zenith Heavens had been one of the peak universes?

The master of this grave Yuan Chun was a woman, and according to her epitaph, she had been a peerlessly talented and proud woman. Her life had been dazzling but her final fate was “Died in battle within the great calamity of the 33 Heavens. Her feather robe lies buried here.”

This grave was only a tomb for Yuan Chun’s clothes.

Lin Ming continued looking. He saw many outstanding figures of the ancient past. Their origins and lives were briefly described on their graves. They came from different universes of the 33 Heavens, and each one of them was a ruler of their era, a king of their time!

Their strength was far beyond that of the Empyreans of the present!

But of these people, only a small number had their bodies buried here. Most of these graves were filled with battle armors, weapons, clothes, or some other objects that the grave master used before their death. There were even some people that only had a tombstone as a marker, with nothing inside at all.

In addition, on their epitaphs, the words ‘33 Heavens calamity’ appeared more than once.

Demon Concubine Yuan Chi had died in battle within the great calamity of the 33 Heavens.

Martial Saint Huang Qi had died in battle within the great calamity of the 33 Heavens.

Cold Ice Fairy Yun Meng had died in battle within the great calamity of the 33 Heavens…

…….

Lin Ming guessed that after these people died in the great calamity, someone had specifically built graves for them. This was because after that great war, it became too difficult to find their corpses, thus these tombs were only filled with clothes and other objects to serve as mementos to their previous existence.

Realizing this, Lin Ming became lost in thought.

In the last 10 billion years of history of the 33 Heavens, a great calamity that could be called a catastrophe of the universe had erupted many times already.

Each time, countless powerhouses died in battle. Sometimes even entire races were exterminated.

The 33 Heavens calamity that was written on these epitaphs clearly affected a much larger area than humanity’s calamity, and the influence it left on the world was even greater!

In the past, these peerless powerhouses that died in the great calamity once shook the earth and heavens, ruling over vast domains through force. But even for these people, after they died, all that was left behind were these square graves that didn’t even hold their bodies.

No one remembered their names, no one remembered their history. All that remained in remembrance of them was a cold tombstone.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming deeply sighed.

No matter how powerful a person, no matter how powerful a race, when they were placed in the endless river of time they were nothing more than a tiny wave. When they rose up they shined in blinding brilliance, but soon, they quickly vanished into the never-ending stream, leaving nothing behind.

This was also the reason why so many martial artists were unwilling to turn to ash, the reason they continued to climb up and seek out the road to eternal life. However, no one had ever succeeded…

“Perhaps this calamity of the 33 Heavens is the great war that erupted 10 billion years ago, and that war was the catalyst that started the primal god race’s decline from their peak. After the war, the Asura Road Master and Holy Scripture creator also went missing, and they left behind their own places of inheritance – the Asura Road and the Akashic Dream Universe. Then… could these graves have been left behind by the Asura Road Master?”

Lin Ming suddenly thought. But no matter how he turned it around in his mind, there was no way he could verify this.

He moved deeper into the cemetery. A light gray fog wafted in the air here. As Lin Ming moved forwards, the fog gradually diverged from before him and he saw what lay at the end of these tombstones.

This, was a great cliff!

And beneath this cliff was not an abyss, but an endless starry space!

This sort of feeling was as if a part of an ancient continent was thrust into space, and here was where it broke off!

Lin Ming stood on the edge of the cliff, looking at the trillions of stars that shined in the distance. As they sparkled in the far-off distance, they seemed cold and lonely. They had existed there for a long time, and would continue existing.

And in this starry space, a long distance away from Lin Ming, a massive white altar floated. As he saw this white altar, his eyes were captured by it and were no longer able to move away.

This white altar was as large as a planet and was like a pyramid in shape. From the top to the bottom, the altar consisted of 33 steps.

“Divine Seal Altar!”

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. In the past when Lin Ming attended the semifinals of the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, the test site had been the Divine Seal Altar.

But, that Divine Seal Altar had been a replica created by Empyrean Vast Universe. A long time ago, Empyrean Vast Universe had stumbled upon a fragment of the Divine Seal Altar that was forged by Empyrean Divine Seal, a human True Divinity who existed 3.6 billion years ago. Empyrean Vast Universe had fused this fragment into the replica he created, allowing that replica to obtain a portion of the ancient Divine Seal Altar’s spirituality.

However, the truth was that the ‘original’ Divine Seal Altar that Empyrean Divine Seal created 3.6 billion years ago was also a replica.

If Lin Ming wasn’t wrong, then Empyrean Divine Seal had participated in the Asura Road’s final trial in the past, and when he moved from the fourth level to the fifth level, he too had to face the test of ascending the Divine Seal Altar.

But even so, the difference between the sizes of that Divine Seal Altar and the one before him was far too great!

The Divine Seal Altar in front of him, whether it was in the aura it exuded or the horrifying energy it contained, all of it left Lin Ming fearful and apprehensive, nearly unable to withstand it.

Perhaps the Divine Seal Altar that was placed as the test between the fourth and fifth level was in truth nothing but a projection of the true Divine Seal Altar.

And the Divine Seal Altar was likely not even called the Divine Seal Altar; it should have another name. The name of Divine Seal Altar was only bestowed upon it because of Empyrean Divine Seal.

As Lin Ming thought this he slowly soared upwards. Carefully, he flew towards the Divine Seal Altar that was deep in the starry skies.

After some time, he began to slow down. As he looked at the Divine Seal Altar that was far off in the skies, a look of amazement crossed his eyes.

At the top of the 33 Heavens Divine Seal Altar there were clearly people!

And not just one person, but two… although they were extremely far away, Lin Ming could see two blurry figures. And as soon as he swept out his divine sense he could clearly discern their appearance.

These two people wore white long robes and their faces were wizened and elderly. They had wide thoughtful smiles, as if they were waiting there especially for him.

Lin Ming paused. He hesitated for a moment, and then continued flying towards these two old men.